<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>editor</author>
  <title>Syed Hamad Raza</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt; text-align: justify" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Justice Denied&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt; text-align: justify" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 172px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=Dialogue2_a.jpg" alt="" width="172" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt; text-align: justify" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;By: &lt;em&gt;Shabana Hamad Raza&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 14&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; May. 7&amp;rsquo;o clock alarm bells on Hamad&amp;rsquo;s mobile as it did on every morning. It has been a year since, but that alarm bell still echoes in my mind and shivers my soul. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;It was time for him to wake up and go to office. But it was not an ordinary day. Instead of being on his bed, he was lying breathless at the PIMS emergency ward. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;[more]&lt;/span&gt;My hands being red with his blood as I carried him to the hospital. There he was lying in front of me, but could not hear my screams. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;lsquo;Hamad utho tumhay office jana hai, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Haniah&lt;span style="color: black"&gt; aur Hamza ko school chorna hai, Hayaan ko apni gaud mein uthana hai&amp;rsquo;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;But he never replied. All had come to stand still for me. My throat choked as I could not hear my own self. My soul mate was silenced and so was my life. I wish that this day would not have existed in my life calendar. I start to tremble at every moment, whenever the thought of him not being beside me crosses my mind. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;In a short companionship of six years and nine months he gave me everything which a man can offer to his spouse. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; color: black; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Today after a year, I feel myself obliged to present tribute to this great human being, an obedient son, a caring husband, a loving and involved father, whom I knew as Hamad and the people remember as Syed Hamad Raza. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;On the fateful morning of 14th May 2007, in the midst of the judicial crisis, my husband Syed Hamad Raza, Additional Registrar Supreme Court of Pakistan was shot at point-blank range, in front of me and our three little kids at our then recently occupied official residence in Islamabad.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Born in 1970 in Sharaqpur, District Shekupura after 10 years of his parents&amp;rsquo; marriage; his birth was not less than a festivity. Being the only child he was loved by the entire family. As he grew up, his talents and skills kept on getting refined. He proved his mettle wherever he went, and left a lasting impression at every footstep. A proud Atchisonian, a gold medallist of Quaid-e-Azam University in International Relations, and lastly a highly respected DMG officer were few of his many notable traits. He was very well read and had a very fine taste for Urdu poetry. His friends praised his demeanour, his conflict resolution style, and believed that he was born to be a DMG officer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Shining all along his educational years, he joined Civil Services of Pakistan (District Management Group) in 1995. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;The common phrase of putting service before own self is claimed by majority of us; lest it is proved practically. Hamad was no ordinary officer. With a God gifted intellect, and a clear headed vision; he had already set his priorities and established his goals. In days to come, he amply demonstrated his dedication and commitment to his service and nation. In an environment where Punjab domiciled officers are reluctant to serve outside the province, more specifically in tough environs of Balochistan, Hamad&amp;rsquo;s youthful exuberance proved to be an exception. He gave 11 years of his prime time to the people of Balochistan and delivered effectively where ever he was appointed. It was for that matter that the entire region remembers his services and was the most grieved ones on his sudden tragic death. From 1995 to 2006, he served as Assistant Commissioner Ziarat, Pasheen, Sibbi, Usta Muhammad, Deputy Commissioner Kharan, Director Health Department Quetta and Deputy Secretary to the Chief Secretary Balochistan. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;His professionalism and personal qualities were acknowledged by all and sundry. This had less to do with his position, rather due to his genial temperament and positive attitude towards his subordinates and ordinary people who brought their applications before him. Although he knew his limitations as a civil servant, he was never afraid to pursue the problems of common people even if it rattled some higher ups. It is a fact that even being a DMG officer, he would often get money from his parents, which underscores his honesty and truthfulness. &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;I came into Hamad&amp;rsquo;s life in February 1999, as we got formally engaged. Subsequently we got married in August 2000. It was an arranged marriage, but the post marriage days were spent as if synonymous to years old association. Allah Almighty blessed us with three beautiful angels, our children Haniah, Hamza and Hayaan; the youngest one being replica of Hamad, both in expressions and behaviour. Hayaan was 11 months when he lost his &lt;em&gt;baba&lt;/em&gt; and would hardly have any memory of his father ever. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Everything around me today reminds me of him and the beautiful times we spent together. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;After a long stay in Balochistan, in areas whose name I had not even heard of; we moved to Islamabad in 2006, as Hamad was given the prestigious appointment of the Additional Registrar of the highest court of law in the country. He was very happy on it; I was delighted too and felt pride as I saw my husband gradually progressing in his professional carrier. After a year of waiting for accommodation, we finally got it in March. We both were very delighted and were in the process of renovating and decorating our beautiful home. Little did I know that all would be ruined within no time. The skies fell on me on the doom&amp;rsquo;s day of 14 May. It left me with nothing. I felt myself robbed of everything I possessed. A future we both planned will not come to be, the dreams we shared will never be realized. I lost my soul. Today, I feel tempted to even question the meaning of my life. Why this happened? &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;And a series of other unanswered questions swirls around my head in an infinite succession.&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Will they ever be answered, I really do not know. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;A nation is great because of the way its people think. This is what I have realized over the past one year, as scores of people around the world saluted the professionalism, integrity and commitment of my husband. I am highly indebted to the elders and common people of Balochistan who came all the way to console me, and offered their support. I realized that there is no big achievement in this world than to win the hearts of the masses with your character and fair play. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;I am thankful to all the people of Pakistan who have given me the respect of a Shaheed&amp;rsquo;s widow and consoled me in these times of grief. I have no words to express my gratitude to Hamad&amp;rsquo;s friends who have been more of a family all along. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;I have not lost hope. Will my husband&amp;rsquo;s death go in vain? No it would never. It shall invigorate the will of every individual who has ordained himself to be truly committed to this nation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: Arial"&gt;Hamad, keep an eye on me, as I live through these years, filling my empty days with your thoughts. In my capacity, I promise you, that I will teach our children the values you practiced. Inshallah one day the &amp;lsquo;Hamad&amp;rsquo; inside these three angels would show his presence carrying on the legacy of truthfulness, integrity and self belief, and would make you feel proud as you watch from heavens. Aameen . Just keep an eye Hamad. The world is not the same without you. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #5f497a"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-05-14 13:40:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:48:38</lastModified>
  <raters>7</raters>
  <rating>4.857143</rating>
  <slug>Syed-Hamad-Raza</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="26ca6d8e-8a97-46eb-8be1-a70a1c2b044e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-07 05:37:26</date>
      <author>blocked drain</author>
      <email>SallyHeath@mailaeb.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.160.86.99</ip>
      <website>http://www.blocked-drain.info/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have viewed some other posts and comments which are generally in accord with  Syed Hamad Raza but I have to recognise that this item has some additional detail.  Keep touching off views in others!  I actually value the manner you have penned this.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="82d510a9-c5b3-41bd-ab7c-ca5049f2cfa7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-05-28 21:47:44</date>
      <author>kredyty na dowod</author>
      <email>glendanelson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.70.24.107</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, I enjoy reading through your post. I like to write a little comment to support you.

Also visit my website -  kredyty na dowod - http://szybkiechwilowkionlineprzezinternet.pl </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3f0ea20d-501a-44bb-8913-e7c38b8839ba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 02:33:52</date>
      <author>body revolution Reviews</author>
      <email>iona.pitre@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.169.198</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! Quick question that&amp;#39;s completely off topic. Do you know how to make your site mobile friendly? My blog looks weird when browsing from my iphone. I&amp;#39;m trying to find a theme or plugin that might be able to fix this issue. If you have any recommendations, please share. Many thanks!

Here is my site  body revolution Reviews - http://yourdigitalslrexpert.com/discover-the-jillian-michaels-exercise-strategy-that-is-right-for-you </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="28946ae7-0686-48de-85da-038b2b413a33" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-27 18:14:57</date>
      <author>auskultation</author>
      <email>amber.feldman@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.39.97.17</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks for one&amp;#39;s marvelous posting! I seriously enjoyed reading it, you happen to be a great author. I will make sure to bookmark your blog and will come back in the future. I want to encourage yourself to continue your great writing, have a nice weekend!

My website  lunge - http://goldway.ru/wiki/index.php?title=%D0%A3%D1%87%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%BA:Sophia2091 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="919661f0-90aa-4346-8fd8-2b4fe206ce9f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 18:04:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia 1300 extract with 60 hca &amp;amp; no artificial ingredients</author>
      <email>trevorbeckham@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Admiring the dedication you put into your website and detailed information you present. It&amp;#39;s good to come across a blog every once in a while that isn&amp;#39;t the same old rehashed information. Wonderful read! I&amp;#39;ve bookmarked your site and I&amp;#39;m adding your RSS feeds to my Google account.

Here is my web-site ::  garcinia cambogia 1300 extract with 60 hca &amp;amp; no artificial ingredients - http://www.webdirectorieslist.org/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ceab665-1e10-446e-a08a-e5c2e7f2f9d4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 17:58:15</date>
      <author>Body Revolution</author>
      <email>tammivargas@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there! I&amp;#39;ve been reading your weblog for some time now and finally got the courage to go ahead and give you a shout out from  Lubbock Texas! Just wanted to tell you keep up the fantastic work!

Here is my homepage -  Body Revolution - http://journals.fotki.com/fredericerdmann/fredericerdmann/entry/brftkqwtqsks/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8606701b-d44c-4ec6-9a67-f1564a4a8640" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 01:16:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements</author>
      <email>jesus-presley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Do you have a spam issue on this website; I also am a blogger, and I was wanting to know your situation; many of us have developed some nice methods and we are looking to swap solutions with other folks, be sure to shoot me an e-mail if interested.

Feel free to surf to my weblog;  garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements - http://soratrasancargo.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-fit/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68ce2688-738e-4128-a648-cd7de0b327eb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 08:19:01</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>candy_carey@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one needs to be updated with most up-to-date technologies afterward he must be visit this site and be up to date everyday.

Here is my homepage -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.buildingfamilies411.com/?p=14 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="70a186f3-8b0d-4cf2-ae18-9940a8013084" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 18:27:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure 60 hca</author>
      <email>christeldoolittle@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I was checking continuously this blog and I&amp;#39;m impressed! Very helpful information specially the last part :) I care for such info much. I was seeking this particular information for a very long time. Thank you and best of luck.

Feel free to surf to my web blog -  garcinia cambogia extract pure 60 hca - http://delhicityguide.net/perks-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e86b2cd5-ac3a-46b9-83bb-6a9940293150" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 18:10:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>randell-trimble@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello! I simply would like to offer you a huge thumbs up for your great information you have right here on this post. I&amp;#39;ll be coming back to your site for more soon.

Feel free to visit my site -  garcinia cambogia - http://cg-tg.com/?p=85 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="55d34347-e337-4483-a8de-7709190d7a51" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 03:56:08</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>deanne.isom@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like the valuable info you provide for your articles. I will bookmark your weblog and test again right here regularly. I&amp;#39;m rather certain I will be informed many new stuff right right here! Good luck for the next!

Also visit my web page  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7b559792-cef4-4bcc-9497-81874d1c9715" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 15:43:11</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure retail shipping cost you Save</author>
      <email>marguerite.woods@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am really inspired along with your writing skills as well as with the format in your weblog. Is that this a paid theme or did you modify it yourself? Anyway stay up the nice quality writing, it&amp;#39;s rare to see a nice weblog like this one these days..

Stop by my blog -  garcinia cambogia extract pure retail shipping cost you Save - http://www.marketintelgroup.com/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1fa3044c-37e5-40ed-8674-ab8bddf0bc68" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 17:07:18</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>jeffery.thorne@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Spot on with this write-up, I truly think this web site needs a great deal more attention. I&amp;#39;ll probably be back again to see more, thanks for the info!

Feel free to surf to my weblog ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.gsbrd.com/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-drop-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="eff2c9ac-7bae-45d4-94a3-ec1003f092a7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 22:41:47</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>randolph_francisco@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My brother suggested I may like this blog. He was once totally right. This publish truly made my day. You cann&amp;#39;t consider simply how a lot time I had spent for this information! Thank you!

my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia - http://pultneyvillehistoricalsociety.org/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b48c40bd-ae66-4921-a3ae-3337afca81d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 07:54:28</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>salpepper@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;d like to thank you for the efforts you&amp;#39;ve put in writing this site. I&amp;#39;m hoping to see the same high-grade content from you in the future as well. In fact, your creative writing abilities has encouraged me to get my own, personal website now ;)

Also visit my website ...  Garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.meditationbuzz.com/insights-on-immediate-products-in-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f077a4a7-f4f2-4951-a913-6daee97541b3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 13:19:00</date>
      <author>miracle garcinia cambogia dr oz</author>
      <email>margheritaesquivel@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You have made some good points there. I checked on the web for additional information about the issue and found most people will go along with your views on this website.

My site ...  miracle garcinia cambogia dr oz - http://thegreetingcardbox.com/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="907f475b-5126-47e7-b41d-49fb98037ae7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 04:40:57</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>suzannadevito@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.19.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is really interesting, You are a very skilled blogger. I&amp;#39;ve joined your feed and look forward to seeking more of your magnificent post. Also, I&amp;#39;ve shared your web site in my social networks!

Also visit my weblog ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.hhqy.net/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cc9fa86e-38de-42c2-8dc9-2de688c17fef" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 02:37:09</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>sherri-lockhart@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.100</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Definitely believe that which you said. Your favorite justification appeared to be on the net the simplest thing to be aware of. I say to you, I definitely get annoyed while people think about worries that they plainly don&amp;#39;t know about. You managed to hit the nail upon the top and also defined out the whole thing without having side-effects , people could take a signal. Will probably be back to get more. Thanks

My blog -  pure garcinia cambogia - http://petfriendlyassociation.com/can-garcinia-cambogia-extract-assist-much-with-weight-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="29f26b65-9a6e-428a-ba61-c0964b27d763" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-29 22:28:44</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>belindakeck@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.88.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up this is kinda of off topic but I was wondering if blogs use WYSIWYG editors or if you have to manually code with HTML. I&amp;#39;m starting a blog soon but have no coding knowledge so I wanted to get guidance from someone with experience. Any help would be greatly appreciated!

Also visit my page ::  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://dixongrove.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="86541334-a8ad-47d4-bf77-e91da579d84d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-21 12:34:47</date>
      <author>wiki.woopi.org</author>
      <email>joshua-scanlon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.119.227.55</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Feasible of evaluation connected with the collateral is the whole system run smoothly. For treating such messy situation, it is smarter to opt to gain DSS loans.

Take a look at my web site ... risk unsecured ( wiki.woopi.org - http://wiki.woopi.org/mediawiki/index.php?title=Organization_Loans_For_The_Woman_With_Bad_Credit )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="de9e0baa-8323-4703-bacd-0aeb04c40fc8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-14 21:10:04</date>
      <author>http://www.lovemyweddingphotographer.com/miami/standards-for-clear-cut-taxi-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com-strategies/</author>
      <email>delphia.greeves@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.191.20</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Don Havird, co-owner of Capitol City Cab, said the e-hail plan might actually combat any discrimination, since drivers wouldn&amp;#39;t be able to tell their friends their grandad&amp;#39;s a mummy&amp;#39;. Was shot and killed July 4, 2013 in Chicago, Illinois. The man, who was quickly taken into custody, according to MCSO, who say at one point Lopez even told the girl he could get into trouble because of her age.

Visit my page ... taxi insurance,  http://www.lovemyweddingphotographer.com/miami/standards-for-clear-cut-taxi-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com-strategies/ - http://www.lovemyweddingphotographer.com/miami/standards-for-clear-cut-taxi-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com-strategies/ ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f248e00d-861b-4bd5-9ce8-620e335e9159" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 11:59:00</date>
      <author>Lawanna</author>
      <email>lawanna.muirden@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.191.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The difficulty for the UK and predicted david cameron the Prime Minister&amp;#39;s existing proposals. Carla Windhorst is seated next to Downing Street last year, Mr Cameron said:&amp;quot; I have heard he is not paying his taxes in the Budget in March.

Feel free to surf to my webpage: tax dodger,  Lawanna - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7f120a35-6382-4618-92f4-7e2e7ea17a3b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-02 21:07:59</date>
      <author>Lina</author>
      <email>linahummel@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.33.14</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>30pm Bannan had been driving a car that was&amp;quot; too powerful&amp;quot; on a night during poor weather conditions. District convicted drivers judge Peter Veits banned Stott from driving for 18 months, after admitting four offences including driving with excess alcohol is a serious matter indeed. Kathryn Jones, prosecuting, told the court the defendant had been a passenger in his Jaguar XJ8 when she hit standing water while driving at over 60mph.

My webpage - cheap car insurance for convicted drivers ( Lina - http://youtarab.com/activity/p/31755/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="27576aa0-3431-4a84-bcb0-3e12138a3f12" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-30 09:33:06</date>
      <author>why is travel insurance so expensive in australia</author>
      <email>rozellafrancisco@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.203</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The easy travel insurance decisions are those that are not excluded cover either. But, the card issuers report a &amp;#39;high limit&amp;#39;, which may takes days to arrive,&amp;quot; he said.

Also visit my webpage ::  why is travel insurance so expensive in australia - http://flashcafe.org/?document_srl=298640 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c820528a-bed5-483c-ab04-6b3d46e4fa4d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-03 15:00:04</date>
      <author>sole trader business insurance</author>
      <email>wolfgangbergin@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.44.19.141</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good luck and let me hear from you. But now seeing my belongings spread out before me, the night that I consummate my marriage,&amp;quot; said Stephen Gichuki, the director general of the British Airways customer services desk. To public liability insurance meet the growing expectations and improved standard of living of the residents of this locality.

Here is my web-site ::  sole trader business insurance - http://bananamoonproject.com/xe/board/9582080 </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>kim_abdalian@yahoo.com</email>
    <email>imranhasan1019@hotmail.com</email>
    <email>awshaikh70@yahoo.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>