<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Thousands face death row reprieve</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p class="first"&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 226px; height: 300px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=_44593151_sarabjit_afp270.jpg" alt="" width="226" height="300" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="first"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The Pakistani cabinet has approved a plan to commute the sentences of thousands of prisoners on death row to life imprisonment, officials say.&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The proposal, which must be endorsed by President Musharraf, is expected to benefit some 7,000 condemned prisoners. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Rights group Amnesty International said the move would reprieve about one-third of the world&amp;#39;s death row population. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
It is still not clear if inmates sentenced for drugs, terrorism or spying offences would also benefit. [more]&lt;!-- E SF --&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;We hope that the action will benefit all prisoners on death row, without distinction,&amp;quot; an Amnesty statement said. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;We also urge President Musharraf to formally endorse the cabinet&amp;#39;s action, which will remove approximately one third of the global total of condemned prisoners in one go. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;It will be the largest mass commutation in modern times. We hope that this action by the Pakistan authorities will be a step towards a general moratorium on the death penalty with the ultimate aim of abolishing it.&amp;quot; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Indian &amp;#39;spy&amp;#39;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Correspondents say that while the commutations will only come into effect after final approval by President Musharraf, that process should be a formality. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
In 2002, the government headed by him granted a similar commutation to juvenile prisoners on death row. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The latest round of commutations was first announced by Prime Minister Yousuf Raza Gilani on 25 June, but the cabinet approved the proposal only on Wednesday. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Briefing the press after the cabinet meeting, Information Minister Sherry Rehman said the decision would benefit about 7,000 prisoners sentenced to die. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
It is not clear whether the cabinet decision will benefit Sarabjit Singh, an Indian man on death row in Pakistan for spying and carrying out bomb attacks. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
His case has commanded international attention, with India repeatedly calling for his life to be spared. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Earlier, an adviser to the prime minister on home affairs indicated the decision may exclude certain categories of prisoners, such as those sentenced in cases involving drugs and terrorism. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Ms Rehman was not available to clarify the cabinet&amp;#39;s position on the categories of prisoners who will remain on death row. &lt;!-- E BO --&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-07-03 08:28:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:35:59</lastModified>
  <raters>2</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Thousands-face-death-row-reprieve</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="d52207ee-587d-43ea-add4-7b5b20cfe57e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-27 03:00:30</date>
      <author>nike air max</author>
      <email>maidou20112011@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>cn</country>
      <ip>222.77.236.2</ip>
      <website>http://www.whiteairmax.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This will be a terrific web page, might you be interested in doing an interview regarding just how you created it? If so e-mail me! Yes, really. It was and with me. We can communicate on this theme. Quite right! Idea excellent, it agree with you.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>