<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Gospel of St. Woolmer</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img style="border-style: initial; border-color: initial; border-width: 0px;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2012%2f8%2fwoolmer.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;By: &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;In the beginning God created the ECB.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;As an afterthought and due to media pressure he created the BCCI and the PCB. To give a surprise to the angels who were bored to the point that they were talking to the bookies, he created Ijaz Butt. He ordered him to take abode in the Garden of Eden Housing Society (later merged into Defence Housing Authrority). He advised to him to watch the calories he ate and never to go near the forbidden tree of the Knowledge of the Good the Bad and the Ugly. From his rib he created the rib eye steak. He thrived in this garden and became the vicegerent of God on earth. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;There was a serpent in the grass of the Garden of Eden. He was called Mazhar Majeed and was an enemy of God, as he had a dual nationality which he refused to surrender till his gonads were crushed at the orders of the Supreme Court. He came to entice the vicegerent at the behest of the Great Satan, Rupert Murdoch who was in hoc to the biggest Satan of all, Sharad Pawar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;Together, these Satans decided to flout the supremacy of the Lord God and Lord Chief Justice and prayed on the innocent to fix the test at the Lords. So it came to pass that three pious young men, favoured of God, fell into their trap and thence to Wandsworth Prison.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;One of these martyrs was Mohammad Asif. had He been blessed by the Lord God to have the highest quality nandrolone delivered at his doorstep, till he committed&amp;nbsp; insolence towards God and Veena Malik and became a castaway, left wandering in the wilderness of forty years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;The Lord decided to wreak vengeance on the perfidious English for their misdeeds. This was visited upon them in the shape of Hashim Amla. This was the greatest massacre in the history of the island since the massacre of the Danelaw a thousand years ago. The Oval was strewn with the remains of the infidel who were destroyed by a most just extermination and the pious flag of SA waved and waved on the Tower of London.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;Meanwhile in Multan, the faithful had joined Inzamamul Haq for a chilla. This meant going to Glasgow and spreading the message of civilization in the godless Scottish glens, as the Celtic nation were completely bereft of the True Faith and of cricket; for it is written in the Holy Book of Wisden that man does not live by Single Malt alone but also by the beard that grows on the face of the Tablighi brother.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;Verily, Amla is the second holy warrior to emerge from the blessed Cape. The first one was Syed Bob Ali Woolmer of blessed memory, who fell to the infidel sword in the battle field of Jamaica. Surely, the boys were toast when the Lord God who was, by mere coincidence, working as the commissioner of the constabulary on that day, intervened personally and put them on the plane to New York.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;And so it is written that those who are the fovoured of God will avoid follow on and will sip warm beer in the pavilion, as the shadows lengthen on the cricket grounds. The word of God will spread from Raiwind to Trent Bridge, and the soul of St. Woolmer will smile in heaven as Inzamam ul Haq shaves his upper lip and Mushtaq Ahmed holds his Walima.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;Praise the Lord.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2012-08-22 02:24:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2012-08-22 02:27:34</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>The-Gospel-of-St-Woolmer</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="545edfc6-335d-47c1-8d0f-147c6d11032d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-08-31 08:42:26</date>
      <author>Imran</author>
      <email>Imran323@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>py</country>
      <ip>115.167.70.0</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:white list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content> Why dont you write on the most honest man on earth, Mr Armstrong, Why a simple soul like Hashim Amla? Are you suffering from inferiority complex?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6946e8db-47c6-4d21-ae74-2f1689b6e83a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-12-03 21:52:56</date>
      <author>Belal</author>
      <email>mdbelalp@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>180.149.14.35</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I read this blog. I also agreed  with Mr.Imran, they should discuss   the most honest man on earth Mr Armstrong,not like as Mr. Hashim Amla.&amp;lt;a  href=”http://www.earningbddhaka.wordpress.com”&amp;gt;Freelance tips&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e556a3ee-ee6e-492e-b1df-cff129d1d883" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-11-23 21:18:56</date>
      <author>health and dieting articles</author>
      <email>berryschindler@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.232.221.174</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>When you&amp;#39;ve got a handle on this data, you&amp;#39;re ready to start your program. Having eating healthily and doing the best exercises is of course essential. Everything sounds simple to date, but it is not because you need to the calories you might be consuming.

Also visit my site -  health and dieting articles - http://En.Wikipedia.org/wiki/Diet_(nutrition) </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="05121be8-a259-4af3-a875-c45aa885567b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2016-10-11 17:42:45</date>
      <author>เบอร์มงคล ผลรวม47</author>
      <email>aldakrieger@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.229.14.82</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! I&amp;#39;m at work browsing your blog from my new apple iphone! Just wanted to say I love reading your blog and look forward to all your posts! Keep up the fantastic work!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2b53aa81-12ed-4419-a117-3e43f5ea2ebf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2016-11-18 09:30:04</date>
      <author>เบอร์สวย ขายเอง</author>
      <email>indira_gaertner@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>209.222.100.46</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya! I realize this is sort of off-topic however I had to ask. Does running a well-established blog like yours take a lot of work? I am completely new to running a blog however I do write in my journal daily. I&amp;#39;d like to start a blog so I can easily share my personal experience and views online. Please let me know if you have any ideas or tips for brand new aspiring blog owners. Appreciate it!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f0c38db4-7820-4a14-8c77-889ad57603e3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2016-12-03 11:06:53</date>
      <author>เบอร์สวย 199 บาท</author>
      <email>edgardogreeves@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.108.2.103</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whoa! This blog looks exactly like my old one! It&amp;#39;s on a entirely different topic but it has pretty much the same layout and design. Excellent choice of colors!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="90a4edcf-4d2a-46c9-be43-3457fd876e5c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2016-12-11 13:38:07</date>
      <author>เรือ ไม้ ตก ปลา มือ สอง</author>
      <email>juanhuxley@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>209.222.100.20</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m amazed, I have to admit. Seldom do I come across a blog that&amp;#39;s both educative and interesting, and without a doubt, you have hit the nail on the head. The problem is something which not enough folks are speaking intelligently about. I am very happy I found this during my search for something regarding this.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7181d27a-9ef9-4657-a46f-7b3c8e0aeee8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-01-15 03:43:03</date>
      <author>honda pcx 2014 ทดสอบ</author>
      <email>katherinadenham@fastem.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.105.157.112</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Write more, thats all I have to say. Literally, it seems as though you relied on the video to make your point. You definitely know what youre talking about, why throw away your intelligence on just posting videos to your site when you could be giving us something informative to read?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e2b1351-097d-4607-90e9-052738222b23" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-01-15 09:00:29</date>
      <author>กระเป๋า แบรนด์ ก๊อ ป เกรด เอ</author>
      <email>jaxoncurran@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.119.14.52</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>WOW just what I was searching for. Came here by searching for กระเป๋าแบรนด์ไทย</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9223322d-540a-41e6-9d55-319db228ae2e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-01-21 18:00:27</date>
      <author>ทํานายเบอร์โทรศัพท์</author>
      <email>nancee.barlowe@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>162.212.172.85</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is not my first time to go to see this web site, i am visiting this web page dailly and take pleasant facts from here daily.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1f4f5a67-a633-43a2-a4cb-aa53befe2010" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-02-05 07:58:46</date>
      <author>เสาเข็มเจาะ รับน้ําหนัก</author>
      <email>ila.wray@care2.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.150.65.60</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Please let me know if you&amp;#39;re looking for a article author for your site. You have some really good articles and I think I would be a good asset. If you ever want to take some of the load off, I&amp;#39;d absolutely love to write some material for your blog in exchange for a link back to mine. Please send me an e-mail if interested. Thank you!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ebefd46-d503-4c71-af89-321d5f4d1008" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-04-04 02:34:32</date>
      <author>กําจัดปลวก ลําพูน</author>
      <email>travisstledger@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.150.90.214</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Right here is the right site for everyone who wants to find out about this topic. You realize so much its almost hard to argue with you (not that I actually would want to…HaHa). You certainly put a brand new spin on a topic which has been written about for a long time. Wonderful stuff, just excellent!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7d279776-5b28-4027-b268-f0c927d8056c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-05 05:04:35</date>
      <author>MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards 2017 live</author>
      <email>valorieglaze@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.232.20.41</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards 2017 Nominations See Complete List Of Nominees! The nominees with the 2017 MTV Motion picture &amp;amp; TV Awards have been announced Thursday. Look into the complete listing of nominees under! MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards Live, Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards Live, MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards 2017 Live, MTV Movie TV Awards, Red Carpet, Nominations, MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards 2017 Stream.   https://theoscarslivestream.org/ - https://theoscarslivestream.org/  https://freeoscarslivestream.us/ http://www.dmmp2p.eu/2017/05/04/mtv-movie-tv-awards-2017/  https://theoscarslivestream.org/2017/04/18/mtv-movie-tv-awards-2017/ - https://theoscarslivestream.org/2017/04/18/mtv-movie-tv-awards-2017/   MTV Movie &amp;amp; TV Awards 2017  This year’s installment from the yearly awards exhibit will now include things like Tv set sequence for The 1st time in its twenty five-12 months background. Many of the categories will even involve opponents from both of those mediums, together with Very best Comedic Performance, Finest Kiss and Most effective Villain, all of that happen to be open to performers from both equally film and television. The performing types may even be gender neutral for The 1st time ever, instead of splitting up accolades concerning actors and actresses.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="79af8e81-9deb-4509-8a68-46a603ac6674" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-29 22:13:03</date>
      <author>Learn colors for kids fingers</author>
      <email>shannonreimann@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>131.153.28.92</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>hey there and thank you for your information – I&amp;#39;ve definitely picked up anything new from right here. I did however expertise several technical issues using this website, as I experienced to reload the site a lot of times previous to I could get it to load properly. I had been wondering if your hosting is OK? Not that I am complaining, but sluggish loading instances times will sometimes affect your placement in google and can damage your high quality score if advertising and marketing with Adwords. Well I am adding this RSS to my e-mail and can look out for a lot more of your respective interesting content. Ensure that you update this again soon.  Stop by my weblog -  Learn colors for kids fingers - http://www.playincubate.com/members/efrenfairbanks/activity/4398461/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5c8526be-2fb9-4efa-aee2-f8b1fbe14b54" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-29 12:07:17</date>
      <author>buy lumigan eyelash</author>
      <email>judeengel@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.245.69.153</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wonderful goods from you, man. I&amp;#39;ve be aware your stuff previous to and you&amp;#39;re simply too great. I actually like what you&amp;#39;ve received here, really like what you&amp;#39;re saying and the way in which by which you say it. You are making it enjoyable and you still take care of to keep it smart. I can not wait to read much more from you. This is really a terrific website.  My weblog -  buy lumigan eyelash - https://sites.google.com/site/buylumiganonlineoverthecounter/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a5c04cfe-26ef-4ed0-ae0e-8c17860a2057" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-29 14:57:20</date>
      <author>buy lumigan drops</author>
      <email>danahotchin@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.88.25.134</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>An impressive share! I&amp;#39;ve just forwarded this onto a co-worker who had been doing a little homework on this. And he actually bought me breakfast due to the fact that I found it for him... lol. So let me reword this.... Thank YOU for the meal!! But yeah, thanks for spending some time to talk about this subject here on your web page.  My web page  buy lumigan drops - https://sites.google.com/site/buylumiganonlineoverthecounter/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>