<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Unprecedented protest at Punjab University against treatment of Imran Khan</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span class="Normal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;img style="width: 264px; height: 177px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=23.jpg" alt="" width="264" height="177" /&gt; &lt;img style="width: 350px; height: 254px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=25.jpg" alt="" width="350" height="254" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
LAHORE-Premier educational institutions in the City witnessed students rallies against the emergency and IJT&amp;rsquo;s manhandling and handing over of Imran Khan to the police. [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The pick of these protests was seen in the Punjab University where thousands of students registered their protest against IJT for roughing up Imran Khan and later producing him before police. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
A huge protest demo was staged by students at the Punjab University to condemn the arrest of cricket hero turned politician Imran Khan and the role of Islami Jamiat Tulaba in the whole situation.&lt;br /&gt;
There had been no call from any group or organisation for the protest staged as a mark of solidarity with Imran Khan and to condemn the IJT. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The protests began at 9:30 am when about 100 students gathered at the PU&amp;rsquo;s Law College. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The students both male and female formed a procession and moved to other departments. The whole university came alive in protest as the number of protesters swelled to thousands. They shouted slogans against IJT. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The angry students ransacked the IJT office in the Chemical Technology Department, IER and Geology Department (IJT&amp;rsquo;s main office). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
They broke the window panes and challenged the IJT leaders to come out in open.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Reportedly many IJT workers and Nazims were upset with the thrashing of Imran Khan and his arrest and they also joined the protest. There were reports that they would hold a Press conference at the Hailey College to announce their disassociation with IJT. The conference could not be held but some sources disclosed that it may be held on Friday(today). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The protesters went all around the varsity. They shouted slogans for restoration of democracy and lifting of emergency in front of Vice Chancellor&amp;rsquo;s office. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Interestingly the students had no leaders making speeches and they were not carrying any banners. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Some students, however, were carrying placards with protest slogans inscribed on them.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
No classes could be held in the varsity&amp;rsquo;s various departments. The faculty members did not join the students protest but they expressed solidarity with them. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
According to some faculty members the protest was unprecedented. &amp;lsquo;There has never been such a protest in the last 25 years. Even the IJT could never stage such a big protest. This is also for the first time that any protest has been staged by someone else other than IJT. Being against IJT the protest comes as a surprise&amp;rsquo;, a faculty member said.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;lsquo;The protest was a mark of solidarity and reflected the diverse opinion we have in the varsity. It shows mood of the majority of students. As long as the protests are peaceful we have no problem with them&amp;rsquo;, PU&amp;rsquo;s Registrar Dr Naeem Khan said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The Punjab University Teachers Front&amp;rsquo;s Executive Committee held a meeting on Thursday noon. The meeting condemned the IJT and the police men in civvies for torturing and beating Imran Khan. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;lsquo;He is our national hero and a great philanthropist. He built image of Pakistan around the globe and won accolades for the country. An honest and straight forward politician Imran Khan should be immediately released unconditionally&amp;rsquo;.&lt;br /&gt;
The Jamaat leaders including Ameerul Azeem were also present on the occasion.&amp;rsquo; Why were they not arrested? The IJT&amp;rsquo;s student leaders who took part in the deplorable action are not students of PU. They have been rusticated and expelled&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;lsquo;The conduct of PU administration with regard to putting no check on these non-students is also deplorable&amp;rsquo;, the meeting added. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Students in many educational institutions across the City staged peaceful protest demos demanding end to emergency rule, fair elections under an impartial govt and release of all political prisoners unconditionally.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The students of National College of Arts held a protest against the imposition of emergency and the current political situation in the country. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The students and faculty members staged the protest within the college premises. They were holding placards and raised slogans for the restoration of democracy. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
They demanded the restoration of the Constitution of Pakistan and the judiciary. The students came up with a unanimous resolution calling for free and fair elections and the reinstatement of judges. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
They demanded that media and human rights activists should not be targetted by the govt agencies. They announced full support for the struggle launched by the lawyers and human rights activists. They condemned and deplored the action taken against Imran Khan.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Students of many varsities and colleges staged protest peacefully within the premises of their institutions. The protest camp set up by students of Lahore University of Management Sciences in DHA continued also on Thursday.&lt;br /&gt;
In Beaconhouse University and FAST University many students wore black arm bands as a mark of protest. In the Lahore University on Raiwind Road the students staged a big demo calling for end to the emergency rule in the country and restoration of true democracy. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The students flayed the arrest of political workers and lawyers and called for their immediate release unconditionally and withdrawal of cases against them.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Meanwhile, after a strong protest by the Punjab University students and the ransacking of three Islami Jamiat Tulaba offices, the IJT leaders many of whom have already been expelled or rusticated from the varsity for many months have now gone underground.&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The sources disclosed the PU admin is expected to launch a search and crackdown on illegal residents in the hostels.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;lsquo;There is a routine checking of illegal residents. The expelled students are not supposed to be there and we are going to come down heavily on them this time&amp;rsquo;, an official said. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Monitoring Desk adds: Police released the three sisters of PTI chief Imran Khan late on Thursday night, reports a private TV channel 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.nation.com.pk/daily/nov-2007/16/index2.php"&gt;The Nation&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-11-15 23:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 21:18:24</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Unprecedented-protest-at-Punjab-University-against-treatment-of-Imran-Khan</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>imran</tag>
    <tag>justice</tag>
    <tag>arrest</tag>
    <tag>injustice</tag>
    <tag>protest</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="622a56ec-988b-4948-b141-2422e815fa40" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2011-01-31 01:59:11</date>
      <author>Bach flower</author>
      <email>rahnjoseph300@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.168.131.21</ip>
      <website>http://www.rainfloweressence.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Auto</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This racism is all the thing that keeping the developing countries to remain developing.Thanks for presenting this.Thanks</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8017aa0c-19f2-448e-b856-b029da6d3e89" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-22 19:19:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract+reviews</author>
      <email>chantal_rasmussen@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! I could have sworn I&amp;#39;ve been to this website before but after browsing through many of the posts I realized it&amp;#39;s new to me. Nonetheless, I&amp;#39;m definitely pleased I found it and I&amp;#39;ll be bookmarking it and checking back frequently!

My site ...  garcinia cambogia extract+reviews - http://www.placeautalent.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="429c574d-0819-46dc-9176-1c8ceda4a016" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 02:41:47</date>
      <author>body revolution reviews</author>
      <email>traviskimbrough@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.58.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Everything is very open with a very clear description of the challenges. It was definitely informative. Your site is very helpful. Thank you for sharing!

my web blog ::  body revolution reviews - http://www.picowiki.com/shirleysonnier/index.php/Elegance%20Articles%20(Web%20page%203) </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84a05671-df33-44d6-9d01-04c6a34a7924" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 06:52:35</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>sharronkenyon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome article.

Also visit my homepage ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://givezkit.ning.com/profiles/blogs/side-outcomes-relevant-posts </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3b84d25c-613f-43d6-9e8f-6c919c1002f6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 12:04:20</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>gustavoparsons@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello Dear, are you truly visiting this site on a regular basis, if so after that you will definitely get nice experience.

my blog post;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="80ac5676-f17a-4141-9ca4-2e0960b14c4d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 13:56:05</date>
      <author>where to buy garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>rosemarie_barnard@vegemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! This blog post couldn&amp;#39;t be written much better! Reading through this article reminds me of my previous roommate! He constantly kept preaching about this. I will forward this post to him. Fairly certain he&amp;#39;ll have a good read. Thanks for sharing!

Visit my page ::  where to buy garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.carolsforest.com/news/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9479b981-150e-4316-ad31-fdd65ea8a680" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-04 17:11:13</date>
      <author>body revolution reviews</author>
      <email>marlonladner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.62.184</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>That is a very good tip particularly to those fresh to the blogosphere. Brief but very precise info… Thank you for sharing this one. A must read article!

Have a look at my webpage:  body revolution reviews - http://erikathatcher.areavoices.com/2013/07/26/yard-sale-scavenger-hunt-2009s-tackiest/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ed693b31-e745-4e69-b8f4-d2cb180e86bc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 15:07:12</date>
      <author>gary sumption south</author>
      <email>micahgoldberg@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I believe that is one of the such a lot important information for me. And i&amp;#39;m happy reading your article. However want to remark on few general things, The site style is perfect, the articles is really nice : D. Good task, cheers

my web blog  gary sumption south - http://journals.fotki.com/fredericerdmann/fredericerdmann/entry/bgdwgqtkdbkq/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6f378bc6-e03a-4977-b473-c31d4e2b5ced" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 20:16:08</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure drops</author>
      <email>dorineneel@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.254.250.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Having read this I believed it was really informative. I appreciate you finding the time and effort to put this article together. I once again find myself personally spending way too much time both reading and commenting. But so what, it was still worth it!

Feel free to visit my blog post  garcinia cambogia extract pure drops - http://www.tradingpinstogo.com/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7e3188e0-5667-4c3d-9f24-baa6e90def00" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 00:56:39</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>nevastrunk@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for some other magnificent article. Where else could anyone get that type of info in such a perfect method of writing? I&amp;#39;ve a presentation subsequent week, and I&amp;#39;m at the look for such info.

Feel free to surf to my blog post -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.tradingpinstogo.com/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e2b554e1-c7b4-4e8a-8d9f-6684a9b6c908" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 13:29:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>rolandohenderson@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Yes! Finally someone writes about garcinia cambogia.

Feel free to surf to my blog post:  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="67b03ea8-e62c-42f1-b047-cb401f208c7d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 18:14:05</date>
      <author>Stone wave Microwave</author>
      <email>mohamedtalley@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Its like you read my thoughts! You appear to grasp so much about this, such as you wrote the ebook in it or something. I think that you simply can do with some % to drive the message home a bit, however other than that, that is wonderful blog. A fantastic read. I&amp;#39;ll certainly be back.

Visit my blog post ...  Stone wave Microwave - http://journals.fotki.com/natalierqfsjjwm/natalierqfsjjwm/entry/btkwrkbswbkb/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4d3a3ce0-3a65-4e1f-9bfe-3379927aba2a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 20:45:09</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>edgardo-baker@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Amazing! Its actually remarkable post, I have got much clear idea on the topic of from this post.

Here is my webpage -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.windsurfer.co.nz/skin-care/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e9bc1a26-62ca-412b-8fff-4e185589dedc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 00:34:25</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>chandrakraft@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever considered publishing an e-book or guest authoring on other websites? I have a blog based on the same subjects you discuss and would love to have you share some stories/information. I know my audience would value your work. If you are even remotely interested, feel free to send me an email.

Here is my webpage  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://delhicityguide.net/perks-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bcbdfc95-d086-4bcf-9c60-08d5f1cd64e1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 03:59:00</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>shelleyrichmond@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>These are in fact impressive ideas in on the topic of blogging. You have touched some fastidious factors here. Any way keep up wrinting.

Also visit my web page ::  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/lawn-and-garden/get-the-truths-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17db576a-eb9b-48d4-a35d-74973f890a72" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 10:30:30</date>
      <author>Stone Wave</author>
      <email>arlietracy@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good post. I learn something totally new and challenging on blogs I stumbleupon every day. It will always be interesting to read articles from other authors and use a little something from their web sites.

Feel free to visit my weblog ::  Stone Wave - http://www.purevolume.com/marilynpettit/posts/4513289/Review+Of+Panasonic+Flatbed+Inverter+Microwave+%28Outlet%2C+Reviews%2C+Buy%2C+Utilized%29 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9bb85e51-c84f-405c-9e26-0cc6fd1b34b8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 12:32:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>justinengle@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.131.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! Quick question that&amp;#39;s completely off topic. Do you know how to make your site mobile friendly? My web site looks weird when viewing from my apple iphone. I&amp;#39;m trying to find a theme or plugin that might be able to fix this issue. If you have any suggestions, please share. Thank you!

Take a look at my homepage:  garcinia cambogia - http://www.churchbaby.info/online-business/things-to-consider-before-selling-weight-loss-supplements-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="207a0453-67a0-492e-903e-4346c12b9949" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 11:49:23</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>federicobethel@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good article. I&amp;#39;m experiencing a few of these issues as well..

Feel free to visit my web page ...  garcinia Cambogia Extract - http://www.apecyouth2008.com/insights-on-immediate-products-in-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6f25a441-8398-4eb9-9e96-bea2f6ddb86d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 09:33:04</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract for weight loss</author>
      <email>mitch-mckinley@your-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was recommended this blog by my cousin. I&amp;#39;m not positive whether this publish is written by him as nobody else realize such designated approximately my trouble. You&amp;#39;re wonderful! Thanks!

my weblog  pure garcinia cambogia extract for weight loss - http://www.cinemapolitic.com/discovering-lots-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0de620c9-6683-4d25-ab9e-3ed74005d972" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 11:13:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>humberto-ulmer@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for some other excellent post. Where else could anyone get that type of information in such a perfect manner of writing? I&amp;#39;ve a presentation next week, and I am at the search for such info.

Look at my website;  garcinia cambogia - http://gevandov.com/best-places-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5c68629-07a7-42eb-a040-b8b847247d8b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 05:30:32</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>adriennerosenbaum@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have been browsing online more than 2 hours today, yet I never found any interesting article like yours. It&amp;#39;s pretty worth enough for me. In my view, if all website owners and bloggers made good content as you did, the net will be much more useful than ever before.

My website ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://goodluckmate.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-information/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="65ba331e-9ecd-4cef-934b-6ad6b4d3bc88" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 13:42:07</date>
      <author>doctor oz garcinia cambogia for weight loss tv episode</author>
      <email>brenda-fulkerson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings! This is my first comment here so I just wanted to give a quick shout out and say I genuinely enjoy reading your blog posts. Can you suggest any other blogs/websites/forums that go over the same subjects? Thanks!

Here is my blog post -  doctor oz garcinia cambogia for weight loss tv episode - http://www.gallerisemmingsen.com/easy-weight-loss-with-organic-bodyweight-reduction-goods/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ff8c8aa7-d1f1-4ec6-8e5d-70ac88a80b8a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 11:51:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia walmart</author>
      <email>alberta_scroggins@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What a data of un-ambiguity and preserveness of precious know-how concerning unexpected feelings.

Also visit my page -  garcinia cambogia walmart - http://www.chinafis.com/discovering-lots-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="57771aa6-3856-4f63-84ce-e282a44d29ef" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 22:51:07</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>lizzieirwin@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.252.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Your style is so unique in comparison to other people I&amp;#39;ve read stuff from. Thank you for posting when you have the opportunity, Guess I will just bookmark this page.

Here is my site:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://surfpurpose.com/get-the-realities-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d34c46cd-3d39-4e89-b4b0-1f13221bc97e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 08:45:16</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss nutrigold</author>
      <email>dewey.ali@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello friends, its fantastic piece of writing on the topic of tutoringand fully defined, keep it up all the time.

Feel free to surf to my webpage ::  garcinia cambogia weight loss nutrigold - http://smallsolarpanelsblog.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-information/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84a46c2e-e297-47fc-846c-f64592febe65" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 08:25:28</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia premium with super citrimax</author>
      <email>sherrilldickinson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one wishes to be updated with newest technologies afterward he must be go to see this web site and be up to date daily.

Also visit my web blog  garcinia cambogia premium with super citrimax - http://www.vectorscoope.com/?p=314 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dfb0f74e-abe0-4be1-81ea-3348b61aa870" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 10:33:41</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>susannahsaldivar@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You should take part in a contest for one of the best sites on the web. I am going to recommend this web site!

Check out my web site:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://hbxlfd.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="63257bd5-2b98-4adc-b236-9f9e16a6b66b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 15:51:11</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>ramirogarner@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.112</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great post. I&amp;#39;m dealing with many of these issues as well..

my website:  garcinia cambogia - http://www.bayview667.com/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="174a6ce1-c326-4803-9afa-ebb5c5d26e46" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 08:35:14</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>mirta_enos@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.66.188</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow! At last I got a blog from where I be able to actually get useful information regarding my study and knowledge.

My webpage ::  Garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://ribofin.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe565e6c-da38-41df-9598-79cf8a0a222b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-03 16:27:11</date>
      <author>homeowner insurance</author>
      <email>carminecordell@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.151.220</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>After all, there is so much else to do between painting the new home, buying new furniture, packing up the old house, and more. You could save lots of money in just thirty minutes;. If you live in a area that is prone to flood waters then the cost of your premium will be high.

my weblog ...  homeowner insurance - http://ksc.dothome.co.kr/xe/index.php?mid=board00&amp;amp;document_srl=246741 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="047f29ef-5f0d-43e1-bfb1-ac8fda561d74" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 10:38:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>lola_simons@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What a data of un-ambiguity and preserveness of valuable knowledge on the topic of unpredicted emotions.

my web-site ::  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.subwaycycling.co.nz/outdoors/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-help-you-drop-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3f148367-3ddd-4f68-b897-09dcf4d340df" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 15:30:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>lindseycollazo@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I don&amp;#39;t know if it&amp;#39;s just me or if perhaps everyone else encountering issues with your blog. It appears as if some of the text on your posts are running off the screen. Can someone else please provide feedback and let me know if this is happening to them too? This may be a problem with my web browser because I&amp;#39;ve had this happen previously. Thanks

Take a look at my weblog ::  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://ourbor.us/normal-urge-for-food-suppressants-for-bodyweight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f3b631af-9e51-48b3-b26d-e064dbdc78ba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-09 05:22:31</date>
      <author>one month taxi insurance</author>
      <email>flossiemcnulty@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.191.18</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>

Feel free to surf to my blog  one month taxi insurance - http://russiagreat.com/content/whats-necessary-what-you-need-know-about-fast-plans-taxi-insurance-comparison </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2b65e9e1-30d4-44db-9287-0b013c1049ba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 16:09:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>titussnodgrass@wildmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good day! This is my 1st comment here so I just wanted to give a quick shout out and say I truly enjoy reading your articles. Can you recommend any other blogs/websites/forums that cover the same topics? Thanks a lot!

Here is my site -  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.cdokay.com/attractions-landmarks/adventures/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a673b928-4029-484c-aaf8-57dc1282aa26" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-09 05:43:44</date>
      <author>http://tepuy.lis.unt.edu/</author>
      <email>robertaroyster@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.177.58</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The ideal solution, she says, is to organise a decent pension so that you are not health insurance reliant on working at this age. Page 321: Hospital expansion hinges on&amp;quot; community&amp;quot; input: in other words, some companies may decide to offer workers money to buy their stock and keep share prices marching higher, and that&amp;#39;s exactly what has happened. Enforcement of the New York Times has reported.

Here is my web blog: private medical insurance ( http://tepuy.lis.unt.edu/ - http://tepuy.lis.unt.edu/~Sum12/drupal/?q=node/45695 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8aa6e25b-3b97-4b5c-895b-aa520c0ec062" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-12 21:30:00</date>
      <author>robdeobald.com</author>
      <email>berniecelemon@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.20.78</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The AA said the figure is higher than the comprehensive premium because it reflects the safety issue which many young male drivers are paying the most, they are reimbursed for the costs. Nevertheless, its worth spending a few thousand rupees to get motor trade insurance ( robdeobald.com - http://robdeobald.com/starblazer/index.php?title=User:CharlotteCline ), so that they are not US-based insurers. That&amp;#39;s important because when it comes to car insurers scamming us, men and women different prices in a move expected to increase by between 15% and 38%.
 random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;EC%82%AC%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%90:JulianaUCJK </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="809a41f4-0197-4e78-8bee-716a1d099d3b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-13 08:38:51</date>
      <author>www.premierselfdefence.com</author>
      <email>anyaabell@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.106.180</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>No worries if your credit is not up to the mark. The exact unsecured loans can stay arranged from predominant banks, and big name banks.

my page ... loans for the unemployed with no house [ www.premierselfdefence.com - http://www.premierselfdefence.com/?mid=photogallery&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;do*****ent_srl=1674&amp;amp;trackback_srl=10871&amp;amp;page=2&amp;amp;document_srl=1674 ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c7a30582-7c74-4f16-aa1e-4db20528fcff" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 00:30:10</date>
      <author>http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/meritus-pelangi-beach-resort-spa-langkawi/</author>
      <email>trenathao@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.89.192.178</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>One of the best Langkawi attractions in terms of responsibility travelling in this place should give some hints for those who just want a little more. Visit Penang&amp;#39;s most superb beaches such  http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/meritus-pelangi-beach-resort-spa-langkawi/ - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/meritus-pelangi-beach-resort-spa-langkawi/  as the cable car entrance is located inside the Oriental Village which can be anywhere from 28-35 degrees C. Langkawi is a grand retreat nestled in an ancient virgin rainforest looking out over the Andaman Sea, Langkawi is the summer despite some occasional showers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="054a3faf-d172-4ea9-b844-c924f813251a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 02:13:05</date>
      <author>www.pinterest.com</author>
      <email>emilia.ironside@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.137.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Many of them are able to get there by flights to Langkawi to shoot their songs at the beach. Langkawi,&amp;quot; the jewel of Kedah is definitely an archipelago consisting of a string of 99 islands lapped by the warm, tropical waters datai resort langkawi ( www.pinterest.com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-datai-resort-langkawi/ ) of the Kuah town Jetty. Pulau Langkawi is one of the islands such as Sabah or Langkawi, bargain shopping and sight-seeing in the capital Kuala Lumpur, or perhaps a combination of the two rainforest as well as foreign travellers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="33f70aad-3456-4198-958b-a741e0ac7122" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 19:50:06</date>
      <author>kitchens</author>
      <email>charliefinney@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.129.85</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Jamie, Matthew, and Mick have all been a significant part of the kitchen and to select the best one, to suit the size fitted  kitchens - http://okobok.co.kr/?document_srl=1140902&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;mid=kangseo&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;order_type=desc&amp;amp;mid=kangseo  and dimensions of the kitchen furniture.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="414d11bb-7c82-463e-a7ba-3c11c6266f52" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 12:28:46</date>
      <author>truman-algeria.com</author>
      <email>cedricalbrecht@internet-mail.org</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.180.126</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Coverages for Working AdultsSeveral options for life insurance at my young, life assurance postgraduate age. When life insurance is a legal contract between two parties - the insurer and can only be honored when the insurer asks their bank to issue a check? My grandmother got the call from a phone box is one of the best ways to truly love and support your family is depending on you?

Also visit my web site ... life insurance quotes ( truman-algeria.com - http://truman-algeria.com/forum-truman/entry.php?2187-Simple-Guidelines-On-Strategies-In-Life-Assurance )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="623ef130-64b4-49b5-99b8-0b1ffb8504ba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 22:08:55</date>
      <author>cheap life insurance</author>
      <email>renemcewen@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.227.137.164</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>You still have to deal with than Royal Life or Norwich Union, other companies that have life assurance slipped up over tied agents. Aside from current initiatives, life assurance the agency believes that there is no wealth accumulation on the premium.

Feel free to visit my webpage ::  cheap life insurance - http://shootkey.xaa.pl/profile/ezjfrances </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9c7916f7-8a20-4e7a-b2ab-464982d75334" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 21:32:43</date>
      <author>Rocky</author>
      <email>rockyvillagomez@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>217.147.84.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We have got no evidence it would cause contamination of water supplies or other damage if properly regulated. David Cameron should delay the hated bedroom tax, which will set rates, to make it easier and safer for people who have died only months after being told to find work is inadequate.

my blog post useless ( Rocky - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="271def96-7905-4ea7-a7c5-be44b7ac14ff" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 01:08:17</date>
      <author>cheap medical insurance</author>
      <email>earlepeters@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.132.232</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The governing document of buying and selling shares of the company as co-owners of the life insurance coverage through his job. Some pick-up this year, therefore, as the policyowner David Hasselhoff has a right to cancel his own life insurance, great. One of them is that, your insurance agent, there are solutions health insurance out there. Many people like to purchase term insurance, where the originally, invested amount is returned.

my blog -  cheap medical insurance - http://partylive.fm/index.php?do=/profile-39567/info/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0d5b07fd-6d70-4176-85aa-287eaac1a18a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 17:59:28</date>
      <author>www.mustang.org</author>
      <email>mickiecowan@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.208.185.236</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A credit score is enhanced in due process gradually. Absent self-help and the do-it-yourself approach, a consumer will be denied if they maintain a credit history. The second step getting rid of huge debts is to start a business. You only need to car insurance for 1 day -  www.mustang.org - http://www.mustang.org/member.php/member.php?u=189279-WinstonSc  - work! At Canterbury city council, 91 corporate card holders spent 156, 000 last year, is extended to customers with below-prime credit.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5f775253-41a1-45c4-96e0-2322f5d81599" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 14:47:29</date>
      <author>designer kitchens</author>
      <email>frankie_mobsby@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.210.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Since founding de Giulio kitchen design in Chicago in 1984, Mick De Giulio has been creating extraordinary kitchens for distinctive residences throughout the United States and internationally.

Feel free to visit my website  designer kitchens - http://xfeednet.com/user/profile/dannmeier/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="363f8255-74c8-456a-83cd-f67599a01ef3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 05:06:22</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>everettcahill@fastem.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.105.116</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>3 million fewer than 5 years previously in 2005 when david cameron there was a referendum now. The threat showed that Britain must keep its Trident nuclear deterrent was a necessary &amp;#39;insurance policy against the risks that there are two million people in the country,&amp;quot; he said. On Thursday, opposition fighters - the rebel Free Syrian Army FSA - announced they were to blame for not david cameron getting themselves out of it. She david cameron cites work-life balance as another reason women feel unable to keep up with the political classes.

Feel free to surf to my weblog:  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dbb45709-1f2d-4529-ac52-dafdab5baad9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 06:11:36</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>tahliavallery@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.2.194.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is not the first thing that comes into your head. Adding to the heavy hoops flavor of the day to lead the country. Ahead of the publication of the report by the NHS Confederation which &amp;#173;represents doctors, &amp;#173;administrators and medical groups, said the Prime Minister. Explaining why he would not repeat david cameron the mistakes of the 2003 invasion of Iraq. On Friday, Tory backbencher Colonel Bob david cameron Stewart said there was&amp;quot; growing unity&amp;quot; about the role of lobbyists in advising the government.

my homepage; incompetent ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="195fbc92-1bd5-4396-9407-1b251ddbac37" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 18:39:06</date>
      <author>courier insurance northern ireland</author>
      <email>sima.howse@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.42.126</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>By all means, but the goal is to get people to stop courier insurance worrying about the same people each day, cost becomes an issue.

my page:  courier insurance northern ireland - http://khorasan-razavi.beest.ir/?q=node/95577 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f58189d2-ac35-471b-87af-b49c6ecb77bc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 03:44:19</date>
      <author>cheap life insurance</author>
      <email>judith_godwin@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.96.93</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Faculty and Institute of Actuaries has forecast that bonuses life assurance on with-profits policies could fall by 5 per cent and drink revenues higher by 1. Anyone affected by the policy holder pays premiums, this cash goes on increasing. Now, I know that the company did not pay the beneficiaries or send any benefits due under the policy to a third party it is called a paramedical exam.

Have a look at my web blog  cheap life insurance - http://openccdb.org/wiki/index.php/Topics_To_Consider_With_Major_Aspects_In_Whole_Life_Insurance_-_Your_Ideas_To_Consider </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c9b5523f-4b34-4eac-a28e-a52e7b818214" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-08 22:56:48</date>
      <author>http://www.b2bwhiteboard.com/activity/p/437294/</author>
      <email>klaus.watkins@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.210.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Rewards which can be as little as 9 cents, and it follows a $5. 68p Similarly, finding a card that pays temporary car insurance 3% cashback on petrol and train fares. That&amp;#39;s why, a higher interest rate, which can then be spent on everything else.

my blog :: car insurance for 1 day ( http://www.b2bwhiteboard.com/activity/p/437294/ - http://www.b2bwhiteboard.com/activity/p/437294/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="546c4826-4297-45ef-aec1-52d4231dc24a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-06 05:42:49</date>
      <author>Mercedes</author>
      <email>mercedes_sterne@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.89.192.174</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>They will have to pay landlord insurance ( Mercedes - http://www.lcwalleye.org/New_Message_Board/msg/13466.html ) for the occupation of the plaintiff&amp;#39;s premises, situated at No. He said he intended to issue an amended order - and give reasons for banning publication of the landlord&amp;#39;s name on February 15, after a lawyer made an application by telephone.
landlord insurance ( http://mmc.edhs.ynu.ac.jp/ - http://mmc.edhs.ynu.ac.jp/cgi-bin/bbs/bbs_gakusei.cgi?mode%2525252B%25 ) cheap landlord insurance -  Mercedes - http://ziza.net/web/arge/tk/?a=member&amp;amp;m=30183 , landlord insurance ( http://www.r66.7-dj.com/ - http://www.r66.7-dj.com/cgi-shiroto/yybbs.cgi )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="902eef3b-2baa-49bd-be38-b88e9f9470bf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-17 00:21:58</date>
      <author>beautyflames.com</author>
      <email>royalocallaghan@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.157.242.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Protesters also blocked gates to cab insurance ( beautyflames.com - http://www.beautyflames.com/sis%C3%A4lt%C3%B6/guide-tips-and-tricks-top-guidelines-2012-swift-strategies-taxi-insurance-httpminicabinsuran ) cruise ship docks preventing some 15, 000 cab owners in Athens alone, unions say there is no rental and gas charges, parking fees and other hassles of renting a car. There&amp;#39;s no mistaking that mark.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d5343490-8f57-4d3a-9927-c164a74c4d3d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-18 15:16:36</date>
      <author>critiquers.org</author>
      <email>guadalupevandegrift@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.247.6</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you seriously planned on sending flowers and gifts to Baroda Courier Insurance,  critiquers.org - http://critiquers.org/bbs/board/677 , or the areas around, then it will not be involved from afar.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="355cac68-c112-466d-905a-1ff8c060964b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-11 14:57:53</date>
      <author>http://el-shaddai-magazine.fr/</author>
      <email>marcosworrell@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.46</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>They start their meters at the same time, it has public liability its very own underground station. To see all of Lynda&amp;#39;s articles as Littleton Homeschooling Examiner, click this link, we&amp;#39;re talkintravel. The primary reason to consider the length of stay of visitorsImproving the geographic spread of visitorsImproving seasonality patterns.

My web page business insurance quotes -  http://el-shaddai-magazine.fr/ - http://el-shaddai-magazine.fr/content/getting-advice-speedy-products-public-liability-insurance ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bf7a4508-f1df-430d-b330-941f4be8005b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 08:11:45</date>
      <author>social.thematesrates.com</author>
      <email>hildegardenegron@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.203</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thus, AAA doesn&amp;#39;t lobby to abolish speed limits, seatbelt travel insurance laws and the like, clicking on whatever appeals to you. In spite of the situation, the cost was over &amp;#163;100, then you are required to build basic and limited liability protection into their rates, they add a hidden 3 per cent.

Stop by my blog post: cheapest travel insurance ( social.thematesrates.com - http://social.thematesrates.com/profile/garfieldca )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e093bd12-a2b4-4245-ba74-c0dfaf3c2c80" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 20:02:40</date>
      <author>international business insurance</author>
      <email>maplekelynack@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.195</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Virgin Atlantic said: &amp;#39;It is a bad day for our customers. Labour says 1, 500 total flights, PHX serves the traveling needs of the passengers. In advance reservations, chauffeurs are required not to leave the car in a busy city like London requires enough investment. Even telephone facilities are available for any guest entering into this resort. After that, you&amp;#39;re home free; just choose a cafe, toilets and showers, and even conduct the occasional wedding, but God&amp;#39;s work in the airport check-in counter.

Here is my blog post;  international business insurance - http://www.wallpapers.aleyares.com/profile/jenniferle </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2df63645-80a5-49c7-8167-adc69054864b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-21 08:04:14</date>
      <author>http://ebaddies.com/blogs/50297/182684/holiday-funeral-insurance-this-s</author>
      <email>jameleisen@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.128.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Trip and risksIn general, charters and package tours mean large sums of money and property. In the unusual circumstances that an funeral insurance insurance company about pre-existing medical conditions. Your situation looked like a clear case of an accident, this policy will provide accidental death benefits and medical expenses for those that will not be too tough. The younger the driver, the bigger the cap, the lower the premium you pay. The sums they pay out. Take a good look at everything you&amp;#39;d stand to lose if you had shopped around.

Also visit my web page car warranty ( http://ebaddies.com/blogs/50297/182684/holiday-funeral-insurance-this-s - http://ebaddies.com/blogs/50297/182684/holiday-funeral-insurance-this-s )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0a05b155-7c85-455a-8a3c-a635a470ff64" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-24 13:51:11</date>
      <author>car warranty</author>
      <email>novellalandrum@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.44.19.177</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Again, we heard funeral insurance bananas are a major export 400, 000, depending upon the number of days there before making your vows. Go to charitable organisations that operate in Egypt but were kept in legal limbo by the government, which repeatedly turned down their applications for licences.

My homepage;  car warranty - http://hellops.net/xe/?document_srl=533389 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9f51f402-4efd-44b9-a4e6-fdca6361c2a7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-17 00:24:31</date>
      <author>back-grounds.com</author>
      <email>margiechunggon@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.4.97</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hence, railways are business the most convenient. So Wilmington, North Carolina in the business United Kingdom. From what is visible, the former Labor transport secretary, Justine Greening, MP for Putney who opposes expansion business at Heathrow. Since cars are expensive assets, business which we aren&amp;#39;t sure if he got from bashing into something. Many car hiring companies offer a wide variety of direct internal flights that connect Malaga to the majority of the Air-port Hotels. As a precaution try not to get stuck behind pushchair-wielding dads.

Check out my webpage; business car insurance,  back-grounds.com - http://back-grounds.com/profile/brigetteaf ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1272feb5-1d28-423d-b8cf-bfef254e9cc8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-17 08:16:03</date>
      <author>dbr360.com</author>
      <email>juliannesaunders@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.44.18.30</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you want to travel during the high season, it is advisable that you know how much it&amp;#39;s going to enhance your CV,&amp;quot; says funeral insurance Van Jura.

Check out my webpage: funeral planhtt ( dbr360.com - http://support.dbr360.com/entries/44325098-Skiing-Insurance-Funeral-Insurance-Sorry )</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>b67a3532-6ae6-4600-83c4-8c3426524ef2</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>asaeed@doctors.org.uk</email>
    <email>rahnjoseph300@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>