<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Benazir Lives</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 206px; height: 240px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=benazir_lives_1.jpg" alt="" width="206" height="240" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif'"&gt;by Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: 'Arial','sans-serif'"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Benazir will live for ever in the hearts of millions of Pakistanis. Like her father, she had two outstanding attributes, unmatched by any Pakistani politician: Universal appeal and personal courage. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Zulfiqar Ali Bhutto was able to reach out to all sections of (West) Pakistani society. His appeal transcended class, provincial, linguistic, ethnic and religious divisions. He was able to inspire international leaders, and rural peasants, with equal ease. The lasting devotion that he earned, however, was from the Pakistani working class. He was the first national politician to give them hope, inspiration and realisation that that things could improve. Although People&amp;rsquo;s Party abandoned it&amp;rsquo;s socialist agenda, fairly early on, the Pakistani working class has never given up it&amp;rsquo;s allegiance to the Bhutto name, and it&amp;rsquo;s loyalty to his party. [more]&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Benazir&amp;rsquo;s greatest asset was the Bhutto name. She had her father&amp;rsquo;s universal appeal. She was charismatic, a great communicator, and able to reach out to all sections of Pakistani society. She had also inherited her father&amp;rsquo;s personal courage. Her father refused to appeal for mercy to the military dictator, who eventually hanged him. Benazir went to address political meetings in all parts of Pakistan, inspite of repeated attempts on her life. She has paid the ultimate price for this courage.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Benazir&amp;rsquo;s worst liabilities were her corruption cases and her husband, Asif Zardari. 2007 was the worst year of her politics. Her mistakes were throwing a lifeline to Musharraf, when he was all but finished after the debacle of the CJ movement, and associating too closely and openly with the Americans.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Because of the blind American support for Israel, invasion and destruction of Iraq, and invasion of Afghanistan, there is widespread anti American sentiment in large sections of Pakistani society. (Although there is commonality of interests as well). It was madness for Benazir to issue pro-American statements on extremism in Pakistan, AQ Khan, and invasion of Pakistani territory by the Americans, while sitting in New York and at a time when the Lal Masjid operation was at its height. It also shows the intellectual bankruptcy of the Bush administration, to openly support Musharraf and Benazir deal. Since 9&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of March, 2007, Musharraf is undoubtedly the most hated figure in Pakistan. The only conclusion to be drawn form Benazir&amp;rsquo;s inexplicable behaviour was that she was counting on the Americans to bear down on Musharraf to drop her corruption cases. This conclusion was drawn by the Punjabi urban middle class and the PPP support was wiped out at least in this social class. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Benazir&amp;rsquo;s brutal murder has changed everything yet again. This is the 9/11 of Pakistani politics. There is surge of PPP vote in the urban middle classes. The wavering PPP voter is likely to come back. Whereas before 27&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of December, Nawaz Sharif would have won a free and fair election, now it is likely to be the PPP. It will be much more difficult now for the ISI to rig the polls, as the public anger will spill over and lead to widespread agitation. In either case Musharraf&amp;rsquo;s days are numbered. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The PPP has handled the succession issue quite well. The Bhutto devotees have got a symbolic leader in Bilawal. Zardari must keep a relatively low profile, as he is widely seen as corrupt and venal. On the other hand, his statements in response to Nawaz Sharif&amp;rsquo;s overtures have increased is stature. The PPP is in a much better bargaining position, after 27&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of December. They can refuse to put up with a rigged election. They can demand that the current election commissioner be sent home, and a neutral commissioner appointed. They can insist on a neutral caretaker Government. They can put the restoration of the sacked judges firmly back on the agenda. They can refuse to put up with any delay in the election. They can make a united stand with Nawaz Sharif, even an electoral alliance, so that when they form the government, they can easily repeal the 58-2b, and the 17&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; amendment, and have real political power, rather than be the President&amp;rsquo;s stooges. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;They have done well to turn the public outrage against Musharraf and his league of quislings. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Musharraf is in a no win situation, if he holds a free and fair election, the resulting setup will throw him out sooner or later. If he tries to rig the election, as planned, there will be widespread turmoil, which he won&amp;rsquo;t be able to control. The army will not come to his rescue, as he will be seen as an increasing liability for their corporate interests. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;It is also time for the Americans to drop Musharraf. He is damaged goods, and is doing incalculable harm to the American interests in the region, in his personal struggle for survival. They best course of action for the Americans is to stay out and wait for the new political dispensation to emerge. They can help, not least their own interests, if they clearly and openly support the democratic process and not a travesty, that is a fig leaf for Musharraf&amp;rsquo;s incompetent and brutal dictatorship. The Pakistani mainstream voter is liberal and secular. They should not be afraid of an open election. In the words of Hina Jilani, we say &amp;lsquo;no to the militants, no to the military&amp;rsquo;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img style="width: 206px; height: 240px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=bl2.jpg" alt="" width="206" height="240" /&gt; 
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-01-01 14:08:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 14:00:54</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>4.25</rating>
  <slug>Benazir-Lives</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>bb</tag>
    <tag>benazir</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="08a823b1-8bf0-43ad-a858-2a0b67c54736" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-02 04:24:05</date>
      <author>mst. nasrin sultana</author>
      <email>nasrinsultana44@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>180.234.43.75</ip>
      <website>http://www.mailware.com/mailware/integration/cart-comparison/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mailware is a multi channel directorrrrrrr and a full up up up up up up up back taskequequequequeque &amp;amp; shopping cart software tohan lectureureureureureureure to your tangleglegleglegleglegle deposititititititit. With Mailware and shopping cart , you can superviseiseiseiseiseiseise your guidelinesinesinesinesinesinesines from all your online foodeee accountle warehouses, relate up up up up up up up customer folderportsportsportsportsportsport to your customers, and superviseiseiseiseiseiseise your accounting. I engage inge inge inge inge inge inge in used it. It is very comfortable and very simplelelelelelele.
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a872d735-e5a7-458d-9165-6a2e6c33ccc7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-17 01:50:56</date>
      <author>SEO</author>
      <email>seocompanysydney.com@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.161.72.231</ip>
      <website>http://www.seocompanysydney.com.au/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Many thanks for your interesting articles.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5a5d83b-2a54-44cc-af16-c2f2ea004ba7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-17 01:52:10</date>
      <author>Horse Racing</author>
      <email>w.beting@gmail.com</email>
      <country>au</country>
      <ip>122.161.72.231</ip>
      <website>http://www.betezy.com.au/horse-racing-betting.aspx</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice informative article. thanks for sharing and keep sharing such kind of articles, as these articles really helpful for experienced and new comers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="092b1499-59ee-4381-a4b2-d23bd84dbd23" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-21 02:28:10</date>
      <author>Notary Signing</author>
      <email>michel44trott@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.176.222.48</ip>
      <website>http://www.findnotarypublic.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I just wanna thank you for sharing your information and your site or blog this is simple but nice article I've ever seen i like it i learn something today...
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5f9a3819-54c5-499f-b6d3-60d7cbf47efe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-08-16 11:29:38</date>
      <author>Девушки Москвы</author>
      <email>Cole@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.4.119.245</ip>
      <website>http://prostitutki-moskvy-foto.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Зачетные девочки в Москве и других городах России и Украины только здесь.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8399f289-1cf3-40c3-b4e8-ea06a96f1602" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-11-17 21:21:34</date>
      <author>Child Security Alarm</author>
      <email>virender.sangwan@detecvision.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.176.234.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was very encouraged to find this site. I wanted to thank you for this special read. I definitely savored every little bit of it and I have you bookmarked to check out new stuff you post..</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fadb4d4b-8d2a-455e-9464-9d3bb9e3f0ec" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-02 03:36:20</date>
      <author>techvyas</author>
      <email>techvyas1@gmail.com</email>
      <country>in</country>
      <ip>182.68.140.67</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is really great because post is so nice. Thank you very much for this post.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="34ae522d-3e13-4e36-8492-6dda99fac927" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-26 16:01:08</date>
      <author>omar</author>
      <email>omarali502000@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>69.210.128.199</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:white list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice. I will add this to our blog: http://www.brownpundits.com/2011/12/26/shaheed-rani-remembering-benazir-bhutto/</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f770567b-173f-471b-b726-80b096a8e091" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-28 01:02:38</date>
      <author>fareeha</author>
      <email>fareeha.majeed@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>50.53.55.38</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Enough with charisma and  courage !   Great qualities for an actress perhaps but in a leader  -- of an entire nation --  where was &amp;#39;character &amp;#39;  ?
What about CORRUPTION ,  ENTITLEMENT ,  COSMETICS ,,,,
I refuse to grieve a woman who brought more harm and no good to the country  -  having had a chance TWICE .  
Her death was a tragedy , agree with that much.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4bc2d647-fc62-4feb-971f-7538271c349c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-01-04 10:05:33</date>
      <author>yourjuicingrecipes</author>
      <email>asikbd02@gmail.com</email>
      <country>ua</country>
      <ip>180.234.75.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>One thing I have actually noticed is that often there are plenty of myths regarding the banking companies intentions whenever talking about foreclosure. One myth in particular is the fact that the bank needs to have your house. Your banker wants your hard earned dollars, not your home. They want the amount of money they loaned you having interest. Avoiding the bank will only draw a foreclosed final result. Thanks for your posting.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e0acf090-67cd-4f3f-8534-596bac57b0d6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-01-04 22:49:45</date>
      <author>Harley Handlebars</author>
      <email>demonscyclekashuji@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.176.189.162</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like the valuable information you provide in your articles. I’ll bookmark your weblog and check again here frequently. I am quite sure I will learn many new stuff right here ! Best of luck.
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9b9ede6d-feda-468b-befd-963a4cdc6e1b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-01-04 23:44:51</date>
      <author>Carbon Bike Frames</author>
      <email>carbonroadbike@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>122.176.189.162</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am very enjoyed for this side. Its a nice topic. It help me very much to solve some problems. Its opportunity are so fantastic and working style so speedy. I think it may be help all of you. Thanks.
http://www.carbonroadbikebicyclecycling.com/</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="66ffc34f-06c6-4cd9-a4f9-e698ac0a3123" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-01-11 22:27:39</date>
      <author>Lead Prices</author>
      <email>metalexchangedirect@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>182.68.87.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Fantastic post it is.I want to thank you for your post.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="00d88966-355b-4baf-81b9-9fc2aebfc05c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-01-11 22:35:31</date>
      <author>Tummy tuck cost</author>
      <email>cosmeticharmony.com@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>182.68.87.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is so cool. I am such a huge fan of their work. I really am impressed with how much you have worked to make this website so enjoyable.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9f5af3db-7105-4a3e-ae51-0b843eb183ae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-03-06 21:13:10</date>
      <author>All India Cargo</author>
      <email>anju@humanoidsindia.com</email>
      <country>in</country>
      <ip>182.68.242.1</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>All India Cargo Packers Movers is a leader for relocating materials of different industries, houses, offices and to serve its customers country wide. All India Cargo Packers Movers Mumbai is an independent Packers Movers service providers and is ranked #1 of the country&amp;#39;s most leading Packers Movers of Mumbai.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="20281a69-790c-4b4b-87e4-4da04d9f36f6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-12-04 11:23:27</date>
      <author>wholesale earmuff</author>
      <email>kzxalamgirhossain@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>202.134.13.142</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Shis sit is very nice for seal in jewelry Top Online jewelry site.Sell with cheap rate.7% off as 1st order.visit here ...........
http://www.JTCwholesale.com</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1c1ecd89-1231-48db-b508-e34e903bf19d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-12 16:16:53</date>
      <author>chamonix transfers</author>
      <email>rashadgawler@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.173.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Believe it or not, but winter is the hot tub accident worst season for this issue. These hot tubs can be for you. In order to get cheap hot tubs by choosing to buy a spa product at home and enjoy spa everyday. They only thing which you have to work harder to correct the problem.

Also visit my blog ::  chamonix transfers - http://www.chamexpress.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2d8e0670-702c-462f-b476-2dea8ccc77eb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-09 23:21:51</date>
      <author>cialis canada pharmacy</author>
      <email>thalialeslie@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.98.70.72</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, just became aware of your blog through Google, and found that it&amp;#39;s truly informative. I&amp;#39;m gonna watch out for brussels. I&amp;#39;ll appreciate if you continue this in future. Numerous people will be benefited from your writing. Cheers!

Look into my blog  cialis canada pharmacy - http://canadianedrugstore.com/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>b4fcf796-f929-49e7-bac1-1dde312a5ff3</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
    <email>anju@humanoidsindia.com</email>
    <email>kzxalamgirhossain@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>