<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>I speak for the judges</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div class="MsoNormal" align="left" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 140px; height: 140px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=tariq_hassan_140x140.gif" alt="" width="140" height="140" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="MsoNormal" align="left" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I&amp;nbsp;am not a judge. Yet when I read in the newspapers that the federal government has notified that 24 judges of the provincial high courts, who did not take oath under the PCO, have &amp;#39;ceased to hold office&amp;#39; with effect from Nov 3, my heart went out to them and also to the judges of the Supreme Court who await the same fate. [more]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Alas there is little I can do to help any of them, despite the fact that the government&amp;#39;s action is totally unconstitutional, unlawful, unjust, unwarranted, unethical, improper, and just plainly and simply wrong any way you look at it. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The adjudicator of last resort &amp;mdash; the judiciary &amp;mdash; has been besieged by the government and there is no credible institution in the country to provide relief, let alone dispense justice to these judges or to anyone else opposed to the government. The legal fraternity and civil society have reacted vigorously and sought the restoration of the pre-Nov 3 judiciary. However, the legal fraternity, though extremely active and vocal, has its limitations and civil society is not as organised. They would need the undiluted support of the politicians to achieve this objective. Ultimately, however, it is all of us, as concerned citizens, who have to ensure this outcome.
&lt;script&gt;
&lt;!--
D(["mb","\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;Over the years, the government has become adept at arbitrarily removing anyone who dares to withstand its pressure. I recall suffering the same fate in early 2006, when I was notified through the TV channels during Eid holidays that I had &amp;#39;ceased to hold office&amp;#39; of chairman, Securities and Exchange Commission of Pakistan, with immediate effect. The government was then at the pinnacle of its power and I had refused to bow to governmental pressure to abandon investigations into the stock market crisis of 2005.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;The notification removing me was not only improper but, like the present notification for the judges, had absolutely no legal basis whatsoever. While I did not consider it proper to go public for the sake of maintaining the dignity of the institution I had headed, I did write a letter to all policy board members and commissioners of the SECP and shared with them the circumstances that led to my removal.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;I also copied the letter to the Chief Justice of Pakistan and the attorney general in the hope that they would take notice of the illegal and improper way I was removed from office. I had not sought personal vindication but had hoped that the highest judicial and legal officers of the country would take action to salvage the institutional independence and honour of the SECP. However, neither the Chief Justice of Pakistan nor the attorney general took any note of this egregious infraction of the law.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;Institutions are more important than individuals. However, as a friend of mine reminded me, it is individuals who make the institutions. The judges who refused to be cowed down by the president and chief of army staff to give judgment in his favour and those who have since refused to take oath under the Provisional Constitution Order are indeed judges who have shown their mettle and who can be relied on to foster and maintain the independence of the judiciary.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;They have not only been sent home; they have also been put under house arrest. In causing personal wrong to these judges, the government has in fact dishonoured the institution of the judiciary. While the wrongs done to these individuals may heal in time, the damage done to the institution will leave an everlasting scar on its face.\n",1]
);
//--&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Over the years, the government has become adept at arbitrarily removing anyone who dares to withstand its pressure. I recall suffering the same fate in early 2006, when I was notified through the TV channels during Eid holidays that I had &amp;#39;ceased to hold office&amp;#39; of chairman, Securities and Exchange Commission of Pakistan, with immediate effect. The government was then at the pinnacle of its power and I had refused to bow to governmental pressure to abandon investigations into the stock market crisis of 2005. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The notification removing me was not only improper but, like the present notification for the judges, had absolutely no legal basis whatsoever. While I did not consider it proper to go public for the sake of maintaining the dignity of the institution I had headed, I did write a letter to all policy board members and commissioners of the SECP and shared with them the circumstances that led to my removal. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I also copied the letter to the Chief Justice of Pakistan and the attorney general in the hope that they would take notice of the illegal and improper way I was removed from office. I had not sought personal vindication but had hoped that the highest judicial and legal officers of the country would take action to salvage the institutional independence and honour of the SECP. However, neither the Chief Justice of Pakistan nor the attorney general took any note of this egregious infraction of the law. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Institutions are more important than individuals. However, as a friend of mine reminded me, it is individuals who make the institutions. The judges who refused to be cowed down by the president and chief of army staff to give judgment in his favour and those who have since refused to take oath under the Provisional Constitution Order are indeed judges who have shown their mettle and who can be relied on to foster and maintain the independence of the judiciary. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
They have not only been sent home; they have also been put under house arrest. In causing personal wrong to these judges, the government has in fact dishonoured the institution of the judiciary. While the wrongs done to these individuals may heal in time, the damage done to the institution will leave an everlasting scar on its face.
&lt;script&gt;
&lt;!--
D(["mb","\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;When Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammad Chaudhry was sent on &amp;#39;forced leave&amp;#39; in March, I struggled with my colleagues to preserve the dignity of his office. As a concerned citizen, I filed a petition before the Supreme Court for his reinstatement. As a concerned citizen, I also participated actively in the movement for the independence of the judiciary and the supremacy of the rule of law.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;As a concerned citizen, I continued to take part in the movement for the restoration of democracy in the country — and got battered by the police while protesting peacefully outside the Election Commission on Sept 29. As a concerned citizen, I continue to struggle with the legal fraternity for the restoration of constitutional rule and the reinstatement of the independent judges who refused to take oath under the PCO, more so because as a person who has suffered governmental abuse I understand not only their personal plight but also the importance of an independent judiciary.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;In his article &amp;#39;First things first&amp;#39; (Dawn, Dec 6) Munir Malik urged the political parties to press for the restoration of the judiciary in their charter of demands, and impressed upon them that without an independent judiciary, true democracy will remain a distant dream. I join him in his plea. If the politicians choose not to speak for the judiciary today, there will be no one to speak for them tomorrow.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;Let me remind them of the famous poem from the Nazi era that encapsulates the fate of all those who condone injustice: &amp;quot;First they came for the communists, and I did not speak out — because I was not a communist; … Then they came for the Jews, and I did not speak out — because I was not a Jew; Then they came for me — and there was no one left to speak out for me.\n\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;The government has indiscriminately arrested not only the non-compliant judges but also lawyers, students and human rights advocates as well as political and social activists. For those of us who are lucky to be free, let us speak for them before the government comes for us.\n",1]
);
//--&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
When Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammad Chaudhry was sent on &amp;#39;forced leave&amp;#39; in March, I struggled with my colleagues to preserve the dignity of his office. As a concerned citizen, I filed a petition before the Supreme Court for his reinstatement. As a concerned citizen, I also participated actively in the movement for the independence of the judiciary and the supremacy of the rule of law. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As a concerned citizen, I continued to take part in the movement for the restoration of democracy in the country &amp;mdash; and got battered by the police while protesting peacefully outside the Election Commission on Sept 29. As a concerned citizen, I continue to struggle with the legal fraternity for the restoration of constitutional rule and the reinstatement of the independent judges who refused to take oath under the PCO, more so because as a person who has suffered governmental abuse I understand not only their personal plight but also the importance of an independent judiciary. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In his article &amp;#39;First things first&amp;#39; (Dawn, Dec 6) Munir Malik urged the political parties to press for the restoration of the judiciary in their charter of demands, and impressed upon them that without an independent judiciary, true democracy will remain a distant dream. I join him in his plea. If the politicians choose not to speak for the judiciary today, there will be no one to speak for them tomorrow. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Let me remind them of the famous poem from the Nazi era that encapsulates the fate of all those who condone injustice: &amp;quot;First they came for the communists, and I did not speak out &amp;mdash; because I was not a communist; &amp;hellip; Then they came for the Jews, and I did not speak out &amp;mdash; because I was not a Jew; Then they came for me &amp;mdash; and there was no one left to speak out for me. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The government has indiscriminately arrested not only the non-compliant judges but also lawyers, students and human rights advocates as well as political and social activists. For those of us who are lucky to be free, let us speak for them before the government comes for us.
&lt;script&gt;
&lt;!--
D(["mb","\u003cbr\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;\u003ci\&gt;The writer, a lawyer based in Islamabad, is a former chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission of Pakistan.\u003cbr\&gt;\u003ca href\u003d\"mailto:thassan@ijurist.org\" target\u003d\"_blank\" onclick\u003d\"return top.js.OpenExtLink(window,event,this)\"\&gt;thassan@ijurist.org\u003c/a\&gt;\u003c/i\&gt;\u003cbr\&gt;\u003c/center\&gt;\n",0]
);
D(["ce"]);
//--&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The writer, a lawyer based in Islamabad, is a former chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission of Pakistan.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:thassan@ijurist.org" target="_blank"&gt;thassan@ijurist.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Source:&lt;a href="http://www.dawn.com.pk"&gt; Dawn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;
&lt;div class="MsoNormal" align="left" style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt"&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-14 08:31:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:59:56</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>I-speak-for-the-judges</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>dr tariq hassan</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="69e08626-6b28-431f-a0c1-9ba61b6d9028" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 17:57:07</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews amazon</author>
      <email>felixedmonds@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.169.198</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for the auspicious writeup. It if truth be told used to be a entertainment account it. Look complicated to far introduced agreeable from you! However, how could we keep in touch?

Also visit my web page ::  garcinia cambogia reviews amazon - http://bleurestaurantandwinebar.com/why-you-shouldnt-use-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4951c2f5-cd58-482f-a714-7c1c8e5bafb6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 18:35:43</date>
      <author>Jillian Michaels Body Revolution</author>
      <email>etsukoellsworth@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.62.184</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I got this website from my buddy who informed me concerning this website and now this time I am browsing this site and reading very informative articles here.

Feel free to surf to my weblog -  Jillian Michaels Body Revolution - http://www.xfire.com/blog/douglasha/4685707 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fb2c2c42-d808-48c7-a069-9273631cf1a0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-24 14:18:24</date>
      <author>cambogia extract</author>
      <email>claudetteknudson@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.67</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, its nice piece of writing on the topic of media print, we all be aware of media is a wonderful source of data.

Visit my website -  cambogia extract - http://www.livehealthyblog.net/need-to-you-buy-pure-garcinia-cambogia-extract-for-your-diet-plan/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b10af29e-a531-4193-8972-efe8dc928aa1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 02:43:08</date>
      <author>body revolution</author>
      <email>chadwick_mcdougall@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Definitely believe that which you stated. Your favorite justification seemed to be on the net the simplest thing to be aware of. I say to you, I certainly get annoyed while people think about worries that they plainly don&amp;#39;t know about. You managed to hit the nail upon the top as well as defined out the whole thing without having side-effects , people can take a signal. Will probably be back to get more. Thanks

Review my homepage ::  body revolution - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="905df264-e451-4de0-bf4b-3d9ad82f92cd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 10:05:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight Loss</author>
      <email>lidia.sparrow@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.254.250.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you wish for to improve your familiarity just keep visiting this website and be updated with the latest information posted here.

My web blog;  garcinia cambogia weight Loss - http://www.topwriter.biz/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="01658692-8132-4e31-877d-8968a62cbf9f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 19:01:22</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia dosage</author>
      <email>mariannepappas@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.23.175</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello Dear, are you truly visiting this web page regularly, if so afterward you will absolutely get pleasant know-how.

Here is my blog post -  pure garcinia cambogia dosage - http://jerryssweetstore.com/general/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7214c346-31ba-42cd-a663-bc0aa495e015" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-04 21:08:48</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>kristin.shively@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Way cool! Some very valid points! I appreciate you writing this article plus the rest of the website is also really good.

My web blog  garcinia cambogia hca - http://coko365.com/?p=54 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9a67ec1-ff61-492d-b199-d182597c922c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 23:13:17</date>
      <author>jillian michaels body revolution system</author>
      <email>richelleholman@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I love your blog.. very nice colors &amp;amp; theme. Did you create this website yourself or did you hire someone to do it for you? Plz reply as I&amp;#39;m looking to create my own blog and would like to find out where u got this from. thank you

Review my web blog;  jillian michaels body revolution system - http://www.lipo-6reviewszone.com/a-manual-to-diet-plan-and-bodyweight-reduction-guides/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="987f9965-1819-4b20-93ee-de06493a82af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 23:44:59</date>
      <author>body revolution meal plan</author>
      <email>bethanyyost@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Remarkable! Its truly awesome paragraph, I have got much clear idea on the topic of from this post.

Also visit my web site;  body revolution meal plan - http://famhealth.org/how-to-lose-excess-weight-with-jillian-michaels-meal-supply-diet-strategy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1ad2887f-04ac-4f9c-960a-b9240c3fa253" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 12:22:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>teresita_sandoval@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.131.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I visited many sites except the audio feature for audio songs present at this web site is actually marvelous.

Feel free to surf to my blog post;  garcinia cambogia extract - http://stjohnscycles.com/?p=6 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9d41643-6a1a-4c34-a9a2-6ba94fb713a8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 16:11:47</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>irish-withrow@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We absolutely love your blog and find nearly all of your post&amp;#39;s to be just what I&amp;#39;m looking for. can you offer guest writers to write content in your case? I wouldn&amp;#39;t mind writing a post or elaborating on most of the subjects you write about here. Again, awesome weblog!

Also visit my blog post ...  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://nj-jidan.org/is-it-safe-to-take-weight-loss-supplements-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="02d59a13-058a-4a6e-977c-1f52a569e9b9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 22:24:21</date>
      <author>Stone wave Cooker reviews</author>
      <email>amycorcoran@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I used to be suggested this web site through my cousin. I&amp;#39;m not positive whether or not this post is written by way of him as no one else recognize such distinctive approximately my trouble. You are amazing! Thanks!

My homepage  Stone wave Cooker reviews - http://thelmadpk.beeplog.com/353566_2008752.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="454dc54c-1568-4be4-901f-6f38f83f1812" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 22:25:15</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>dennis-kersey@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there, I do think your site might be having browser compatibility issues. Whenever I take a look at your site in Safari, it looks fine but when opening in I.E., it has some overlapping issues. I simply wanted to give you a quick heads up! Aside from that, excellent blog!

My weblog  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.rewirequote.co.uk/dr-oz-explores-historical-ayurvedic-secrets-and-techniques-for-all-natural-excess-weight-decline/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="11ee48a4-c54c-4eef-b065-e8f40f66020d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 12:57:22</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>susie_peralta@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.208.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I do accept as true with all the ideas you&amp;#39;ve offered for your post. They&amp;#39;re very convincing and will certainly work. Nonetheless, the posts are too brief for beginners. May just you please extend them a bit from subsequent time? Thanks for the post.

My site ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://kern-act.me/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="82235289-f536-4669-afa7-e57738d32b7c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 19:16:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>vernahickson@mailservice.ms</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I blog frequently and I genuinely appreciate your content. The article has truly peaked my interest. I will take a note of your website and keep checking for new information about once a week. I subscribed to your RSS feed too.

Visit my web site:  garcinia cambogia - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aa64c76f-55b9-4d55-a37d-37193fb876a9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:52:19</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>bennie_morris@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>No matter if some one searches for his vital thing, so he/she wants to be available that in detail, therefore that thing is maintained over here.

Feel free to visit my weblog  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.freewoof.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="924a098e-880c-4160-bca4-23cc88881baa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 08:41:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>benjaminedmonds@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This page really has all the information and facts I needed concerning this subject and didn&amp;#39;t know who to ask.

my web-site;  garcinia cambogia - http://ourbor.us/normal-urge-for-food-suppressants-for-bodyweight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="48182b02-7798-4083-b5b2-0bc9e02c7c05" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 11:39:33</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract Negative side effects</author>
      <email>mattiecothran@snail-mail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.62.71.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello to all, how is everything, I think every one is getting more from this site, and your views are nice in favor of new visitors.

my web blog  garcinia cambogia extract Negative side effects - http://piercell.com/get-the-realities-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fda44ed3-10d0-4676-aa08-2738bd0a1750" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 09:48:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>herman-houle@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I always emailed this weblog post page to all my friends, because if like to read it next my links will too.

Feel free to surf to my web-site;  garcinia cambogia extract - http://crapemailfromadude.com/?p=56 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2fe510b5-713b-47ec-b9b4-e5740da8e8e8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 11:45:18</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>wesley-bowen@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! Quick question that&amp;#39;s totally off topic. Do you know how to make your site mobile friendly? My web site looks weird when viewing from my apple iphone. I&amp;#39;m trying to find a theme or plugin that might be able to resolve this problem. If you have any recommendations, please share. Thanks!

Feel free to surf to my website;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://meetsmartpeople.com/get-the-truths-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="15238ea7-15de-484d-8984-6d4631a94789" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 13:09:25</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>santomontoya@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Marvelous, what a website it is! This blog gives helpful data to us, keep it up.

Here is my web-site;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://pultneyvillehistoricalsociety.org/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3e61fa08-5d9e-49f8-b271-a331acb1ca61" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 06:10:05</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>arielle.peralta@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Helpful info. Fortunate me I found your web site unintentionally, and I&amp;#39;m surprised why this accident didn&amp;#39;t took place earlier! I bookmarked it.

my website:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.sxqyjy.com/weight-loss-2/many-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5c6bb444-ac7c-4e56-a6ef-b53d5855eb48" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 08:19:20</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>shereehyatt@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.166</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya just wanted to give you a quick heads up and let you know a few of the pictures aren&amp;#39;t loading correctly. I&amp;#39;m not sure why but I think its a linking issue. I&amp;#39;ve tried it in two different browsers and both show the same results.

Also visit my web site:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://nzppa.org.nz/can-garcinia-cambogia-extract-assist-much-with-weight-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="eb357a47-3704-4598-bd52-a9e13698ea1a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 08:14:45</date>
      <author>http://dailynest.com</author>
      <email>ellacardona@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.134.226</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>One  http://dailynest.com - http://dailynest.com/members/victorbur/activity/413235/  of the joys of travelling in this way is that it allows you to indulge in people-watching not least in the upmarket French resort of Cassis. It was a slip of the tongue, it was an immediately impressive beast.
 motorhome insurance - http://blog.wardrobewiz.com/members/augustus0/activity/12118/   self build campervan insurance - http://webmasterlondon.com/SEO/user.php?login=austinwis  cheap motorhome insurance ( budpoint.net - http://budpoint.net/ramka.php?id_wpisu=85470&amp;amp;url=http://motorhomeinsurance.blog.co.uk/ )
 classic camper van insurance - http://www.cornappleresearch.org/user.php?login=nickolasr  motorhome insurance ( penny-stock-social.com - http://penny-stock-social.com/blogs/viewstory/245582 ) campervan insurance;  forolumis.es - http://forolumis.es/activity/p/147885/ ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="de98f4ec-3086-4d6a-ac29-3aebd7e03d36" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-04 12:01:02</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>chester-edkins@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.174.130</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>At this time it appears like Movable Type is the best blogging platform out there right now. (from what I&amp;#39;ve read) Is that what you are using on your blog?

Also visit my homepage;  garcinia cambogia - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f8b37e11-352c-4917-82da-b9f0b00a9ebd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 01:59:10</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>christal-waters@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.253.169</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Possession of the most traumatic events of Birkenhead-born O&amp;#39;Grady&amp;#39;s life the death david cameron of his six-year old son, Ivan.

Review my homepage - arrogant -  www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron  -</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>4d6fb932-5c29-45c8-8854-b6129da656b6</category>
    <category>77aaeaca-44b7-4987-8967-e5125aeec852</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>