<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Anarkali </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+1.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mudassar Bashir&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Anarkali&amp;rsquo;s name and her story is an unforgettable one. When we look into the pages of history, there are various conflicting accounts of her story. One group says that she was Prince Saleem&amp;rsquo;s lover and was a pretty slave girl in Emperor Akbar&amp;rsquo;s court. Her name is&amp;nbsp; variously described as Nadira begum, Sharf un Nisa or Shareef un Nisa. Emperor Akbar never approved of her relationship with Shekhu (Prince Saleem). He could not put down the fire of love that burned in her heart and, in anger, bricked her up in a wall. When Prince Saleem ascended the throne, he erected an elegant mausoleum over her grave.[more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Another school of historians is of the view that this mausoleum belongs to of Jahangir&amp;rsquo;s step mother who had a special affinity for him. One distinguished scholar who has researched this is the late Maulana Ilm ud Din Salik. I myself agree with his conclusions. He is of the view that this is the burial place of Jahangir&amp;rsquo;s own wife. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;He has written that the mausoleum was built for Jehangir's wife, who was the daughter of Zain Khan Kokah. She was closer to the emperor than was Nurjahan. If one looks at the books written during the time of Akbar and Jahangir, one finds no mention of a slave girl called Anarkali, who caused a conflict between Akbar and Sheikhu. Tuzk-e-Jahangiri is a well known autobiography of &amp;nbsp;Jehangir. In this book the emperor has written candidly about&amp;nbsp; the events of his life from his childhood to old age in a great deal of detail.&amp;nbsp;At several places in this book he has mentioned his fondness for wine, women and meat. Later, in the times of Shah Jahan, Mohammed Saleh Kamboh wrote Shah Jahan&amp;nbsp;Nama. The incident has not been mentioned anywhere in these books.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Manochi, who was a traveller given to much concoction, has added several anecdotes of his own invention to his books about the Mughals. Even he has not described this incident anywhere in his writings. In the British period there was much talk about it when Imtiaz Ali Taj wrote his play Anarkali. The Mughal court was painted in a different colour in this play. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; color: #000000;"&gt;Afterwards, Khan Asif, who was originally a resident of Mochi Gate area Lahore, immortalised this character by making the great movie called Mughl-e-Azam. Madhu Bala played Anarkali in the movie. This turned&amp;nbsp; Anarkali into a legend. The Film itself is became a world classic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of the building&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Buildings of Jahangir&amp;rsquo;s period are well known internationally. Jahangir gave special personal attention to the construction of this tomb.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;In line with the eastern side of the dome of the mausoleum, lies the mound slab of the grave with two dates visible on it: 1998 AH (or 1599 CE) and 1024 AH (or 1615 CE). A review of history indicates that the first of these dates corresponds to the date of death of King Jahangir&amp;rsquo;s wife and the second date is probably the date of inauguration of&amp;nbsp;mausoleum itself. Mausoleum&amp;rsquo;s building has two floors with a dome in the centre. Both floors had eight doors and around them in a circle, stood as many domed turrets. Each turret had its own door and an oriel (jharoka). The mausoleum&amp;rsquo;s building was surrounded by a big garden. After the fall of the Mughal Empire, the mausoleum fell into the hands of Sikhs. The plinth of the grave, made of marble stone, was uprooted and shifted to Darbar Sahib. Along with the plinth, the mound-slab of the grave was also excavated from its foundations. It bore dates and poetic inscriptions and this reduced its immediate utility to the minimum. So, for many years it lay abandoned under the sepulchral dome.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fimage.axd.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 6px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Even worse fate was in store for this mausoleum, as many a time it was put to torch. The brick sellers took apart the boundary wall and pilfered the bricks. After the fall of the Sikhs, the British Raj did not fare much better. The colonial British whitewashed the biggest and most beautiful dome with white paint. This dome had exhibited the most exquisite mosaic work. Later, the colonial British government converted the whole building into a church and christened it St James Church. The basement of the mausoleum, which housed the actual grave, was closed pemanently. The mound-slab, which should have been relocated squarely under the dome was moved to a corner to the east.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;To date, the mound slab is at the same place, as nobody has the audacity to move it back to its original place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 6px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&lt;img style="font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: medium;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+6.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;After the partition, this mausoleum was used as the civil secretariat and many new buildings were built in its garden. Kanhayya Lal, in his book &amp;lsquo;Tareekh e Lahore&amp;rsquo; (p318), writes thus about this mausoleum:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;lsquo;This magnificent mausoleum is made of baked bricks. It is an octagon in shape and each side of the octagon has a door. On the inside, the mausoleum has two storeys. In the centre, it has a magnificent dome. The upper storey has nine windows, seven ventilators and four latticed ventilators. The main dome is in the centre around which are eight smaller cupolas, containing eight side openings each. In the past, it used to have eight portals on the lower and eight on the upper floor. Now only the lower ones remain on which mirror inlaid double doors have been installed. The upper floor portals have been altered. The mausoleum rests on a vast octagonal plinth, elevated to the height of fours steps. The main door for general use is now towards the South. In the Southeastern corner, a small door leads to a separate accommodation which contains the marble mound slab of Anarkali. A stone crucifix is affixed on the main dome.&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+3.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="400" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Passing by the Civil Secretariat , one can not even imagine the magnificent mausoleum inside this government building. When you enter the Civil Secretariat from the Lower Mall gate, you will see the white dome of this building towards the western end. Another road off lower Mall road goes down towards Krishan Nagar (Islam Pura). In its beginning on the left side there is another Government building called People&amp;rsquo;s House. A little ahead is the Government Printing Press building with Chishtia High School across the way. Behind the Printing Press is an old cricket ground called Baba Ground.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Many renowned cricketers have played on this ground. If one looks towards the South from this ground, the whole mausoleum building can be seen. Behind this mausoleum is an old mosque where marble has been used in the dome and sandstone in the minaret. Behind the dome of the mausoleum one can see some old houses in an old residential area. To reach the building of the mausoleum, the door of the Punjab Bank can also be used. In the Civil Secretariat, big cars and big officers remind one of the British colonial era. At one end of the dome, a new door can be seen whereas its old and original doors have been plastered over with mud and limestone. The building of the mausoleum is now used as the official record office. Here, old coins, copies of old writings and pictures have been displayed in glass show cases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;On the eastern corner of the tomb is the grave made of white marble. On this grave ninety names of God are written. All this is written in &amp;lsquo;Khat e Jali&amp;rsquo; (Jali Script). Similar writings also exist on the graves of Asif Jah and Jahangir. a Persian verse by Jahangir is written on the casket. This verse reflects pining for the lost love:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: medium; letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;تا قیامت شکر گویم کردگار خویش را &amp;nbsp; آه گر من باز بینم رویی یار خویش را&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Verse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;I will sing Lord&amp;rsquo;s praises till the end of time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;If I could see again the love of my life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;The name of &amp;lsquo;Majnoon Saleem Akbar&amp;rsquo; is clearly visible underneath God&amp;rsquo;s names.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;The inner building of the tomb is solid beautiful and exuberant as it must have been when it was built. On the western side of the dome two new rooms have been added. Some officers have written history books sitting in these offices but they seem to have been oblivious to the history of the place itself. This tomb is associated with one of the greatest love stories of Lahore. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; color: #232323;"&gt;But, it is the bad luck of the inhabitants of this city, that they, not just, do not know anything about this tomb, but&amp;nbsp;have no easy access to it either.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; color: #232323;"&gt;The general public knows this place only as the Civil Secretariat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt; In India an epic story is related to a grand building of Taj Mahal. For this very reason, tourists from all over the world flock to this place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;An important page of Lahore saga, which has been used to make many movies and to earn fame and fortunes, sadly for the inhabitants of Lahore, is not known to&amp;nbsp;the new generation at all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; color: #000000;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Making this tomb accessible has been the responsibility of all successive governments following partition&amp;nbsp;of the Subcontinent but none of them have paid any attention to it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;The governments' first responsibility is to enhance its profile by relocating the archived official record; and making its main entrance accessible to the people by separating it completely from the civil secretariat; otherwise this tomb will be forever a governmental office.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PS&lt;/strong&gt;: A new outlook is currently being given to this tomb by&amp;nbsp;opening up a big space around this tomb and by renovating&amp;nbsp;its old mosque&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #1f497d;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;Translated by Hikmat House&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 15px; font-family: Damascus; color: #1f497d; min-height: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+4.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+7.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+8.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f3%2fAnarkali+10.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-03-16 09:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-03-22 13:53:51</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Anarkali-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="50c70249-9f1e-4f4f-8a55-a4bf109a8943" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-06 14:28:02</date>
      <author>investasi kebun sawit</author>
      <email>ankecolston@mailnew.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.7.120</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>And there were more palm oil 2009 than 100 years old, the first was Providencia, but they had an incredible visual capacity to express themselves. The two south-east Asian countries account for 85% of the world&amp;#39;s palm oil supply.

Here is my weblog ::  investasi kebun sawit - http://www.investasikelapasawit.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bf17717a-b200-4db7-8208-9f4a5db9c05b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-13 17:47:13</date>
      <author>daftar harga pulsa termurah</author>
      <email>wallace_elisha@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.143.163</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>However, we remain focused on pulsa sangat murah our work to build ADC&amp;#39;s long-term value as a leading global network infrastructure company. So again, earlier I mentioned that we don&amp;#39;t address pulsa sangat murah the entire PC market, we address a subsection of the PC market. Peter BlackmoreThe growth over the last few years. And then if you look at the rankings by suppliers in the telecom side.

Feel free to visit my webpage:  daftar harga pulsa termurah - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cP2Ir1mn8x0 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5360d195-fc2c-4094-a3e7-f2e0b4fbf241" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-04 05:08:36</date>
      <author>video creation</author>
      <email>fletacoover@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.27.112.110</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Scamming is a form of online crime, in that it can cause havoc with computer systems. What we&amp;#39;re going to be doing is we&amp;#39;re going to be coming together and we&amp;#39;re going to be presenting in a live webinar with a Q&amp;amp;A session and also looking at answering all of your questions and presenting to you a really cutting edge type of technology that we put together that will help you outsource all the way to anyone that you want around the world and do it all from home without you having to send over any files or anything overseas. That should tell &amp;quot;Supernatural&amp;quot; enthusiasts how important it is to get your tickets now.

My blog post ...  video creation - http://www.fiverr.com/allinoneseo/create-an-eye-catching-video-from-your-images-and-turn-it-into-hollywood-video,http://www.fiverr.com/allinoneseo/create-an-awesome-wedding-album-video-or-video-from-your-image-with-stunning-effects-to-share-with-your-friends-and-family </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="284e569f-418f-47a0-b0f0-da274de4e3b4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-03-07 19:38:40</date>
      <author>cheap christmas ideas</author>
      <email>isabell_burg@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.172.188.73</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m pretty pleased to discover this web site. I need to to thank you for ones time for this fantastic read!! I definitely appreciated every bit of it and i also have you book-marked to look at new information on your site.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ffdec16e-76ee-422d-af13-9b64919bbc31" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-06 09:30:58</date>
      <author>overhead door repair</author>
      <email>veola.bromby@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>1.179.183.109</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi colleagues, its enormous post regarding educationand completely defined, keep it up all the time.  my site ::  overhead door repair - https://www.google.com/maps/d/viewer?mid=1PHKM3iHUQyjQjjth-I_IWUJ75bQ&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;ll=29.720272697951877%2C-95.47847294999997&amp;amp;z=9 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="305ea62e-1bd4-4d13-ae4c-c498fc35cbd1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-08-28 15:03:48</date>
      <author>http://dom-mody37.ru/index.php/component/k2/itemlist/user/17839</author>
      <email>chasechill@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.211.162.240</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think this is among the so much significant info for me. And i am satisfied studying your article. But want to statement on some normal issues, The website style is great, the articles is in point of fact excellent : D. Good process, cheers  My weblog; Аренда квартир в Аликанте;  http://dom-mody37.ru/index.php/component/k2/itemlist/user/17839 - http://dom-mody37.ru/index.php/component/k2/itemlist/user/17839 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0446fc4b-5a48-4893-b008-6506ffb7ab1d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-26 14:44:50</date>
      <author>judi poker</author>
      <email>porterkunkle@gmx.net</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>176.61.139.75</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello! Quick question that&amp;#39;s totally off topic. Do you know how to make your site mobile friendly? My web site looks weird when browsing from my iphone. I&amp;#39;m trying to find a template or plugin that might be able to correct this problem. If you have any suggestions, please share. With thanks!  Here is my web site  judi poker - http://playerqq.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e5728ba-0b6c-4c96-9391-57fd31f42a65" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-24 13:33:46</date>
      <author>mezo</author>
      <email>wendellleddy@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>104.151.74.123</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Oh my goodness! Awesome article dude! Many thanks, However I am having difficulties with your RSS. I don&amp;#39;t know why I can&amp;#39;t join it. Is there anybody else getting the same RSS problems? Anyone that knows the answer can you kindly respond? Thanx!!  Stop by my website  mezo - http://mezocoupons.blogspot.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d7fabbf7-f27b-46a7-bd0e-8c43ddb1591e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-29 14:54:51</date>
      <author>buy lumigan eyelash</author>
      <email>aguedadonahoe@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.89.79.65</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure why but this site is loading very slow for me. Is anyone else having this issue or is it a issue on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later on and see if the problem still exists.  Here is my web-site -  buy lumigan eyelash - https://sites.google.com/site/buylumiganonlineoverthecounter/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c738086f-8f0f-445c-b20f-31793d74ccc5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-29 16:25:26</date>
      <author>buy lumigan drops</author>
      <email>isaacqualls@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>199.229.233.122</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>That is very attention-grabbing, You are an overly professional blogger. I have joined your rss feed and look ahead to searching for more of your wonderful post. Also, I&amp;#39;ve shared your website in my social networks  My blog post ::  buy lumigan drops - https://sites.google.com/site/buylumiganonlineoverthecounter/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>