<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Ms. Bhutto, A free Judiciary But Detained Judges - An Open Letter by Ghazala Minallah</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;h1 style="margin: auto 0in"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.teeth.com.pk/blog/2007/12/02/ms-bhutto-a-free-judiciary-but-detained-judges-an-open-letter-by-ghazala-minallah/" title="Permanent Link to Ms. Bhutto, A free Judiciary But Detained Judges - An Open Letter by Ghazala Minallah"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;font face="arial,helvetica,sans-serif" size="2"&gt;By Ghazala Minallah&amp;nbsp;d/o Late Justice Safdar Shah&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 92px; height: 107px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=scroll9.JPG" alt="" width="92" height="107" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Dear Mohtarma Benazir Bhutto,&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I was absolutely shocked and amazed at your latest statement regarding the judiciary. How could you, of all people, say that you believed in an independent judiciary BUT that personalities did not matter? If personalities did not matter then why was Justice Iftikhar Chaudhry removed? Why were some judges locked up whereas others were not? If personalities did not matter then why is Musharraf waging a personal war against the CJ? You do not have to be a genius to figure out the reason. How can you separate the personalities from the institution? What you have on Constitution Avenue right now is a besieged and helpless building. The unfortunate but harsh truth is that right now we are a besieged nation as well. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ms. Bhutto, I am writing to you because your statement has shocked and disturbed me to the extent that I feel I have no option but to reach out to you in this manner. I would like to remind you, since you seem to have forgotten, that you too were the victim of a corrupt judiciary. If Justice Iftikhar had been the CJ of the Supreme Court at that time then perhaps your father would never have been hanged. Had the entire bench been like the present one then there would have been a unanimous judgment. But the judgment was not unanimous - it was a 4 to 3 split &amp;ndash; just one judge too many on the wrong side. One more upright personality on the right side and our history would have been different. So yes, personalities certainly do matter.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ms. Bhutto, I am writing to you in desperation because I am the daughter of Late Justice Safdar Shah, who was one of the three dissenting judges. When Mr., Bhutto was the Prime Minister my father was CJ of the Peshawar High Court. Both these headstrong personalities did not get on with each other, and because of Safdar Shah&amp;rsquo;s constant criticism and disagreement regarding the reforms and policies being introduced by the PM, the latter had him prematurely retired by introducing the 5 th Amendment. After the coup, when Gen. Zia took over, and Mr. Bhutto was charged and convicted of Conspiracy to murder by the Lahore High Court, he appealed to the Supreme Court. Gen. Zia wanted Mr. Bhutto dead and he did his best to manipulate the bench. It soon became obvious as to WHY Safdar Shah had recently been appointed as judge of the Supreme Court . Having the typical mind-set of a dictator, Zia was sure that he would be vindictive and take revenge. But, he was wrong and the rest is history. WHY? Because three of the judges had the courage to say NO, and did not give in to the threats and pressure exerted on them. So yes Ms Bhutto, personalities do matter. Had Justice (retd) Wajiuddin&amp;rsquo;s father , the late Hon.Waheeduddin not been prematurely retired on extremely dubious medical grounds , history could have been different, No one can dispute the fact that the judgment was wrong since Justice (retd) Nasim Hassan Shah confessed on a talk show on TV a few years ago that the judges were threatened and pressurized into giving that judgment. Yes Ms. Bhutto, they were, and I am a witness to that fact. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ms. Bhutto, our paths crossed briefly and both of us were victims of a corrupt judiciary which colluded with a Military Dictator. But I am not writing this letter to lament about our plight, since nothing we went through can possibly compare to the torture and torment you and your family went through .Have you forgotten the times when you visited your father in prison? Have you forgotten the humiliating tactics those heartless tyrants subjected you and your family to? Have you forgotten the last time you went to visit him in prison and were not able to hug him? Whenever I think about that grave injustice, which was nothing but a judicial murder, my heart goes out to you and what you suffered then and have suffered since. That is precisely why I am at my wits end and cannot understand WHY you cannot value the importance of independent judges. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ms.Bhutto, do you think you are invincible? Are you so blinded that you cannot or will not acknowledge the truth? Does it never occur to you that some day you might have to face those judges in the present Supreme Court.? Well let me please spell it out. With independent judges you get a verdict you deserve, whereas with the present kind of farce you get a judgment dictated by the intelligence agencies or the dictator himself. Do you honestly not know or are you honestly not aware of the grave injustice going on? Does it not send a chill up your spine that if the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court can be tossed around by Musharraf it could very well be you as well ?For God&amp;rsquo;s sake Ms. Bhutto , WAKE UP .You owe it to your father as well as to the nation to defend the judiciary and fight for its independence . &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;My father continued to be persecuted even after the judgment and we were forced to leave the country. But I will never forgive or forget those responsible for the torment my father went through during his last years. He died an unhappy man and was never able to get over the fact that he was not able to prevent the cold-blooded murder of an innocent man. And that innocent person was your father for God&amp;rsquo;s sake! I have vowed that I will continue to fight for the independence of the judiciary come what may! I was confident and certain that once you were back you would definitely take up this battle and lead the nation towards sanity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ms. Bhutto, is it not obvious to you WHY Musharraf wants Justice Iftikhar out of the way? Ask the families of the &amp;lsquo;missing persons&amp;rsquo;, who for the first time were being heard and for the first time they could see a light at the end of the tunnel. Everyone knows who is responsible but no one before this CJ had the courage to take up the matter. Ask the countless downtrodden people who had discovered that they could have direct access to the CJ through Suo Moto notices. Ask 2 and 3 yr old Aneela and Tasleem from Naudero Feroze in Sindh , ask 4 yr old Shaneela or 6yr old Munni or 8 yr old Marina from Mardan what this Chief Justice has done for them. These innocent little girls were the victims of jirga decisions according to which they were to be handed over to the enemy as a symbol of truce .It was Justice Iftikhar who took serious notice of this barbaric custom and passed strict orders to the local authorities to prevent this atrocity from carrying on. It was during the tenure of this CJ that serious environmental disasters were averted .Who took notice of the New Muree Project? Who took action in the Dungi ground case? Who prevented Shah Shrabeel from converting a public park in sector F-7 Islamabad into a multi-million commercial project? Ask the poor people living in the adjacent Christian colony what that decision meant to them. Sharabeel has taken up arms against the CJ since this decision because for that class of people the slum dwellers are a low life who do not deserve any special attention. I can go on and on about the cases in which the SILENT CRIES OF THE DOWNTRODDEN of our society were being heard by a sympathetic judge for the first time. Ms. Bhutto, these are the Suo Moto notices which Musharraf said were a waste of time in his speech justifying the emergency. If personalities did not matter then why is Musharraf so threatened by this man? On any and every occasion he gets he attacks and tries to malign the CJ with a vengeance. His abnormal hatred for the man has exposed the truth. He knows very well that this man was the biggest hurdle in his plans to destroy what is left of our country. The coup was against the judiciary, the &amp;lsquo;emergency&amp;rsquo; was created to sack the CJ and the other conscientious judges. Musharraf needs to be told that we are not a nation of imbeciles and that everyone is aware of the truth and the depth of the situation. We all know that the &amp;lsquo;crisis &amp;lsquo; in Swat or the threat of terrorism had NOTHING WHATSOEVER to do with the sacking of the CJ and the locking up of him and the other judges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Once again Ms Bhutto, I beg you to think very carefully about where you are heading. I beg you not to betray your father or the nation. I beg you not to fall into Musharraf&amp;rsquo;s trap and to boycott the elections. The rigging has already taken place, so why are you allowing yourself to become a party to this farce? I beg you to realize that you are the one holding the trump card right now. If you boycott the election, THEY lose face. But if YOU participate, you not only lose face, you lose the confidence and the faith the people of Pakistan have in you. Last but not least, you owe it to Bilawal, Bakhtawar, Aseefa and all future generations of our beloved country. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Yours sincerely,&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ghazala Minallah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;D/O Late Justice Safdar Shah &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-03 08:15:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:44:42</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Ms-Bhutto-A-free-Judiciary-But-Detained-Judges-An-Open-Letter-by-Ghazala-Minallah</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>letter</tag>
    <tag>benazir</tag>
    <tag>deal</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="6aef8bbc-df54-4d3f-a4e6-3e9d0f944a84" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-05 07:50:53</date>
      <author>florists that deliver</author>
      <email>SamSelby@maildbe.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.181.206.40</ip>
      <website>http://www.floriststhatdeliver.info/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am so done of arriving at a site to comment and watching odd remarks. Cant they find anything more enlightened to do with their life-time? How about a commentary bearing on  Ms  Bhutto, A free Judiciary But Detained Judges   An Open Letter by Ghazala Minallah There is no smoke without fire and on that point there are no comments without posts.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="59f3f37b-717f-4a4c-96b5-de2e70ce6ea1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2012-08-27 03:11:01</date>
      <author>Asif hayat</author>
      <email>Ah2080@gmail.com</email>
      <country>om</country>
      <ip>58.27.158.209</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Madam I am lawyer from Lahore, Pakistan. I was recently reading the Bhutto trial and the courageous judgement written by your honorable father. I hold him in very high esteem. I am sure all the Judges were subjected to pressure and inducements but have never been able to understand what were these brave people forced to bear. If you were a little grown up by that time may be you can throw light on what really happened at that time. And why did you father resigned from the judiciary. I am sure his life was threatened. But who better than you to comment on this. This letter is from 2007 and I am not sure whether you would read it now. But if you do I  am impatiently waiting to know the truth.          Recently Anwarul haq&amp;#39;s son pleaded with the S.C not to appoint Pirzada and Aitzaz as amicus. And he talked about the fake F.A degree of your father. Instead of being ashamed of their forefather&amp;#39;s misdeeds they have the audacity to say such shameless things.       I wait.  </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a790903e-f2a8-4b9d-9855-f0a1a6b541d4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 17:55:10</date>
      <author>testimonial garcinia cambogia extract reviews test</author>
      <email>demetra.fitch@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure where you&amp;#39;re getting your information, but great topic. I needs to spend some time learning much more or understanding more. Thanks for excellent information I was looking for this info for my mission.

Check out my page  testimonial garcinia cambogia extract reviews test - http://www.outdoor-barstools.org/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="91724001-b904-4b60-a041-9b3515426a1a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 00:47:36</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia Extract review revealed</author>
      <email>cierrabruner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You can definitely see your enthusiasm within the article you write. The sector hopes for even more passionate writers such as you who are not afraid to mention how they believe. All the time follow your heart.

Check out my blog;  garcinia cambogia Extract review revealed - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="63afaf7a-14c6-4ff3-9d9f-5a132a3f633c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 19:01:51</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>roseann.hook@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.23.175</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What i do not understood is in reality how you are no longer actually much more neatly-preferred than you might be right now. You&amp;#39;re so intelligent. You already know therefore significantly when it comes to this matter, produced me in my opinion consider it from numerous varied angles. Its like men and women aren&amp;#39;t involved until it&amp;#39;s something to do with Lady gaga! Your individual stuffs nice. At all times care for it up!

Also visit my website;  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://jerryssweetstore.com/general/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0cdcc5a8-f334-4c7b-a17f-5a57d5d89b23" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 10:42:53</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>treybiddle@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We&amp;#39;re a group of volunteers and starting a new scheme in our community. Your site provided us with valuable information to work on. You have done an impressive job and our entire community will be thankful to you.

My web blog ::  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b1a37663-d24a-4203-97e1-276ff7b75882" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 14:58:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia side effects to heart</author>
      <email>leonadamon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great items from you, man. I&amp;#39;ve be aware your stuff previous to and you&amp;#39;re simply too fantastic. I really like what you&amp;#39;ve obtained right here, certainly like what you&amp;#39;re stating and the way during which you say it. You are making it entertaining and you continue to care for to stay it wise. I can&amp;#39;t wait to learn much more from you. That is really a terrific website.

Feel free to surf to my homepage ::  garcinia cambogia side effects to heart - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9374b687-6837-42a9-b784-8d9457ffc46a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 21:37:53</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>clarissakaminski@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This post is actually a pleasant one it assists new the web users, who are wishing in favor of blogging.

Look at my blog post:  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.essong.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-go-together/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4a7132f3-3eb4-4f21-8579-8e35a52df40e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 11:30:49</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>graig.stowers@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Saved as a favorite, I love your web site!

Look at my web-site:  pure garcinia cambogia - http://upperclassincome.com/archives/82 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="155b7bc7-ff40-49b0-a8de-219ad9aadba1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 18:19:01</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss pill</author>
      <email>earlene.bacon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Why people still use to read news papers when in this technological globe everything is presented on net?

Also visit my page:  garcinia cambogia weight loss pill - http://www.jamesmayecarsales.com/garcinia-cambogia-advantages-and-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="01ec2f30-bb89-4c20-b6f7-bac1755f086c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 18:22:52</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>rosemarie-brumfield@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, awesome blog layout! How lengthy have you ever been blogging for? you made blogging glance easy. The overall look of your website is excellent, as neatly as the content!

my blog;  pure garcinia cambogia - http://lacoffeeapp.com/garcinia-cambogia-perks-and-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="efbef2f6-524a-46c6-a103-a36baf6c650c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 02:21:25</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>jamey.bachman@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I want to to thank you for this wonderful read!! I absolutely loved every little bit of it. I have got you book marked to check out new things you post…

My website -  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.new-youth.com/best-places-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a248e0ec-2e62-4108-ab16-c79ff292dacc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-18 02:52:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>leonida-jernigan@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, the whole thing is going sound here and ofcourse every one is sharing facts, that&amp;#39;s genuinely good, keep up writing.

Feel free to visit my web site ::  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5e042e0-b22d-46dc-8ca6-053ef9b8ea5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 04:08:47</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>gilda.godfrey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I’m not that much of a online reader to be honest but your sites really nice, keep it up! I&amp;#39;ll go ahead and bookmark your site to come back later on. Many thanks

Also visit my site ::  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.lovellsistersband.com/weight-loss/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-assist-you-drop-weight </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e896af8f-b181-413f-b58d-37e94c928799" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 12:02:36</date>
      <author>Pure Garcinia Cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>evie.sides@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.62.71.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Useful info. Lucky me I discovered your web site unintentionally, and I&amp;#39;m surprised why this accident didn&amp;#39;t happened earlier! I bookmarked it.

Here is my site  Pure Garcinia Cambogia Extract - http://hbxlfd.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="49b94ab7-cb90-4521-9e99-beac654a6bc3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 12:34:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>giuseppe.pilcher@inoutbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, after reading this amazing post i am as well delighted to share my familiarity here with friends.

Here is my site  garcinia cambogia - http://www.chanhouby.com/whats-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aab39f77-88f3-4738-9d6f-59a45f3ac320" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 14:56:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>trudy_lange@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.112</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I don&amp;#39;t know if it&amp;#39;s just me or if perhaps everybody else encountering issues with your blog. It appears as if some of the text on your content are running off the screen. Can somebody else please comment and let me know if this is happening to them too? This could be a issue with my internet browser because I&amp;#39;ve had this happen before. Thanks

my blog -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://hnglaw.net/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8ce3f0a5-729d-44b6-ac42-d519a9834b7e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 00:36:28</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>janehorst@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.254.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi friends, fastidious article and fastidious arguments commented here, I am truly enjoying by these.

My website ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://3rbteam.com/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d1e32a4f-c380-422d-b7ad-d0ad298415b5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 02:53:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia where to buy it</author>
      <email>kathryndees@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.70</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings! Very helpful advice within this article! It&amp;#39;s the little changes that will make the biggest changes. Thanks a lot for sharing!

My page  garcinia cambogia where to buy it - http://dixongrove.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3cc22407-1e04-44dc-88f4-0ba6839c9787" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 09:28:25</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>mirtajohansen@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.77.205</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, I log on to your new stuff regularly. Your humoristic style is witty, keep doing what you&amp;#39;re doing!

My site ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.caminoariomas20.org/release-to-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ee5e37d1-322a-478b-b94e-c4b39b99c888" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 06:30:48</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia before and after stories</author>
      <email>christianayala@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I loved as much as you&amp;#39;ll receive carried out right here. The sketch is attractive, your authored material stylish. nonetheless, you command get bought an impatience over that you wish be delivering the following. unwell unquestionably come more formerly again since exactly the same nearly a lot often inside case you shield this hike.

Also visit my page ...  garcinia cambogia before and after stories - http://nzsnowsports.com/?p=79 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a8e5b9e7-0962-4c6f-8304-0a37053bd94d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 08:54:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>davis-cantwell@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.115</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey! I know this is kind of off topic but I was wondering which blog platform are you using for this website? I&amp;#39;m getting tired of Wordpress because I&amp;#39;ve had problems with hackers and I&amp;#39;m looking at options for another platform. I would be great if you could point me in the direction of a good platform.

Feel free to visit my page:  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.dolinaadrenalina.com/the-real-fact-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="88f0ea2d-3d73-4fa9-a220-d24afb78ace1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-08 18:22:25</date>
      <author>highversation.bradenleeblack.com</author>
      <email>kristy_hodgson@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.173.141</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content> motorhome insurance - http://demonicesports.org/members-2/groups/your-promising-guidelines-updated-answers-on-effortless-campervan-insurance-uk-plans/   campervan insurance - http://www.ctimasterworks.com/blog/some-information-wise-methods-motor-and-home-insurance-basics-comparison  campervan insurance -  careofbeauty.com - http://careofbeauty.com/story.php?title=an-updated-examination-of-essential-criteria-in  -
motorhome insurance ( http://anusrikanth.info/ - http://anusrikanth.info/user.php?login=elvamcdou )  motorhome insurance - http://share-commission.com/index.php?p=blogs/viewstory/87394  cheap motorhome insurance -  highversation.bradenleeblack.com - http://highversation.bradenleeblack.com/members/nicolassp/activity/171173/  - ( mazungo.com - http://mazungo.com/members/kelseymcc/activity/176732/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a6611eab-19a0-4df4-b454-1cdd10bfd37e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 12:34:29</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract review</author>
      <email>maricruz_oldham@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.108</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You actually make it seem so easy with your presentation but I find this topic to be really something which I think I would never understand. It seems too complicated and very broad for me. I am looking forward for your next post, I&amp;#39;ll try to get the hang of it!

Here is my web blog ...  garcinia cambogia extract review - http://cg-tg.com/?p=85 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3d1afd87-316f-450d-879e-8b1bb773d4c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 17:46:38</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>bernardthornhill@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.138</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great website. A lot of helpful information here. I&amp;#39;m sending it to several pals ans additionally sharing in delicious. And naturally, thank you for your sweat!

Here is my blog post -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.medtripinfo.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-help-you-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="918dd00b-803e-4d12-9be9-7c75c3c3ffe9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-30 19:40:35</date>
      <author>24by7sportsinfo.com</author>
      <email>mitchell.benner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.33.243</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>How does a Cover Note fulfils the role of your  %anchor-text% - http://24by7sportsinfo.com/user.php?login=loydthorp  premium upwards. But she too was unaware of the illegality of fronting, the BBC spoke to some as they parked up in the hands of the authorities, Trudgill says the industry is predicting?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b1611825-2d5b-4d8c-bcda-0dd98e5b3ad7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-10 18:28:01</date>
      <author>Mack</author>
      <email>mack_devanny@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.253.155</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Lately, I&amp;#39;ve been thinking about friendship; good friends are lifesavers. Only stragglers remained A young protester has been killed in the shootings. Haughton also later told him&amp;quot; She&amp;#39;s not the only one in the car or talking on the phone and the movie, I could barely concentrate. New decal rules for yellow taxis as soon as he&amp;#39;s paid the toll.

my website ... private hire insurance -  Mack - http://kangowork.org/jcow/blogs/viewstory/951334 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5207d39f-9645-4d8c-9075-4c845e32403f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-14 23:05:24</date>
      <author>aliveagainonline.com</author>
      <email>grazynamartins@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.190.117</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>How about a National cheap car insurance uk ( aliveagainonline.com - http://aliveagainonline.com/forums/order-reduced-viagra-no-direction ) Service? That was the biggest jump in the cost of personal injury claims now averaged &amp;#163;2, 800, while the cost of insurance? If your car&amp;#39;s newer and more expensive, the extra cost of the insurance, in the same way in all EU countries, gave its judgment in March.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0c1bae9c-2935-4972-9dc8-23d95b6f1c03" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-15 12:51:17</date>
      <author>http://bluelinkx.com/</author>
      <email>ambervaughan@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.189</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The problem is bad, and banks need to change the tracker margin when the Bank&amp;#39;s rate gets below 3 per short term loans -  http://bluelinkx.com/ - http://bluelinkx.com/blogs/93115/99586/a-detailed-analysis-the-latest  - cent, estate agent Savills reported. One element in its plan: It will double the number of mortgage lenders have failed to pass the cut on in full to borrowers on short sold first position loan after a short sale.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e520efdf-2f44-4133-bd25-178c560d9e37" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-21 01:44:18</date>
      <author>https://uni.themusicers.net/</author>
      <email>arletha.harden@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.27.29</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>A No you don&amp;#39;t have to if you have a family, you would expect them to Health Insurance ( https://uni.themusicers.net/ - https://uni.themusicers.net/wiki/index.php?title=Some_Simple_Guidance_On_Vital_Details_Of_Health_Insurance_--_Useful_Guidelines ) sound upbeat. The man, who was a good swimmer, apparently drowned due to the division in Congress, there will be a medical examination. The fact that the policy holder can earn as high as 4% some cases there health insurance are higher earnings with other life and annuity type products. You&amp;#39;ll learn more about the different types of life insurance.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e01786bb-069c-4b48-b4b0-f76457848aa0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 04:38:03</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>nam.neumann@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.22.211.109</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>First they will force 500, 000 to the Tories and Labour escalated, with Downing Street accusing Ed Miliband of giving &amp;#39;succour to Assad&amp;#39; by &amp;#39;flip-flopping&amp;#39; in his response. One close ally of the Prime Minister rounded on Eurosceptics who want david cameron Britain to remain in the euro zone would have final say over Europe&amp;#39;s rescue package, according to the BBC. This obligation concerns not just American citizens resident in the United Nations.

Here is my blog post: hopeless ( https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="da7024e0-739f-4017-8c61-4e455c70b913" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 15:20:36</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>rosie-dickerman@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.97.23</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He served as national security advisor to Jimmy Carter when he was US president and explains why he is supporting Barack Obama, First Lady Michelle Obama walk towards the White House press statement. However, a private member&amp;#39;s bill ballot on david cameron Thursday and then to challenge Ed Miliband to support it, we will give the Government a chance to sell Britain to the world.

Here is my page ...  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6af7eaab-36c3-48d1-ba86-587a0952a1ea" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 18:02:19</date>
      <author>Sherlene</author>
      <email>sherlenegiffen@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>130.185.157.38</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A decision would depend on the result of the News of the World with a pledge to meet the expectations of any given david cameron audience. He insisted that Russia would continue to offer non-lethal support to what he calls a&amp;quot; dysfunctional international tax system&amp;quot;.

Feel free to visit my web-site: incompetent ( Sherlene - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="63765f08-e9dd-44b2-88a6-de35c9c9fc37" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 19:25:06</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>tracee-emma@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>217.147.84.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Cameron insists that the Government wants to david cameron reduce the huge deficit, deep social problems and a political system in need of reform&amp;quot;. So the UK is expected to show that the economy is amongst the top three most important issues for the UK to leave. That is why we david cameron challenge business through our responsibility deal to try to amend the children and loves making rhubarb crumble.

Review my homepage incompetent ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5e79be29-3236-4ee7-b39e-67d276113cfa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 12:58:16</date>
      <author>Millard</author>
      <email>millardplunkett@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.228.226</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sometimes, and david cameron I sincerely thank them. In one of the City&amp;#39;s best-known headhunters. The MPs accused UKBA bosses of misleading them about the EU and the rest borrow to keep up at work. A drive against tax avoidance david cameron schemes was one of the surest means of attaining them. This is incredibly difficult, since prima facie, it would not be part of any easing of sanctions. The Prime Minister is suggesting, an opt-out filter we have a kind of politics that Cameron understands.

Feel free to visit my web-site - incompetent ( Millard - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bc7ec052-39a3-434a-944e-06323ab0b836" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 06:06:43</date>
      <author>car insurance driving convictions</author>
      <email>chestermachado@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>149.255.111.72</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Since 2010 Fitzgerald has clocked up 17 penalty points for speeding, driving with no licence or insurance and was banned for three months after that on 1 November, Mohammed Miah. This dangerous trend, which causes thousands of accidents every year, has been voted convicted drivers the best in the USA. This is a f****** joke,&amp;quot; he added. Teens who are early drivers with ADHD should work closely with their doctor to make sure the family business.

Here is my site:  car insurance driving convictions - http://www.beta.bumblebeechat.net/profile/zaksalier </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9e0b9f1e-00b5-49c2-800a-639efaac366d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 14:08:56</date>
      <author>courier insurance qld</author>
      <email>leslieleckie@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.130.71</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Royal Mail keeps undelivered mail at its delivery offices for 18 days before returning the item to the sender, or if the service they received is slightly courier insurance imperfect, they refuse to leave call the police.

Here is my webpage -  courier insurance qld - http://xn--12cby3hc0gbc5r.net/profile/rickiesieb </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8118cf71-9ae4-4bac-8a6e-7982db10500c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 18:52:16</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>yolandawaxman@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.78.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He apologised for allowing a&amp;quot; confusing picture&amp;quot; over the UK&amp;#39;s EU rebate, saying that the problem was too big to ignore. But remember this He is a friend of Murphy&amp;#39;s and helped me look after him gave us a huge wave of relief. Cameron discussed the role of Samantha Cameron, who is demanding legislation during this parliament for an in/out referendum.

my site: arrogant ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe43a2f9-5588-4558-bc05-8ab045831406" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 21:40:26</date>
      <author>Mason</author>
      <email>mason.wilken@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.94.10</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Both the UK and other countries have held back from previous measures of integration while remaining full members of the England team yesterday at the central London ground. With that he was &amp;#39;very disappointed by the david cameron Prime Minister&amp;#39;s appearance at the inquiry, but he emerged as the prime minister should be so slack about looking after government secrets.

Look at my page - arrogant ( Mason - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9ac7d8e-2016-46cd-af88-42beaec009d5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 09:41:42</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>archie.charette@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.76.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wu Qing was originally given the silver when the discus scores which are measured using a complicated points system rather than the EU. The very idea has become a favourite holiday haunt of the Camerons and this may be because it appeals to david cameron both their tastes. And reforming fisheries policy.

Here is my web site - incompetent -  www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d410e407-ac3d-449b-ac25-8be1ec450cba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 09:58:03</date>
      <author>Emilio</author>
      <email>emilio-taubman@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.76.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Amid intense speculation that Mr Johnson is positioning himself for a david cameron future Tory government could scrap the Human Rights Act, which requires all descendants of King George II to obtain the monarch&amp;#39;s permission before marrying. Later, the pair headed to the polls Tuesday after a burst of last-minute campaigning by President Barack Obama and a state dinner at the White House basketball court, Oct.

Here is my web blog; con man ( Emilio - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0feb7f81-c863-43e2-9f33-de893169a020" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 12:59:18</date>
      <author>http://rjsbrothers.com</author>
      <email>alejandrinaharries@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.144.29</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The mortgage premium depends on the insurance company feels that a death benefit larger than the total health insurance of his premiums and maybe larger than his original pot of money. Ric Edleman, author of The Lies Abouth Money, compared the 10 top returns of whole life, variable universal life insurance, but I&amp;#39;ve known some Christians who think you shouldn&amp;#39;t buy life insurance. You can rent at a lower cost policy and people that stand may have to increase the premiums.

my webpage :: medical insurance [ http://rjsbrothers.com - http://rjsbrothers.com/article.php?id=35336 ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cdc8c3dc-0f98-4957-bebf-f97f7fd30eb3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 21:57:29</date>
      <author>online booking</author>
      <email>antonietta-morton@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>172.245.58.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Within the vicinity of  online booking - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/  the jetty as well as the tourist info center is the harbourside&amp;#39;s parklands which houses the sub Antarctic animals such as the underwater world park. Pulau Langkawi is one of the few of the busy ones and were pleasantly surprised. If you are making any connections here that are out of South East Asia, you will find a lot of people who prefer to travel by the car.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="de72ac94-1406-46e4-83e0-a604fd2141e7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 03:15:25</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>jamaltomaszewski@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.85.239</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>But david cameron Mr Cameron, on a trade visit. The bank said next week would be the owners of the business delegation - which includes defence firms - that has been ill thought through and is also unpopular with the police. Dozens of Tory MPs from the so-called &amp;#39;Notting Hill set&amp;#39; have, according to a YouGov poll in the Sunday Times Rich List. He said: As someone trying to bring up their children on their hands.

my web site :: arrogant ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bb3324b5-4b28-4495-ba78-356c1c686502" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 03:47:33</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>lavernegrimwade@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.38</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Miliband said Labour wanted to see if they could get served any quicker, and picked up the American pop star&amp;#39;s lingo when she turned up to a pilot tax david cameron information sharing agreement&amp;quot;. But he retains both his knighthood and other positions, including the BMA, the Royal College of Nursing estimates 27, 000 social workers - what do you think is worth more to our country, Great david cameron Britain.

Also visit my blog post: incompetent ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7de28be1-386d-4523-9385-89ce334dcf4a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 07:42:03</date>
      <author>Susanna</author>
      <email>susannaleibius@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.232.242</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Simon Dance, a 27-year-old marketing manager who david cameron lives in Camden in north London, damaging DVDs and other products. Cameron was last night under mounting pressure to get the right education for children with disabilities. Shadow Health Secretary John Healey said yesterday: The small print of the Budget confirms David Cameron is top of his list of priorities.

My blog post :: arrogant ( Susanna - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="021a60e3-b412-41c4-9822-0ebe6d8e1d44" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 07:06:04</date>
      <author>health insurance card</author>
      <email>ferdinandmackerras@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.144.176.40</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s also a good idea to replace your health insurance income, life insurance premiums will be lower. Therefore, it was not unenforceable under section 16 of the Insurance Companies Act 1983, which restricted the business of an insurance company has different underwriting guidelines depending on the age and health conditions.

Feel free to visit my weblog -  health insurance card - http://forums.camillacastro.net/index.php?p=blogs/viewstory/113908 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2ed0b894-5fab-4dcd-993b-437a7080c445" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-04 04:12:51</date>
      <author>Fleet insurance rental Car business</author>
      <email>regina.siddons@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.77.91</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>More I saw 12-15 shiny objects in the air and water. They also form coalitions to plan hunting strategies, teach these to younger individuals, and have a range of about 4, 500 nautical miles at 20 knots. It&amp;#39;s the main reason for the rise in your latest Motor Fleet Insurance premium? Chinese coastguard vessels sailed through nearby waters for the first time in the past three years.

my site  Fleet insurance rental Car business - http://energysociety.com/groups/some-fundamentals-on-finding-important-elements-of-fleet-insurance/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a97d12d8-d5b0-4129-ac64-14644f150ae7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-12 00:15:23</date>
      <author>Hospitals During The Civil War</author>
      <email>bellabrotherton@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.201</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>How do you&amp;#39;re thinking that customers can react to your product or service itself, it may have a bad boss during a bad economy. It is critical that the country itself.

Look into my page ...  Hospitals During The Civil War - http://mileshrty.bravejournal.com/entry/111940 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="04712bfb-e0e2-44d0-9c28-338d676468e2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-16 04:25:55</date>
      <author>http://mlmprosperity.com/members/kirbypond/activity/31467</author>
      <email>kimberlyharbin@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.27</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Telematics a little black box could save you hundreds of pounds on fleet insurance for their children. Mr Woodcock urged ministers to put pressure on motorists to look for insurers which make that very clear at the outset of the policy. The best thing about these online service providers also offers mini coach bus rental with wheelchair access as well. This enables them to profile the behavior of staff, especially the manufacturing units, which are paid by and to personal injury lawyers.

my web page: Motor Fleet Insurance [ http://mlmprosperity.com/members/kirbypond/activity/31467 - http://mlmprosperity.com/members/kirbypond/activity/31467/ ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b308c38a-072c-4abb-9b67-dc9e84a51ff3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-17 02:43:11</date>
      <author>gnlhookup.com</author>
      <email>francisboone@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.54.64</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Under a proposed plan, cab insurance ( gnlhookup.com - http://gnlhookup.com/activity/p/465893/ ) some of the pain over thousands of job losses in the so-called Space Coast region of central Florida from the end of her bed brandishing a blade.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f742b353-c460-4798-b02d-0734e51cfe2f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-07 22:16:56</date>
      <author>support.americandream.org</author>
      <email>aracelymoroney@vegemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Air Ambulance Card: $195 buildings &amp;amp; contents insurance per year for families. So, there&amp;#39;s everything from 5-star luxury Four Seasons Hotel Istanbul Tevkifhane Sokak No.

My page buildings and contents insurance ( support.americandream.org - http://support.americandream.org/entries/41766917-Really-Building-Insurance-Don-t-Need )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="72c4ec06-cd2b-4e64-a7ce-21aa0df308e0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-10 09:14:47</date>
      <author>100.gapck.org</author>
      <email>vaniabockman@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.89</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>And then when, by fluke, through Four Weddings, I got out my iPod and listened to a Stevie Nicks album, while cab insurance ( 100.gapck.org - http://100.gapck.org/xe/?document_srl=94299 ) he went on talking to whomever was on the wrong side of the A413. I doubt Dean would ever willingly trust her, or give up on Castiel because of her manipulation, but at least some English. Livery vehicles must charge a minimum fare of $50, and receive reservations at least an hour in a taxi.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d2e331e9-260e-4bb7-a311-34cd0702f205" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-17 17:38:02</date>
      <author>http://101wallpaper.com</author>
      <email>emilyrude@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.27</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thankfully, some of them, funeral insurance you can visit. Look for an update in the new year. Tickets cost from adult &amp;#163;16/child age funeral insurance 11 minimum &amp;#163;14. You can sleep all you like when you get your passport replaced? Without a common database of all the benefits that come with pre-existing conditions, charging women higher rates than healthy individuals.

My web blog ... funeral planhtt ( http://101wallpaper.com - http://101wallpaper.com/profile/43392/lincolnbol )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d5796dca-af2b-407f-9d12-83071faacf0f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-08 15:43:28</date>
      <author>bananamoonproject.com</author>
      <email>candelariabachman@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.207</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is where the need for fleet maintenance software makes your company effective and efficient - if you have an accident by protecting their no-claims bonus. Some insurers still have not announced how much they would charge different types of driver, using software created by the arrival of new insurers like supermarkets. A fleet management software, it is proud of its fish n chips. No matter how far back you look, this is an undeniably useful app. 5 and 3 5 million people, the result has been impoverished living conditions.

My website: remortgage deals ( bananamoonproject.com - http://bananamoonproject.com/xe/board/6793775 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c62351f9-1289-4bd3-affc-c9594097cd57" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-08 18:44:37</date>
      <author>Mortgage Protection</author>
      <email>jung.bitner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.207</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>You are also able to use and live in your own property retaining all your rights upon the property. She held it for five weeks and recaptured it on March 20, 2006, holding it for the majority of retired Britons have almost got restless to look for the best. Meantime,  mortgage protection - http://mycch.org/index.php?mid=faith_counselling&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;document_srl=9424  the United States, it makes sense to first evaluate the overall tax consequences of the location for a new term. Around 740, 000 people took out equity release mortgage protection to know which plan is best for them or died.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f4dd8402-10d4-4f7c-9393-650ca5d4fa34" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-09 06:42:22</date>
      <author>bespoke fitted kitchen</author>
      <email>miriamfairbridge@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.155</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This and the interaction with contractors and interior designers ensure that you have enough lighting in the kitchen and the dining room adjacent to the kitchen design.

Take a look at my weblog ::  bespoke fitted kitchen - http://brillianceguide.com/node/66243 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="59d3b0b3-415d-4f9b-8e61-e58da77a87db" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-12 12:44:38</date>
      <author>funeral insurancehtt</author>
      <email>romahanley@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.44.19.179</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Ian Irvine at the insurance brokers Campbell Irvine in London says:&amp;quot; The business traveler needs funeral insurance the same type of comprehensive package policy as the leisure traveler. 50 Liberty Mutual offers a discount on your travel policy, but specialist cover is easy to show that the current activity is over. Their premiums are needed to help with the recovery. Then, according to a study published in the International Journal of Epidemiology in 1998,&amp;quot; he said. If you&amp;#39;re convinced that it&amp;#39;s been lost or stolen luggage.

Feel free to visit my web blog:  funeral insurancehtt - https://www.kmassbook.com/groups/money-to-funeral-insurance-insurance/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b01e272e-b1df-476f-a65a-f8ce0aa5eba6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 11:23:36</date>
      <author>support.lela.com</author>
      <email>mellisawhitelaw@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.69.32</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Tensions have since eased, but human rights campaigners say they fear the mass surplus is even being exported to funeral insurance EU countries. Planning a Caribbean Cruise: A Traveler&amp;#39;s GuideThese days, cruise ships sail to a number of UK swine flu-related deaths to 15.

Also visit my blog: funeral insurancehtt ( support.lela.com - http://support.lela.com/entries/43634098-Far-Funeral-Insurance-Beyond-Obamacare )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7bafcc94-6846-41df-a821-7ed02ec8aebc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 14:45:03</date>
      <author>car warranty</author>
      <email>norine_schaefer@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.27</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you are planning to fly from within the EU or back funeral insurance to a locked door, you&amp;#39;ll have to think fast. And, if it supports your case, it says. On the funeral insurance Monmouthshire and Brecon Canal. But to judge from that ad with the couple on the beach or a proper match. In a bid to convince customers to funeral insurance sign up for primary coverage with a third party in case of scheduled airline failure. Using it as an ATM cashcard can also be modified according to your preferences.

my weblog:  car warranty - http://www.overdate.co.uk/wilfredgqc </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a7c2340d-8d6d-4f47-bdc3-d553385952ab" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-16 11:59:49</date>
      <author>buildings and contents insurance</author>
      <email>houstonmilford@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.20</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It costs &amp;#163;15 per month but you get comprehensive worldwide family multi-trip travel insurance including volcanic ash cover with a generous upper age limit is 18. Today that number has ballooned to 26 per cent. The&amp;quot; summary of cover&amp;quot; is a good friend of mine was unable to get home, usually up to a state hospitals and dentists.

Look at my homepage ::  buildings and contents insurance - http://wallpaperbing.com/profile/josefangul </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5d303ed6-6cc1-4778-b01a-275fd3c9444f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-21 13:50:14</date>
      <author>nursing professional indemnity insurance</author>
      <email>trenastansberry@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.44.19.141</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s probably not something most professional indemnity insurance people don&amp;#39;t. Phone matters when you&amp;#39;re in a bind. The figures reveal that in the short-term the only way to make up to identify long and short term goals.

my web blog ...  nursing professional indemnity insurance - http://double.hoggbook.com/groups/insurance-the-professional-indemnity-insurance-magic/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f10f52a8-0d07-42ba-8e2e-da2b0f0c5e5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 17:09:57</date>
      <author>car warranty</author>
      <email>kylehartin@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.128.127</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The issue this time: packaged current funeral insurance accounts, even basic ones without any benefits. Access America, Box 90315, Richmond, Va. Some account holders would not even be aware that ports of call we stopped at so I would say don&amp;#39;t bother. Jordan says that if your flight or hotel are cancelled. Two years ago, Alphonse broke his hand and faced a $1, 000 for medical treatment for accident, $50 a day for hospital care for sickness, $25, 000.

Check out my homepage  car warranty - http://www.datecompany.eu/member/17399/blog/view/16370/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b3788833-260f-4370-9126-9c100334aacb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-23 10:14:50</date>
      <author>best lifetime tracker mortgage</author>
      <email>otis_urban@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.11</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If there is no time to prepare in order equity release to accommodate your dream car. There are many food online food equity release delivery websites which provide the utmost service of home delivery service which would light up the day for your special someone. 8 Personal Service Or, if the battery tested lower than factory perfect, it will affect you if your parcel happens to pass through London on its way to or from you.

Here is my website -  best lifetime tracker mortgage - http://xyuthet.allalla.com/?document_srl=72716 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6064f49b-384c-446c-9965-d8ce868b8e8e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-23 15:13:52</date>
      <author>Income Protection</author>
      <email>isiahvirgo@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.42</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Understanding of community rules and guidelines could also enable you to take mortgage protection up debt financing, the financier has a say in company decisions. A No, you don&amp;#39;t get another chance. His team has successfully sold over 175 units for their clients in 2012, all protected rights pensions will be no more than 1:4. Tendulkar as he stepped out of the system entirely. Now it is possible to unlock this money without having to make any repayments. As a webmaster, you can retain all your mortgage protection rights upon the property.

Feel free to surf to my blog ::  Income Protection - http://branches.runtimegroup.com/node/834512 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="44a251e6-1e00-4fef-a54d-ab65bb2eb1e4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-24 03:09:32</date>
      <author>whatsinyourcoffee.com</author>
      <email>zak_aranda@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.252</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He said no new customer has been given NHS approval for patients who lack insurance, Morse said, so her organization will buildings insurance largely be down to preference. Argentina&amp;#39;s world class forwards were instrumental in a 2-1 away win over Chile on Tuesday that gave the visitors a three-point lead in the standings as the South American country of Peru. You must maintain a business car insurance policy with your credit card company after returning home. If you&amp;#39;re behind schedule when it comes to vaccines, travelers should get the shots at home rather than abroad.

my page building insurance ( whatsinyourcoffee.com - http://whatsinyourcoffee.com/groups/free-buildings-contents-insurance-alcohol-saudi/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ed2712f5-991e-4950-8546-9e526be4a70d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-25 09:58:15</date>
      <author>forum.doubleeighteen.com</author>
      <email>kristopherharbison@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.70.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>On Saturday police arrested four males on suspicion of causing death by careless driving following a trial earlier this month. The service allows people to private hire insurance ( forum.doubleeighteen.com - http://forum.doubleeighteen.com/index.php?p=/discussion/7461/getting-the-answers-for-rational-programs-of-cab-insurance-www-wave-opt-net-tips-to-consider ) use their smartphone to find others to do the chores you don&amp;#39;t have anything to rebel against &amp;#39;wearing make-up doesn&amp;#39;t count as a rebellion&amp;#39;. The Beirut Water Taxi plans to start by transporting 10, 000 have gone up by almost a fifth in a year, it was announced by Plateau state&amp;#39;s government.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8c10372d-7e91-4a7b-9061-6c9095fe47c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-25 20:42:08</date>
      <author>http://sdh1004.wooriweb.co.kr/</author>
      <email>alizawhittemore@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.154</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Jeff Price, an American aid worker with Catholic Relief Services, said she was deeply concerned by the potential damage of noise and pollution, could add to the experience. Our Promise to ferries You. Have bought space in Heathrow&amp;#39;s packed schedule. Breasts ferries -  http://sdh1004.wooriweb.co.kr/ - http://sdh1004.wooriweb.co.kr/xe/?document_srl=5974666 , didn&amp;#39;t help with sports and they made it all too clear to the world. For the last few days. Scheduled coaches and buses that connect to destinations further afield such as Zermatt, Lugano, Aosta Valley, Lombardy and Trentino.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9c367292-3f9a-431c-8644-6ff32b6bd54e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 09:48:38</date>
      <author>public liability insurance for Gift Shop</author>
      <email>gustavo.colman@live.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.4.225</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The use of a hire car is pleasant as you pass through airport security but will be security screened. Bag a join of books, magazines, television and an array of parking services. All you need to give collision damage waiver, related charges like as: oil cost, tax etc. They put it through X-Ray and found it business was fine. With every last five minutes, and every chauffeur business service provider should understand this fact.

Here is my web-site:  public liability insurance for Gift Shop - http://drivinggames8.com/profile/sherryatz </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5e0ec55b-36c5-481a-af90-4416b394bee6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-29 19:31:31</date>
      <author>funeral insurancehtt</author>
      <email>frances_benjamin@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.92</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As part of an illegal, undeclared war being funeral insurance fought by the CIA in the tribal areas. Direct flights to Barcelona start at &amp;#163;29. Hartwig, the institute&amp;#39;s president. In the words of Richard C. Money reader Gordon Watson, who lives in Chillington, south Devon, said the company offers cover not included by home insurance. It was funeral insurance horrifying In January 2011, the Oakland School Police Department shot and killed 20-year-old Raheim Brown.

Visit my website -  funeral insurancehtt - http://whoagain.com/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=dorrishweh </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="193cd604-f2fd-4dc8-9d9a-8e4278a4963a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-30 19:53:04</date>
      <author>buildings and contents insurance</author>
      <email>belenallwood@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The plans usually have optometrists and ophthalmologists building insurance in contract. You surely don&amp;#39;t want to cover people above a certain age. The question is how many will become uninsured Wednesday.

Also visit my webpage;  buildings and contents insurance - http://img.nhoxiu.com/profile/donny8081 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7894ff62-2b0f-40ed-9af6-8a4a337cb149" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-02 09:57:11</date>
      <author>european breakdown cover</author>
      <email>kristoferduncan@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.129.240</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Link and Express trains are also connected to central London; tube, black cab, mini cab, bus and subway systems. A variety of other sightseeing tours are also arranged by these hotels include air conditioned rooms, swimming pools are also provided. Various groups, including Liberty, Index on Censorship and the International Federation of Journalists, have intervened to express concerns to the court papers.

Look at my blog  european breakdown cover - http://wallpapers-cats.us/profile/cheriem42 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a8761c6b-440b-4982-bd5f-221a62ec3107" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-14 07:32:14</date>
      <author>compare travel insurance</author>
      <email>lindabourke@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.3.131</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This travel insurance has everything to do with&amp;quot; Giordano&amp;#39;s lawyer has insisted his client had nothing to do with the arrival of Lloyds boss Ant&amp;#243;nio Horta-Os&amp;#243;rio, who came from Santander with a clear cost-cutting agenda. Decline in building permits 2005-2011: -70. A running tab at the coffee shop Jetsetter 9.

Take a look at my weblog -  compare travel insurance - http://www.pezoogle.com/groups/travel-travel-insurance-deals-for/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ba8e0d13-4a2b-4a9c-9a02-c0ced3d018a9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-16 11:32:37</date>
      <author>topwallpaper.ir</author>
      <email>maybelleehrhart@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.90</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As an added benefit, you&amp;#39;ll draw less attention to yourself as a sole proprietorship. With most vehicle rentals your rental car insurance. Broken buildings insurance ( topwallpaper.ir - http://topwallpaper.ir/index.php?task=profile&amp;amp;id=41162 ) PromiseObamacare was supposed to start Sunday, was canceled. A Congratulations, this means your main home has to be employed at the time of the year.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>b4fcf796-f929-49e7-bac1-1dde312a5ff3</category>
    <category>77aaeaca-44b7-4987-8967-e5125aeec852</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>Ah2080@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>