<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Dead Man Walking</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 203px; height: 300px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=Mush_in_uniform.jpg" alt="" width="203" height="300" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;There was a story that if you give a razor blade to a non human primate, it would inflict fatal self harm. Our Great leader can accomplish the same with a microphone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Death by Microphone:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Every time the Great Leader talks, he gives himself away. He is relatively better if he is working from a text prepared by someone else. He exhibits his most sublime superficiality if he is being spontaneous, when he is expressing his own thoughts. The recent examples are &amp;lsquo;Q-league will win&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;CJ is scum of the earth&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;It would be nice if you beat up (Ziauddin) on my behalf&amp;rsquo;. &amp;lsquo;Benazir is responsible for her own death&amp;rsquo;. He recently promised the nation, that he would be holding regular weekly press briefings, so that no misunderstandings arose. By not keeping his promise, he has deprived the nation from a great deal of entertainment, and himself from a quick demise. He deliberately uses an affected Punjabi accent, in spite of his Delhi background, to blend in with his predominantly Punjabi constituency of Pakistan army. &lt;em&gt;(Media ko main nay azadi di yay)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The End Game:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Musharraf is now more isolated than he has ever been over the past 8 years. The people have lovingly rubbed the faces of his closest associates in the ground. The army chief has sent clear signals to demonstrate that he wants to extricate the army from the current political mess. This may be a tactical retreat of the snout from the trough, and no doubt they will try to be back again, but it is a retreat nevertheless. Anyway, Musharraf is too much of a baggage for the army to carry, and it is in their interest to dump him as soon as possible. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Americans:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;If you read between the lines of the &amp;lsquo;statements of support&amp;rsquo;, you will note that the Americans are trying to carefully distance themselves from Musharraf. They are emphasizing the role of Musharraf in holding &amp;lsquo;free and fair elections&amp;rsquo;, reiterating &amp;lsquo;respect for the people&amp;rsquo;s choice&amp;rsquo; and their desire for &amp;lsquo;continued co-operation&amp;rsquo;. They are taking credit for asking Musharraf to give up his army chief role, and ending the Emergency. In the meanwhile, they are cultivating Kiyani, and trying to ensure, that he will continue to do their bidding once Musharraf is gone. It is likely that the Americans have worked on this strategy since the end of last year, when Musharraf became increasingly unstable. It is not possible for the Americans to openly ditch Musharraf, because of the domestic fallout that the Bush administration will have to face, when they are accused of having their Pakistan policy in tatters. The shenanigans of the American officials in Pakistan after the elections, have been seen in Pakistan as blatant interference, and naked imperialism; and have done nothing to advance the American interests, but then they are probably playing to a domestic gallery and not for their national interests. I think they know that Musharraf is beyond salvage, and they are trying to ease the impact, by slowing down his departure, an exercise in damage control. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The New Parliament:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;By giving mixed signals on the judiciary, and talking of a working relationship with Musharraf, Zardari is falling into the same trap, that Benazir fell into last year: throwing a lifeline to a drowning Musharraf and damaging his own standing. Her motivation probably was to have her corruption charges removed. Zardari may be amenable to the same manipulation. What he should realise is that there has been a sea change in the political climate after 27&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of December and after 18&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of February. He holds all the cards. It is much better that he takes the risk of&amp;nbsp; the NRO, challenged in the restored Supreme Court, than to cohabit with Musharraf and risk splitting his party and giving the political initiative to Nawaz Sharif. At the moment he is in such an ideal bargaining position, that he can dictate his terms even to the Americans. Nawaz Sharif has been on the other hand, has been much more astute in reading the people&amp;rsquo;s mood, and brought about a complete transformation in the fortunes of his party. Whereas the people&amp;rsquo;s party politicians are using weasel words and doublespeak to be able to defer challenging Musharraf, the PMLN politicians are coming across as earnest and straight talking. Remember: you can not fool the people, remember Durrani &lt;em&gt;(Ghalat Bayani)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Judiciary: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In spite of the frenetic efforts of the establishment to cultivate a split in the lawyer&amp;rsquo;s movement, they are likely to win in the near future. The time is now to strike the final blow. Aitazaz&amp;rsquo;s call for a long march on the 9&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of March was a master stroke; it has been undermined by the stupidity of Asma Jehangir and Justice Tariq Mahmood. The lawyers won last year not because of the action of the Supreme Court, but because a massive uprising, due to their own campaign. Otherwise the Supreme Court would have wilted before a brutal military regime, as it has done throughout its history. To ask for more time for the parliament to bed in is a mistake; it will bed in much better if there are millions of people on the streets to support it. Aitazaz, by deferring to the sentiments of some of his colleagues, has postponed his long march, again it shows the kind of genius he is. Now the People&amp;rsquo;s Party have the suddenly the ball in their court, and unless they deliver quickly, they will be shown up to be collaborators and not revolutionaries that they claim to be. The movement will not be reversed. How long can the judges be held prisoner? How long can Aitazaz Ahsan and Ali Ahmad Kurd remain under house arrest? When they are out marching tomorrow, and joined by the people in their millions, who will stop them? The Punjab Government headed by Shehbaz Sharif? or the federal Government headed by Amin Faheem? Who will wield the truncheons? who will fire the tear gas? Who will be the plain clothes thugs beating up the demonstrators? Will it be the Punjab Police or will it be the Pakistan Army? or will it be the goons of MQM?&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Media:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The banished media men and women are emerging from the shadows. The blaze of media exposure is deadly for the ghouls like Musharraf and his stooges. It has been refuelled and reinvigorated by their recent struggle against dictatorship and burns much brighter. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Musharraf is dead. He is just waiting to be buried. The whole world knows it. Even his best mate George Brain-dead Bush. It is time someone told him as well. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;by &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="arial,helvetica,sans-serif" size="2"&gt;Please leave a comment below, also see:&lt;/font&gt; &lt;span style="font-size: 11pt; font-family: Verdana"&gt;&lt;a href="/JDP/post/2008/02/The-People-Have-Spoken.aspx"&gt;&lt;span class="Hyperlink1"&gt;&lt;font color="#000000"&gt;The People Have Spoken&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span style="font-size: 11pt; font-family: Verdana"&gt;&lt;a href="/JDP/post/2007/12/Extraordinary-Rendition-III.aspx"&gt;&lt;span class="Hyperlink1"&gt;&lt;font color="#000000"&gt;In The Beginning There Was The Gun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-02-27 18:31:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 21:33:48</lastModified>
  <raters>6</raters>
  <rating>4.166667</rating>
  <slug>Dead-Man-Walking</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="9d199c18-7ca3-4855-8668-a6a4355814f8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-12 16:55:12</date>
      <author>Mutuelle</author>
      <email>assursante2@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>196.217.58.158</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very good data, I’m always mastering something new, and invest a lot of time reading through articles lately.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0b4be9e1-311c-4878-8980-e4bc362e41ec" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-12 16:58:30</date>
      <author>Mutuelle</author>
      <email>assursante2@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>196.217.58.158</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very good data, I’m always mastering something new, and invest a lot of time reading through articles lately.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e0dc48d2-8c0f-453c-a5e4-fe4eca894f80" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 12:42:44</date>
      <author>body revolution</author>
      <email>michel.mcgrew@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This paragraph is actually a nice one it assists new web viewers, who are wishing for blogging.

Take a look at my web page ...  body revolution - http://www.fatburningblogger.info/fitness/dr-travis-and-jillians-pull-up-challenge-movie/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f30341d0-0bca-40fc-b845-8f1e66cd7f08" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 04:22:16</date>
      <author>body revolution review</author>
      <email>philiparnold@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello it&amp;#39;s me, I am also visiting this web site daily, this web page is actually pleasant and the people are truly sharing pleasant thoughts.

Here is my homepage -  body revolution review - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="86be1533-2b38-4773-8baf-56317562d9d6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-16 21:25:51</date>
      <author>Jean</author>
      <email>jeancallaway@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>46.4.227.130</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>You need to be a part of a contest for one of the highest quality websites on the internet. I will highly recommend this site!

Feel free to surf to my weblog - conseils en referencement ( Jean - http://mcg.ustc.edu.cn/sdap1/spermgenes/comments/?page_id=5897 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f06d3f19-3a0e-459a-9d92-666735e65252" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-16 23:51:11</date>
      <author>Nelle</author>
      <email>nelle_trinidad@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.39.121.113</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>A fascinating discussion is worth comment. I do think that you ought to write more on this subject matter, it may not be a taboo matter but generally people don&amp;#39;t talk about these subjects. To the next! Many thanks!!

Feel free to surf to my blog post referencement gratuit,  Nelle - http://de.ekopedia.org/Look_for_Engine_Optimization:_How_To_Drive_Internet_site_Site_visitors_To_You ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b6875c89-b56c-474c-aed1-1c363e7bbb59" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-12 00:10:18</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>lemuel.patton@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.227.62</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thirty-three percent of  homepage - http://ceunsik74.cafe24.com/xe/?document_srl=46490  shoppers obtained three price quotes and 26% obtained four or more.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="404f6b01-cc87-4493-9f0c-000d37cc9fb5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 18:52:01</date>
      <author>incompetence</author>
      <email>tillylonsdale@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.130.76</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Cameron, who said after the vote: We care about what the UK thinks. But the NHS Confederation&amp;#39;s acting chief executive Nigel Edwards warned Mr Cameron to scrap the special protection for health, schools and overseas aid. So this G8 will be no escaping this decision, no &amp;#39;remind me later&amp;#39; and then it never gets done. At Carlton, Cameron played up to the boundary of the premises.

My web-site  incompetence - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="20b2cd28-0da9-4456-9529-a7cc350ef5cf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-08 02:50:48</date>
      <author>http://blog.hotelsuggest.com/uncategorized/challenging-strategies-an-intro-to-convenient-fitted-kitchens-secrets</author>
      <email>patrice-wheelwright@whale-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.130.71</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Look for good quality names like FireKing, and kitchen ideas Fenton on your products. This information might assist you when you decide to make another series of kitchen designs available from the Internet Kitchen Company and their families or households are not eligible to enter.

Review my blog :: cheap kitchens ( http://blog.hotelsuggest.com/uncategorized/challenging-strategies-an-intro-to-convenient-fitted-kitchens-secrets - http://blog.hotelsuggest.com/uncategorized/challenging-strategies-an-intro-to-convenient-fitted-kitchens-secrets/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="95b11bd9-a0ad-4f4d-80bd-c84b8cb3d381" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-11 20:34:46</date>
      <author>tosutah.com</author>
      <email>brandiebreillat@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.59.115</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Photo by Chad Buchanan/Getty Images for LMVHHOLLYWOOD - JUNE 26: Former Miss USA Kenya Moore arrives at the 2008 BET Awards held landlords insurance -  tosutah.com - http://www.tosutah.com/privateforum/profile/GretchenP  - at the ArcLight Cinemas on October 23, 2012 in Los Angeles, California. The Government has addressed the issue of the identity of the landlord as well as their jobs.
 landlords insurance - http://www.myriapulse.com/wiki/A_Helping_Hand_With_Smart_Solutions_Of_landlord_insurance_mouse_click_the_next_article   cheap landlord insurance - http://www.pneumounder40.org/blog/2014-01-22/emerging-challenges-primary-issues-landlords-insurance-couple-simple-information   landlords insurance - http://www.con-news.com/consuite/profile/EileenHar </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e4a68f4f-8a61-4d1a-b10f-6289dff8bbbd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-04 17:04:54</date>
      <author>Joe Pantel</author>
      <email>israelfosdick@wildmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.171.236.246</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you a lot for sharing this with all people you really know what you&amp;#39;re talking approximately! Bookmarked. Kindly additionally seek advice from my site =). We will have a link alternate agreement between us!

Feel free to visit my weblog ::  Cash&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Joe Pantel - http://www.gipsys.de/index.php?option=com_phocaguestbook&amp;amp;view=phocaguestbook&amp;amp;id=1&amp;amp;Itemid=54 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dc1fd3a3-33db-4ec9-bc8f-80b694033858" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-11 23:14:08</date>
      <author>http://toboganium.com</author>
      <email>johnny.carroll@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.95.106.219</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>As a Green Keeper on a golf course, and landscaper with experience, I&amp;#39;m asked, continually, for help with people&amp;#39;s gardens. You may want to include a vegetable garden in your landscaping plan. A landscape designer knows where to place the flowers for greater effect and what plants to seed.

My blog landscaping ideas for front of house -  http://toboganium.com - http://toboganium.com ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6518abe8-8a31-474c-94c3-09b3c535f8f7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-26 11:21:23</date>
      <author>Jennifer</author>
      <email>huberthallowell@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.79.127</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The truth is that the job isn&amp;#39;t as predictable as it may sound. For the homeowner, recycled plastic paving stones offer several benefits. Consequently, individuals have two choices: They can bite the bullet and pay whatever it takes to get their front yard up to snuff, or they can see if they can do some or all of the work themselves.

My web page; toboganium.com [ Jennifer - http://toboganium.com ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="21298ca3-71bf-40b2-b2ac-d04d8c904ea9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-05 02:52:31</date>
      <author>google plus age restriction</author>
      <email>windyaguiar@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.94.99.38</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is very attention-grabbing, You&amp;#39;re a very professional blogger. I&amp;#39;ve joined your feed and sit up for in search of more of your great post. Additionally, I have shared your web site in my social networks

my blog post ...  google plus age restriction - http://www.lmgtfy.com/?q=ajax+google+apis </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b7939c9e-088d-42f6-b33d-cae4afce3649" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-05 04:24:14</date>
      <author>toboganium.com</author>
      <email>mablemcburney@your-mail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>104.140.210.220</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>• Three simple steps that will help you determine the best dimensions for the backyard patio. Had you always been thinking to upgrade the pavers of the patio. Chances are you rent or lease the property upon which your business is located, and really have no idea about the types of trees and shrubs that are planted and why they are planted where they are.

Feel free to visit my website; simple landscaping ideas ( toboganium.com - http://toboganium.com )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e9713365-cd9b-46d7-adeb-54711f4830b8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-08 13:54:44</date>
      <author>frontyard landscaping ideas</author>
      <email>harveyoloughlin@t-online.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>66.118.156.234</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>• Three simple steps that will help you determine the best dimensions for the backyard patio. Anytime you are considering changing your landscape, you must also thing about the structures that already stand on your property. Chances are you rent or lease the property upon which your business is located, and really have no idea about the types of trees and shrubs that are planted and why they are planted where they are.

My blog post ...  frontyard landscaping ideas - http://toboganium.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c81accbe-14ab-486c-9559-c207c5e7fe85" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-02-12 19:56:45</date>
      <author>Tampa bay Painter</author>
      <email>pete.mcclure@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.94.99.19</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, I believe your web site may be having browser compatibility problems. Whenever I take a look at your website in Safari, it looks fine however, if opening in IE, it&amp;#39;s got some overlapping issues. I simply wanted to provide you with a quick heads up! Besides that, great site!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="779f57ce-e41b-409e-8cf0-a3b9c620ba77" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-15 10:51:37</date>
      <author>slimming capsules from china</author>
      <email>marceltancred@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.46.86.244</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Stacker fat burners could cause the tiny muscle tissues in artery walls to thicken, lowering the area out there for blood to move by way of.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b6d4ba32-6f41-4da7-b761-5aded24e86d3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-19 14:41:52</date>
      <author>slimming world magazine</author>
      <email>mariannedostie@hotmail.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.44.79.130</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Though ephedra has a protracted, tried and examined historical past as a standard drugs, it is equally unsafe if consumed without session.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="47599faf-206e-422e-8bc8-5d5885f8c544" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-03 07:06:44</date>
      <author>verifying address</author>
      <email>tabathanewling@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>83.234.49.38</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Your style is so unique compared to other people I&amp;#39;ve read stuff from. Thanks for posting when you&amp;#39;ve got the opportunity, Guess I&amp;#39;ll just bookmark this web site.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7048c0da-da5e-472e-99cc-7f573f3c6106" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-07 13:25:53</date>
      <author>slimming world hi fi bars</author>
      <email>briannakinchen@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>37.230.212.180</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I had my first Slim Quick at midday, whereas by that time I should&amp;#39;ve been consuming my second Slim Quick.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2f394b96-c488-4c4d-9310-78550834e1b3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-11 12:42:34</date>
      <author>Valerie</author>
      <email>luisaalleyne@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>37.106.200.20</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up this is kind of of off topic but I was wanting to know if blogs use WYSIWYG editors or if you have to manually code with HTML. I&amp;#39;m starting a blog soon but have no coding experience so I wanted to get advice from someone with experience. Any help would be greatly appreciated!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6e0e86e4-fe2c-465d-b163-d42e6b7fa804" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-16 20:19:58</date>
      <author>slimming legs fast</author>
      <email>danafouch@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.44.78.75</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The majority of those fat burners include horrifying facade effects on the human physique.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84422d5d-8c8a-40f4-9284-35d48d1ba805" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-19 14:51:43</date>
      <author>juggernaut airsoft armor</author>
      <email>kellee_grills@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>213.184.111.172</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nearly all of today&amp;#39;s Desert Eagle Airsoft gun replicas are engaging and can be very addictive. This type of gun holds utmost importance for airsoft enthusiasts and they make the most use of it in their respective game purposes including target hunting game. Todays market offers endless sea of acessiores and upgrades for your rifle. I had lost trust in Ray Ewer who had poorly represented me in the Newton flooding incident. Airsoft rifle tends to be very useful and productive because of easy operational mechanism attached with the weapon.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e18774b8-c6da-46a1-b12a-5372131597b3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-07-11 23:22:22</date>
      <author>verify email account</author>
      <email>abbybegley@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.120.163.88</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Subscribe for free email validation API   here -  http://bit.ly/1G4sTfE  and procure 500 credits that you could implement in web or desktop application or this 100 % free JAVA based application   here - http://bit.ly/1JKU86K   to verify and scrub your e-mail</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9c1e29f5-2fce-4f24-8efa-1bb429b71ff2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-19 10:01:27</date>
      <author>John Mueller</author>
      <email>jeannahailes@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>158.222.5.144</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Cialis is used to deal with erectile dysfunction and the indicators and signs of benign prostatic hyperplasia. Underneath the model identify Adcirca, it is usually used to deal with pulmonary arterial hypertension.   Levitra can also be used to deal with erectile dysfunction.  In the next video, Dr. David Samadi from Mt. Sinai hospital explains how erectile dysfunction can sign different well being issues and the way Cialis, Levitra and Viagra work:   Cialis might be taken with or with out meals as wanted, instantly earlier than sexual exercise. The 10mg tablets needs to be swallowed complete and never greater than as soon as per day. Cialis can also be out there in 2.5mg tablets which are taken day by day.   Levitra might be taken with or with out meals. It&amp;#39;s taken as wanted in 10mg tablets about 60 minutes earlier than sexual exercise. It shouldn&amp;#39;t be taken greater than as soon as each 24 hours. Sexual stimulation is requirement for response to therapy.   Common unintended effects of Cialis embody warmth or redness in face, neck or chest, chilly signs equivalent to stuffy nostril, sneezing or sore throat, headache, reminiscence issues, diarrhea, upset stomach, muscle ache and again ache.   Common unwanted side effects of Levitra embody warmth or redness in face, neck or chest, runny or stuffy nostril, headache, dizziness, upset stomach and again ache.   Overdose signs  Cialis overdose signs embrace chest ache, nausea, irregular heartbeat and feeling gentle-headed or fainting.   Overdose on Levitra might result in again ache, muscle ache or imaginative and prescient issues.  Cialis and Levitra shouldn&amp;#39;t be mixed with any nitrate drug for chest ache or coronary heart issues. It is best to inform your physician earlier than speaking these medicine you probably have coronary heart illness, excessive or low blood strain, seizures, liver or kidney illness, a blood cell or bleeding disorder, a stomach ulcer, listening to or imaginative and prescient issues, a watch disorder or bodily deformity of the penis.   Studies on Cialis counsel that it&amp;#39;s efficient 88% of the time. For patients with diabetes, it&amp;#39;s efficient fifty six% of the time. [1]   Initial research on Levitra recommended that it was efficient between seventy four% and 87% of the time. It&amp;#39;s much less efficient for males with hypertension, dyslipidaemia or diabetes.[2]   Prescription  Cialis is the one erectile dysfunction drug that may be prescribed as a as soon as-every day pill. It&amp;#39;s also efficient for longer – as much as 36 hours. It is usually used to deal with pulmonary arterial hypertension. It&amp;#39;s preferable for individuals with tachycardia because it doesn&amp;#39;t have an effect on the guts in the identical method as Levitra.  Look into my web page  John Mueller - http://www.buyviagraonlinenow.com/canada/buy-viagra-canada/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="59e1a0a4-f430-4ea0-bd21-48d658bd456b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-20 08:47:31</date>
      <author>Ian Read</author>
      <email>rodgerdacomb@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>138.128.229.131</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sexual dysfunction comes in lots of kinds and might have an effect on each women and men. Study sexual dysfunction and sustaining sexual well being.   Featured Horny Goat Weed: Extra Than simply a reputation  Behind the humorous identify of horny goat weed stands a time-examined aphrodisiac that will increase libido in women and men, and improves erectile operate in males.   Is Licorice the Lady&amp;#39;s Viagra?  The most potent aroma confirmed to stimulate ladies is not males&amp;#39;s cologne and even champagne; it is truly the all-pure scent of licorice. See extra &amp;#187;   Natural Male Enhancements that actually Work (Plus These That do not)  Our Inexperienced Intercourse columnist ask what each man needs to know, however none dares ask: Does pure male enhancement actually exist? Study extra about natrual made enhancements that actually work. See extra &amp;#187;   Viagra Options: 5 Myths About Pure Male Enhancement Aids  Do pure male enhancement aids actually work? Try the 5 myths about pure male enhancement aids in this text by HowStuffWorks.com. See extra &amp;#187;   Sexual Ache Disorders: Causes and Remedies  What are the causes and therapies of sexual ache disorder? Be taught concerning the causes and therapies of sexual ache disorder. See extra &amp;#187;   1zero Unusual Sexual Circumstances  Unusual sexual circumstances can hinder and take over an individual&amp;#39;s regular life. Study unusual sexual situations. See extra &amp;#187;   5 Suggestions for Enhancing Feminine Libido  Low libido or intercourse drive is a typical complaint amongst ladies of all ages. Study in regards to the causes and remedy of low libido. See extra &amp;#187;   Asexual Habits  What is the definition of asexual habits? Study asexual conduct in people and different organisms. See extra &amp;#187;   Dyspareunia  What is the definition of dyspareunia? Find out about how painful intercourse, also called dyspareunia, can have an effect on an individual&amp;#39;s sexual well being. See extra &amp;#187;   Impotence  What is the definition of impotence? Find out how impotence impacts males, each bodily and psychologically. See extra &amp;#187;   Incest  What is the definition of incest? Be taught concerning the well being dangers and social taboos related to incest.  My web site:  Ian Read - http://www.buyviagraonlinenow.com/buyviagraonline/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e17c0246-a910-410a-b050-6a08f8e19763" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-20 14:47:46</date>
      <author>Aura Mins</author>
      <email>rodrigoniland@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>138.128.227.2</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>HubPages&amp;#187; Health&amp;#187; Males&amp;#39;s Well being we want to have the ability to let our physique loosen up and relaxation for good well being. Tension prevents this from taking place because it limits blood circulate to the areas of the physique that want blood stream to provide males a wholesome exhausting erection. Restricted blood circulation additionally impacts many different areas of the physique, however we&amp;#39;re right here to debate one explicit side.   Sure, you possibly can go see your physician, and if you’re in good well being, you will get a prescription to purchase the well-known little blue pill Viagra, and away you go. However there are different medicine free strategies that may have very related results which are simpler on the wallet, much less time consuming, and superb for you. And these strategies will clearly produce other advantages in addition to they&amp;#39;re all pure.   Watermelon Apart from being scrumptious, watermelon is chalked for of citrulline which is understood to calm down and dilate blood vessels which is just about what Viagra and different ED medication do. So as a substitute of heading to the physician, wander over to your native grocery retailer and seize a watermelon. Attempt to eat a quarter of it to get the maxim profit for a couple of days and watch the pure means begin to take impact. You can too drop the pink a part of the melon (ideally chilly) with out the seeds right into a blender for a scrumptious and refreshing drink!   Pomegranate This fruit additionally has different attributes apart from being scrumptious. Pomegranates are loaded with anti oxidants, so whereas it’s serving to clear your blood of toxic waste, it additionally raises different parts in your blood which relaxes your blood vessel partitions rising blood circulation in your physique and extra importantly to your penis. Haven’t been strolling up with the morning &amp;quot;woody&amp;quot; recently, see what these two fantastic fruits can do for you and enable you that morning erection again, which is a superb signal for wholesome blood circulate. So gentlemen, time to both go procuring, or add these things to the grocery checklist. Possibly they&amp;#39;re already within the home for the household, so dig in and get pleasure from!   KegelExercises  Not an enormous fruit eater? Effectively there may be one thing else, the Kegel train. This was initially designed for pregnant girls to assist with the birthing course of, effectively guess what? In additionally helps with the erection course of, who would have thought? Do a easy seek for &amp;quot;Kegel workout routines for Erectile Dysfunction&amp;quot; and one can find allot of nice assets about them. It was in all probability found whereas males have been doing this train with their companions in a help class. Strengthening the muscles in any a part of your physique will increase blood movement to these muscles, so specializing in the muscles in your groin space goes to extend blood movement to your penis. Hey, isn’t that what Viagra and different ED meds do?   Tright here you could have it. Have to get a few of that misplaced vitality again? Effectively listed here are some options to assist, all simple to acquire or do. And if you’re blissful in your love life you’ll be completely happy in the opposite points of your life too, reducing your total stress, and bettering your general well being. Because of this, life generally begins that upward spiral to happiness in all elements of your life.   Wait, was somebody speaking about well being care?  Resources: Medication.com Edguider.com Webmd.com   Related Chronic Ache Relief &amp;amp; TreatmentsAlternative Remedies for Chronic Fatigue Syndrome by Melissa Flagg22   HealthCan Turkey Tail Mushroom Struggle Most cancers? by ologsinquito7  sendingBkCreative 7 years in the past from Brooklyn, New York Metropolis   edguider - I simply love the images right here! They obtained on to the purpose.  I&amp;#39;ve heard nice issues about watermelon for ED. I am a girl however I can actually share this with some males folks.   Great begin! Nice hub! Thanks!  Authoredguider 7 years in the past   Thanks BkCreative, glad you preferred it :)  prasetio30 7 years in the past from malang-indonesia   nice suggestions. I will bookmark this one.  Coming out with a brand new one prasetio, test it out subsequent week   Thanks for doing the work to get the info as that is significantly better than the fast and straightforward pill which can trigger points in different regards not addressing the true problems with ID this data, three Pure Various Remedies For Males With Erectile Dysfunction addresses the wholesome choices. :)   Thanks Katie, glad you prefer it. They&amp;#39;re so many pure cures on the market, more often than not we don&amp;#39;t want pills   Debra Allen 6 years in the past from West By God  I like this text and the good info. Pure is all the time the most effective. I&amp;#39;ll move this alongside.   Thanks Lady Guinevere, glad you appreciated it.  chamilj 6 years in the past from Sri Lanka   I suppose everybody like pure method. Helpful Hub. Thanks sharing.  Hariom three years in the past from INDIA (Haryana) SAMPLA   Useful hub.Pure remedy all the time extra helpful. Drugs have facet impact however pure therapy no facet impact.   A very helpful house cures for sexual energy is  5 ml. onion juice+5 ml. ginger juice+5 ml. honey+2 gms. pure ghee/butter   take this each day.this recipe increase sexual energy and enhance well being.  Otniel 2 years in the past   I respect your variety and gnroeues recommendation lots!. I&amp;#39;ve been making an attempt it hardly and didn&amp;#39;t get these superb outcomes!. It&amp;#39;s good to see that you bought my remark in a great way!God bless you!VA:F [1.9.10_1130]please wait VA:F [1.9.10_1130](from zero votes)   Aslam mohd 2 years in the past  Good different.  Visit my homepage:  Aura Mins - http://www.buyviagraonlinenow.com/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>222c72c1-f8ad-4bc7-abda-823e95a8c9f7</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>