<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Tuzk e Jahangiri</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2008%2f11%2f610x_edited.jpg" alt="" width="147" height="152" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Laddies and Gentlemen, Jiyalas and Jiyalis whether Urdu Medium or English Medium, please accept my salama laikum. I must pologise to my readers for the lang absence. I pramise to be more regular in future. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Secondly I cangratulate JDP on its first birthday paty, on behalf of Pakistan Peepal Paty. Slowly slowly, their efforts will bring fruit. Justuce will be restored in Pakistan. Chief Justuce will not be restored in Pakistan, but he will be honoured in Mreeka. Itzasab will be honoured in Cambridge and Kurd Saab will be honoured in Kurdistan.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I am writing to you fram Muzaffara Bad. This is the capital of the gormint of Zad Kashmir. We are having a paty meetung. There are lats of jiyalas here and some jiyalis. Some of them sapeak Pahari. Some of them sapeak Urdu. Not many of them sapeak Ingulsh like me, but education is suppredding slowly slowly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Education is impatant. Sheed Chairman Bhutto was highly educated but he was killed by Journal Zia. Sheed Mohtarma was highly educated and she was killed by terrorists. Thanks God I am still alive. This is what I have told the paty in Zad Kashmir and they are also saying thanks God. On the other hand, the Shriek Chairman is not so highly educated, but he can count up to ten. This is impatant to get a ten percent share for building a stronger damo cracy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;There is a prablem. The members in Zad Kashmir fat all the tam. I told them if you were fatting inside occupied Kashmir, Kashmir would be free by naoo. They are complaining, that Shriek Chairman says, who who is fatting the Indian army is&amp;nbsp; terrorist and they are not happy. I said they are casting votes under control of an occupying army, and their votes won&amp;rsquo;t change anything. They are saying it is same to same in Pakistan, so why bather? To be hanest, I am sick and tired of this discussion, so I have said the whole Zad Kashmir paty is dismiss. After all, I am the secty journal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Then there is the prablem of drones. The media is making hue and cry all the time. I am asking them, are you the maternal uncles? It is faran planes, faran missiles, killing farners. Why are you frying your pan cakes in the middle? It is only eight days from Friday to Friday, since the damo cracy was restored. Do you want the fauj back? Do you want me to be hanging upside down in the Shahi Qila again? It is time they shut up and left big deciyuns to big people like me.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;This country will pragress according to the viyyun of Sheed Bhutto, Sheed Mohtarma, Kaiday Yazam, Lama Qbal and Haji Fazal Din, under the guidance of Shriek Chairman. Af course you will always find me at the fore front of suttruggle for damo cracy as secty journal of the paty.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Long live Peepal Paty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="/JDP/search.aspx?q=hazik&amp;amp;page=1"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2" color="#000080"&gt;More articles by &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-11-25 14:34:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-11-26 15:51:33</lastModified>
  <raters>5</raters>
  <rating>4.2</rating>
  <slug>Tuzk-e-Jahangiri</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>