<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Chief Justice Gets Medal of Freedom</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2008%2f11%2fCJ_more_flowers1.jpg" alt="" width="215" height="291" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
TEXT OF THE SPEECH BY&amp;nbsp; CHIEF JUSTICE&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Madam President,&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Distinguished ladies and gentlemen:&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;It is a singular honour to be awarded the Harvard Law School Association&amp;rsquo;s Medal of Freedom on behalf of 170 million Pakistanis who continue to stand for rule of law, independence of the judiciary, equality, freedom and justice for all.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;[more]&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;This the 19th day of November, and I stand 10,816 km from my hometown. I stand in one of this planet&amp;rsquo;s largest reservoirs of law: America&amp;rsquo;s oldest law school. And I stand here as a humble representative of all those Pakistanis who continue to defy autocracy, repression and oppression in all their forms.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I stand here for all those Pakistanis who have risen against despotism, dictatorship, brutality, tyranny and injustice. I also stand here for all those Pakistanis who stand for the principle that no one is above the law and all those Pakistanis who agree with Thomas Paine that &amp;ldquo;in absolute governments the king is law, so in free countries the law ought to be king; and there ought to be no other.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The power to issue the writ of habeas corpus was exercised with dramatic effect by Lord Chief Justice Edward Coke 8 decades before the English Courts guaranteed the subject of the Crown the right of vote in 1704 in the case of Ashbey Vs. White. It was also three hundred years before full adult franchise was granted to all in England.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;For the record, the Act of Settlement, that institutionalized a guaranteed security of tenure came in 1701 some 86 years prior to the Grand Convention at Philadelphia, the Convention that gave birth to a Constitutional Democracy in this country. In other words, judicial independence preceded constitutional democracy by more than 8 decades.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Intriguingly, Pakistani autocrats, whether uniformed or otherwise, are trying to turn the wheels of history in the wrong direction. Our autocrats, whether uniformed or otherwise, while decreeing a democratic order are, at the same time, postponing the establishment of an independent judiciary to an ever more distant future. Such democracy is bound to fail; you can&amp;rsquo;t have a constitutional democracy without security of tenure for the judges.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Imagine; 307 years ago, King William III was cornered into signing the Act of Settlement which &amp;ldquo;established tenure for judges unless Parliament removed them.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Three hundred years thence, Pakistani lawyers are now struggling to keep their autocrats, military as well as democratic, from influencing judges. The campaign underway is truly, truly unique. To begin with, the campaigners&amp;mdash;devoting time, effort and risking life and limb&amp;mdash;seek neither any office nor power. A hundred thousand intellectuals lawyer&amp;rsquo; at two in the morning, thousands getting burnt by the cruel sub-continental sun, hordes waiting in rain drowning a Chief Justice&amp;rsquo;s car in rose petals are all things neither Pakistani nor something that the Third World has ever witnessed. Unprecedented and without any equal in human history, the whole movement is about three things: principles, principles and principles.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;On March 9, the debate was all about the action against me alone through the Presidential Reference or indictment. No more. The indictment or charge sheet was thrown out and trashed by the verdict of 13 senior judges of the Supreme Court including those who would profit by my removal. The struggle now is all about &amp;ldquo;Trias Politica&amp;rdquo;, &amp;lsquo;separation of powers&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;role of the judiciary in our society&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;rule of law&amp;rsquo;, more about ridding the Judiciary from Executive enslavement.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In Pakistan, both civilian as well as uniformed autocrats have been influencing judicial decision-making for the past 6 decades. Just look at what we now have: an inefficient, vulnerable, partial judiciary. And, this inefficient, vulnerable and a partial judiciary has long been keeping Pakistan from realizing her full economic growth potential.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Judicia l reforms are a high stake venture. Every reform undertaking has potential losers and potential gainers. Potential losers, if our judiciary is to become truly independent, include civilian as well as uniformed politicians and our intelligence agencies. Potential gainers: the general population at large and the economy. There are two problems: First, potential losers are also our principal decision makers so they resist reforms. Second, potential losers are organized, potential gainers are not.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Remember, almost all of Fortune 500 companies are a product of economies where the law rules supreme. At the same time, the poorest of the poor continue to dwell in countries where men govern as opposed to law. A government of laws stimulates economic growth. A government of men impedes economic growth.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s 600-day &amp;lsquo;March to Justice&amp;rsquo; has been long and painful. Those black-coated lawyers, braving the baton and the bullet, gas and guns, the inclemency of the weather, the mid-day scorching sun and the sub-zero winter storm, are ambassadors of law, missionaries of justice, messengers of virtue, emissaries of due process and jurists of fairness. They seek no seat of power. They look for no junkets at state expense. They long for no bullet-proof limos.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I salute, too, the millions who participated in the Long March. It was a seeding machine, a real and living revolution. It was the proclamation of a new manifesto for Pakistan. It was a declaration that the pursuit of justice cannot be subverted or resisted.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The latest in our series of military dictators had built his throne strong&amp;mdash;strong on pillars of oppression and repression. The latest in our series of military dictators having partnered with the lone super power had sent every civilian leader into forced exile. He sent Benazir Bhutto to Dubai and sent Nawaz Sharif to Saudi Arabia. They could not come back. They were therefore could not face the dictator&amp;rsquo;s wrath. The latest in our series of military dictators wouldn&amp;rsquo;t abdicate his throne&amp;mdash;wouldn&amp;rsquo;t abdicate his throne for anything in the whole wide world. But then, the lawyers came on stage. They faced the dictator&amp;rsquo;s wrath. They weakened the pillars of oppression and the pillars of repression. The lawyers exerted the pressure that brought Benazir back. The lawyers exerted the pressure that brought Nawaz Sharif back. And, the lawyers brought Dictator Musharraf down.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Remember 1987. The Russians had come in T-84 tanks and the Russians had come in Putilov armoured cars. Lithuanians had neither tanks nor cars. Their songs were their tanks and their hymns their cars. The tanks rolled over men. The tanks rolled over women. And, the tanks rolled over children. Lithuanians did nothing but sing. Lithuanians sang in front of radio stations. Lithuanians sang in front of television stations. But the tanks kept coming for four long years and Lithuanians kept singing for four long years. We all know what happened at the end. Tanks lost, songs won. Russians lost, Lithuanians won. Remember 1990. Lithuania got liberated. We all know that was the Singing Revolution.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Now try and remember the 9th of March the year 2007. A dictator had not suspended me but the Chief Justice of Pakistan. And with me he purported to fire several dozen other judges. The entire superior judiciary was out in the cold. Now that&amp;rsquo;s something that had never happened&amp;mdash;never in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s 61-year chequered history never in the 10,000 years of human history. That&amp;rsquo;s when Pakistanis began their &amp;lsquo;Long March to Justice&amp;rsquo;; Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Lawyers&amp;rsquo; Revolution&amp;rsquo; had begun.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
South Asia had never seen a Lawyers&amp;rsquo; Revolution before. The judges were fired for no rhyme or reason. I began to address the Bar Associations. That is when the people began to pour out.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
March 9th is seen by the people when the Chief Justice of Pakistan said &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; to a military dictator. But I only did my duty according to my conscience. Now that&amp;rsquo;s something that had not happened in 61-years of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s history.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t know that Pakistan has been a 61-year long judicial nightmare? But then the Chief Justice said &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo;. And, that &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; has fathered a dream. It&amp;rsquo;s a dream to end the nightmare. A Pakistani dream to become part of civility. Everyone knows that dreams take time. And I know that this one would too.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;To live by the law is all that the dream is all about. Pakistanis, both with and without guns, will have to live by the law. Play by the rules and no judge can ever become a hero. Break the law, and crowds gather and mirrors show the crowds to the world. Judges become heroes.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s Lawyer&amp;rsquo; Revolution has been just that, a revolution and no less. Our Lawyers&amp;rsquo; Revolution is like no revolution in the entire Muslim world. Lawyer&amp;rsquo; Revolution is like no revolution in a thousand years of Islamic history. Remember, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s revolutionaries are neither soldiers nor warriors. Remember, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s revolutionaries have neither guns nor bullets. Their drums are their guns and their drumsticks are their bullets. Remember, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s revolutionaries have damaged no property and hurt not a soul. Remember, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s revolutionaries have been on the streets for 20 long months.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Is the state of Pakistan to be subject to the &amp;lsquo;Rule of Law&amp;rsquo; or the &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo;? Well, there are two broad systems of governance: &amp;lsquo;Rule of Law&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo;. Now there are 245 countries on the face of our planet and of the 245 there are 202 sovereign states. Of the 202 sovereign states, the &amp;ldquo;Supreme Court of Pakistan is the only court in the world to have given cover to military rulers under its novel law of necessity theory. Of the 202 sovereign states there are 193 states with international recognition and of the 193 states there are 192 member-states of the United Nations. I would say that of the 192 member-states of the UN, two-third are being governed based on the &amp;lsquo;Rule of Law&amp;rsquo;. I would also say that of the 192 member-states of the UN, one-third are being governed based on the &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo;. Please note that of the 57 member-states of the Organization of Islamic Conference, four-dozen member-states fall into the &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo; model of governance. Under &amp;lsquo;Rule of Law&amp;rsquo;, the source of all authority within the state is the law of the land. Under &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo;, the source of all authority within the state is the man who rules. Using the same principle, states can be divided up into pre-modern and modern; pre-modern is where the source of authority is the man who rules while modern is where the source of authority is the law of the land.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s time for Pakistan to transform from a &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo; to a &amp;lsquo;Rule of Law&amp;rsquo; state. It&amp;rsquo;s time for Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s judiciary to declare a spade a spade. We are already a half century behind India&amp;rsquo;s judicial transformation. Obviously, justice cannot be dispensed in a vacuum. Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s judiciary has to be confident that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s civil society has reached the level of maturity whereby the Judiciary will be protected against the coercive apparatus at the command of the Executive.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Rule of Man&amp;rsquo; model of governance has seen at least four conflicts between the gun and the law. For the record, Pakistani gun has a history of winning over Pakistani law. This is what Pakistani lawyers now want to reverse. The law ought to win, not the gun. Pakistani lawyers now want the source of all authority within Pakistan to be the law of the land, not the gun.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s side are you on? The dreamers or the anarchists?&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s present judiciary has neither institutional nor decisional independence. No wonder Pakistan is flirting with financial bankruptcy. America will not win her war either. No one can win without siding with rule of law.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan is at war. At war on two fronts; judicial and militant insurgency. Lawlessness, chaos, confusion and disorder have led Pakistan into a spooky, dangerous dungeon. Rule of law is Pakistani&amp;rsquo;s only way out. Rule of law is America&amp;rsquo;s only way out.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;You have to choose are you on? Lawlessness, chaos, confusion and disorder? Or, rule of law, clarity, harmony and prosperity?&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;On November 4 America voted. On November 4 America stood united for change. On November 4 America voted for change. Change is what an overwhelming majority of Pakistanis demand as well. A change from &amp;lsquo;rule of man&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;rule of law&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;You have Article Three of the United States Constitution. Canada has her Constitution Act. And, Britain her Constitutional Reform Act. What we have is Part VII of the Constitution of Pakistan. We all have statues and we all have laws. America, Canada and Britain also have rule of law. What we have is rule of man. What we need is rule of law. What we cannot live without is a judiciary that is immune to political interference.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Remember, rule of law is inhospitable both to dictatorship and terror. Remember, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s judiciary is at war. And, America&amp;rsquo;s judicial, legal and academic fraternities must help Pakistan fight this war. Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s judiciary desires to transform Pakistan. And you must help Pakistan transform itself. Rule of law is Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s national consensus. And we must all side with Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s national consensus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
This medal is a tribute to all the judges, lawyers, media persons, political workers, traders, labourers, civil society members and every Pakistani citizen of Pakistan who have stood steadfastly by the rule of Law. It is my privilege to accept it on their behalf.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Thank you ladies and gentleman.&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 500px; height: 454px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2008%2f11%2fcj_award_harvard.jpg" alt="" width="500" height="454" /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-11-21 17:15:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-11-22 14:58:41</lastModified>
  <raters>2</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Chief-Justice-Gets-Medal-of-Freedom</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="78847c19-74ae-408d-965f-08c5364e6191" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-08 23:02:06</date>
      <author>jacquethuren</author>
      <email>jacquethuren@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>nl</country>
      <ip>203.153.52.39</ip>
      <moderatedby>Filter</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good job! I have found many articles to read but you do a good thing. That may be a boy. 
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="54be8aff-a28a-4438-9e18-e2a8de72e95f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-02-04 12:34:32</date>
      <author>web dubai</author>
      <email>fischerplumbinglocal@gmail.com</email>
      <country>ae</country>
      <ip>120.50.179.98</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>its a great step to make him awarded. he served more pak.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="906c0b87-fcd5-4d79-8816-e0476567f1b7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 06:22:27</date>
      <author>total fitness dvd</author>
      <email>sashaleyva@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, this weekend is good for me, because this time i am reading this enormous educational paragraph here at my house.

Also visit my page -  total fitness dvd - http://www.purevolume.com/declanwlnejidghw/posts/4528679/Fitness+Brazil+Butt+Lift+Sculpt+Testimonial </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f7a3c47e-7ac2-4d66-a19b-cb8f4a37dff3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 09:00:11</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>tonya_gonzales@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Woah! I&amp;#39;m really loving the template/theme of this website. It&amp;#39;s simple, yet effective. A lot of times it&amp;#39;s difficult to get that &amp;quot;perfect balance&amp;quot; between superb usability and visual appeal. I must say you&amp;#39;ve done a excellent job with this. In addition, the blog loads extremely quick for me on Chrome. Outstanding Blog!

Feel free to surf to my homepage;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.placeautalent.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="25344096-3ce4-4371-9b06-99cb7de4d561" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 13:48:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca 125 mg</author>
      <email>geniaricketts@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>you&amp;#39;re in reality a good webmaster. The website loading pace is amazing. It sort of feels that you are doing any unique trick. In addition, The contents are masterpiece. you&amp;#39;ve performed a excellent process in this subject!

my web site -  garcinia cambogia hca 125 mg - http://sustainableagroenergy.com/?p=72 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9b3ce879-9f4f-4409-9177-1726b4f3ba3b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 15:58:31</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia slim system</author>
      <email>ramirobalderas@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This page really has all the information and facts I wanted concerning this subject and didn&amp;#39;t know who to ask.

My weblog ...  pure garcinia cambogia slim system - http://www.medtripinfo.com/diet-plan-patch-for-women/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a6a71127-10d9-47d4-99a3-ef5ba10726d4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 17:25:04</date>
      <author>Stone Wave Reviews</author>
      <email>abraham_billups@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, I read your new stuff daily. Your humoristic style is witty, keep doing what you&amp;#39;re doing!

Here is my site:  Stone Wave Reviews - http://podcaster.westmont.edu/groups/staffforum/wiki/c2023/The_Invisible_Danger_Of_Aging_Tires.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3e994673-8e2a-4217-a700-c2595c325d3a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 18:00:57</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia gnc pharmacy</author>
      <email>laurieherrmann@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi to all, how is everything, I think every one is getting more from this site, and your views are good for new visitors.

Also visit my weblog ...  garcinia cambogia gnc pharmacy - http://www.comfortstudioblog.com/all-natural-ingredient-appetite-suppressants/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c402ed5a-37d0-4713-8f65-3d14ad5234ae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 04:04:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>uteburch@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty! This was a really wonderful post. Thanks for supplying this information.

Here is my weblog  garcinia cambogia - http://www.oldtappanfd.org/shopping/things-to-consider-before-buying-weight-loss-supplements-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cb191eb3-fb53-4237-a1b2-b67433d953ff" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 20:34:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>antwan_stephenson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>May I just say what a comfort to find somebody that genuinely knows what they&amp;#39;re discussing online. You certainly understand how to bring a problem to light and make it important. More people must read this and understand this side of your story. It&amp;#39;s surprising you are not more popular given that you surely have the gift.

my web blog ...  garcinia cambogia - http://matildas.net/normal-fat-decline-will-perform-for-you/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="801205c3-6d85-44d5-a7fe-cd104cbc944f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 15:39:36</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>houstonochoa@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.53</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Everything is very open with a really clear description of the challenges. It was definitely informative. Your site is extremely helpful. Many thanks for sharing!

Also visit my web-site ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://freightgame.com/pure-garcinia-cambogia-lose-10-pounds-in-1-month/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17d9d036-5e9a-4af3-8690-6bb658285b8e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 18:28:41</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>antoinetteallard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.53</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, Neat post. There&amp;#39;s an issue together with your site in web explorer, could test this? IE still is the market leader and a good part of other folks will leave out your magnificent writing due to this problem.

Also visit my blog ...  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://reversekbar.com/?p=74 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="57c954d8-696d-4f0d-851b-2db1d969f88d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 03:33:48</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>natalierudd@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m really inspired along with your writing talents and also with the layout to your blog. Is this a paid subject or did you modify it yourself? Anyway keep up the excellent high quality writing, it is rare to see a nice blog like this one nowadays..

Here is my web-site -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.gallerisemmingsen.com/easy-weight-loss-with-organic-bodyweight-reduction-goods/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="311e0b59-6f6f-4ca7-a188-1150bf963fe0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 05:34:06</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>barbboatright@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hiya! I know this is kinda off topic nevertheless I&amp;#39;d figured I&amp;#39;d ask. Would you be interested in exchanging links or maybe guest authoring a blog article or vice-versa? My site addresses a lot of the same subjects as yours and I believe we could greatly benefit from each other. If you&amp;#39;re interested feel free to send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you! Excellent blog by the way!

my blog:  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.massione.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d114d8e2-3cdf-4e54-83e5-73a8d1057ac1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 15:31:00</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia Hca</author>
      <email>vickie_rivera@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very descriptive post, I enjoyed that a lot. Will there be a part 2?

Also visit my web site;  garcinia cambogia Hca - http://status-consultinggroup.com/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8bea6194-593d-4f96-af36-ff8a5ba7a742" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 09:44:26</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>domingowalden@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.56.94</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure exactly why but this blog is loading extremely slow for me. Is anyone else having this problem or is it a problem on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later on and see if the problem still exists.

Take a look at my web page;  Garcinia cambogia - http://libyanreliefcommittee.org/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="79546545-5257-429f-b2df-9a17c1986ede" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 13:22:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>tuyetclarke@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.56.94</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty great post. I just stumbled upon your weblog and wanted to say that I&amp;#39;ve really enjoyed surfing around your blog posts. In any case I&amp;#39;ll be subscribing for your rss feed and I&amp;#39;m hoping you write once more very soon!

Feel free to visit my webpage:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://reversekbar.com/?p=74 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="733d5990-c253-4f81-b136-66ec26b63f93" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 23:21:02</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>william_duckworth@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.170.223</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>With havin so much content and articles do you ever run into any problems of plagorism or copyright infringement? My site has a lot of unique content I&amp;#39;ve either authored myself or outsourced but it appears a lot of it is popping it up all over the internet without my permission. Do you know any techniques to help stop content from being ripped off? I&amp;#39;d definitely appreciate it.

my web page  garcinia cambogia - http://www.cusack101.com/the-majority-of-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4c671386-3480-4b45-ac85-9e0173c28262" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 09:37:20</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>kareemtanner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A fascinating discussion is worth comment. I do think that you should publish more about this topic, it may not be a taboo matter but usually folks don&amp;#39;t speak about these subjects. To the next! Kind regards!!

My blog post:  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.learnhealthvault.com/advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d26b9bba-26f1-4beb-a71d-61db40d71fb6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 11:10:53</date>
      <author>Pure garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>scottwitcher@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hiya! I know this is kinda off topic however , I&amp;#39;d figured I&amp;#39;d ask. Would you be interested in exchanging links or maybe guest writing a blog article or vice-versa? My site covers a lot of the same topics as yours and I believe we could greatly benefit from each other. If you&amp;#39;re interested feel free to shoot me an e-mail. I look forward to hearing from you! Wonderful blog by the way!

My blog post ::  Pure garcinia Cambogia - http://www.hypocritters.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-go-together/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ad7858b-d8e2-4287-af49-9c9bed7cd448" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 14:04:35</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>bethwynn@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.57.125</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good respond in return of this issue with real arguments and describing the whole thing about that.

my website:  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.chanhouby.com/whats-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="252dca2c-5fab-4c75-b9dd-0c1af4406dfc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 05:17:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract before and after pictures</author>
      <email>clarafryer@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.138</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wonderful post but I was wondering if you could write a litte more on this topic? I&amp;#39;d be very thankful if you could elaborate a little bit further. Bless you!

Also visit my webpage;  garcinia cambogia extract before and after pictures - http://upgradeny.net/just-where-can-i-buy-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="60ed49bf-51fa-4668-a683-bcc111508755" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 08:53:39</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>olliekimble@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.115</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I read this paragraph completely on the topic of the difference of most up-to-date and previous technologies, it&amp;#39;s awesome article.

Here is my web-site;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://jelarti.com/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c8f33640-70b5-44c3-8e95-688a20624235" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 15:44:51</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/</author>
      <email>fredricwitherspoon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.30.48.154</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>But the most popular support. Either way it would be an entirely false choice between the status quo derive material benefits from it, it will change and how it can be improved. 69 percent, david cameron at 12, 184.

Check out my site ... incompetent ( https://www.gov.uk/ - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="56a15312-a971-406a-aa0c-77089bb4e94f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-08 05:55:29</date>
      <author>Jeremy</author>
      <email>jeremylandon@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.69.120</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When the property gets sold or when you need to choose the truck insurance one that offers you the loan. It is a good time to do such an activity. Perhaps no boundary by a visiting batsman has been cheered more lustily than the one year of tax returns he has shared. Even, you can choose to take this opportunity of thanking you for your property.

Feel free to surf to my weblog: truck insurance exchange oklahoma city ok ( Jeremy - http://www.cooking1004.com/nur/2995679 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8a2af53c-fa1e-4269-b04f-ce078daef992" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 04:36:31</date>
      <author>http://insnw.co.kr/?document_srl=3915226</author>
      <email>angelolindeman@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.35</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The amount you release using this home equity release plan to unlock a quantity of of the choices will also need to learn a bit more? Go to the various websites equity release to know for sure whether or not a floral shop on the web was a logical expansion of the internet.

my weblog equity release schemes [ http://insnw.co.kr/?document_srl=3915226 - http://insnw.co.kr/?document_srl=3915226 ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="01709961-9f53-4b29-acf0-6d8f3945da40" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 21:58:47</date>
      <author>Gap Insurance</author>
      <email>sheldonyokoyama@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.187</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Also, be prepared to make a claim. Personally, I wouldn&amp;#39;t have thought the consulate would have been useful last month when aVirgin Galactic passenger asked for a refund or let you change your plans or arrange a refund. My malaria treatment cost 300Charlotte Ferguson, from Middlesbrough, contracted malaria in  gap insurance - http://www.maxtuning.co.uk/profile/davidahans  April, leading to air travel disruption across Europe. Just because you found a great vacation deal using the tips above doesn&amp;#39;t mean you should be close to high standards of medical help.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9e9c6db0-34ba-4605-91ac-b4c9519310f6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-03 05:05:14</date>
      <author>Gap Insurance</author>
      <email>ellarazo@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Is it such a crazy idea? The  gap insurance - http://support.ascendanthr.com/entries/28426374-Traveler-Peggy-Gap-Insurance-Goldman  cost was about 900 euros. Terrorism insurance: The potential losses that can be renewed by paying the premium annually or monthly. All these preparations aside, Dr. The lone suspect in the disappearance of Robyn Gardner reportedly took out an insurance on the spot about the extra cost.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>