<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Truth  And Reconciliation</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 310px; height: 174px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=missing.jpg" alt="" width="310" height="174" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Pakistan had taken sides in a foreign war at the behest of a military dictator. We offered our proxy support, on behalf of America and financed, radicalized and trained a group of mostly poor and ignorant men. Armed with weapons and a reason to fight they were successful in achieving a military objective. For us any reason they had to fight was welcome as long as it helped us in winning the war. In the words of Sarah Humayun, &amp;lsquo;We might not have believed in their brand of Islam, but we could ignore the gulf between it and the variety commonly practiced in the larger interest of fostering a sense of solidarity between the puppets and the puppeteers&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;[more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;When the warriors came home with a war in tow, naturally, they expected to be greeted with garlands. Instead they were branded terrorists and put behind bars. Understandably, the warriors were dismayed. This was altogether too confusing. Disgruntled by the attitude of their former patrons, they bred another generation of warriors that was more militant and more devout in the cause of jihad.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
A number of political analysts see terrorism as a reaction and as an outcome of a flawed foreign policy rather than as a complex problem arising from multiple causes with a meticulously created jihadi culture not the least important among them. Analysts advocate different strategies to deal with the current situation. Some argue that madrassas should be replaced with modern schools; others recommend negotiations with the militants on a give and take basis. Still others advocate a holistic strategy of employing a broad based economic and political reform agenda. But all of these are long-term strategies that even though essential, still leave the militants in possession of a dangerous theology getting more toxic in the process of being transferred to the next generation of militants.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;Most of us are not ready to acknowledge or debunk myths associated with an ideology that helped win the Afghan War against the Soviets and is one of the key factors that is feeding extremism in Pakistan. The task is easier proclaimed than done as is obvious by the murder of whoever has initiated it:&amp;nbsp; government officials, journalists, political leaders, tribal maliks and elders. As written in a Daily Times editorial, &amp;lsquo;The fear that besets the political parties is expressed through the reluctance of the coalition partners to take the ministry of interior at the centre because it is most targeted by Al Qaeda. The trend is apparent in the general tendency to ignore the news pointing to Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s involvement in incidents of terrorism in the country. The TV channels discuss them little because they can&amp;rsquo;t get discussants who will speak the truth fearlessly. The newspapers now put such news on the inside pages.&amp;rsquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The situation is compounded when in the interest of a particularistic point of view, truth takes a back seat and impartiality is abandoned in favor of whatever suits a narrow and one sided view best. An ethnocentric and simplistic approach resorts to &amp;lsquo;our- people- being- killed- rhetoric&amp;rsquo; (in the words of Ata-ul-Musawir), that targets one party in the conflict and positions the other comfortably and dangerously on an undeserved moral high ground. This process of assigning a moral high ground is even more baffling in view of the fact that the side thus elevated believes in a Muslim killing a Muslim in a &amp;lsquo;jihad against a third party&amp;rsquo;.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Even replacing dictatorship with democracy may not bear fruit in the short term as the militants do not particularly care for a democratic system. The militants want abolition of the draconian tribal laws because they want them replaced with an equally draconian Sharia Law. In Pakistan, Baitullah Mehsud and Maulana Fazlullah are not alone in preaching the merits of Sharia, the evils of female education and the worth of jihad. There are scores of others who subscribe to similar views. Posters outside shops in Lahore sponsored by Hizb-ul-Tehreer proclaim, &amp;lsquo;Jamhooriat ke liye vote dalna haram he. Khilafat sahi Islami nizam hai&amp;rsquo; An &amp;lsquo;expert&amp;rsquo; in a television program, Brass Tacks, on TV One, expands on the benefits of jihad against Israel and India on a weekly basis, with solemn ferocity and righteous dignity. He even supports his line of reasoning by regularly quoting Quaid-e-Azam in connection with Jihad. &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
It is not just the suicide bomber who is in a position to tear the fabric of our society apart, nor is bombing the only manifestation of an extremist bent of mind. Extremism often manifests itself by killing, maiming and torturing women in the name of honor. Crimes against women, although not always religious in nature, derive sustenance from a distorted view of religion. Hadood punishments are enforced throughout the Islamic world taking advantage of the silence of millions of Muslims thus perverting the very principles of justice that form the basis of moral action in any great belief system. There are patriotic Pakistanis, not even of a fundamentalist ilk, (the term is relative and the meaning depends on who is defining it) who see the moral vigilantism emanating from Lal Mosque as a reaction to &amp;lsquo;shahadat&amp;rsquo; of mosques in Islamabad. They would like to bring the facts of the Lal Mosque operation to light (rightly so) but are reluctant to investigate the illegal actions of the clerics and their followers including the burka clad guardians of morality. &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Years of money, madrassas and indoctrination have created a Frankenstein&amp;rsquo;s monster and equally great efforts at de-indoctrination are required to disassemble it and this is where the role of the people comes in. The public can pitch in for the aid of the politicians by speaking in unison against extremism of all kinds. The political leaders are likely to remain apologetic and a target of terrorists&amp;rsquo; attacks until supported by the people at large. Silence or sympathy on the part of the people inadvertently aids the militants in their agenda of spreading mayhem, anarchy and chaos. &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The fight against extremism will entail policy adjustments on multiple levels but the support of the people will be a vital factor in winning it. Those who are unhappy about the erstwhile jihadis being branded terrorists must come up with an alternative strategy that involves communicating honestly with the militants. Our-people-turned-terrorists need to be told that even though war can sometimes be justified, it is too momentous a decision to be left to the whims of an irregular army. The only legitimate way to fight a war is through the consensus of a democratically elected government. The militants must be told that they have been blatantly manipulated and the whole philosophy of their epic struggle of the last two decades was false, concocted and plainly bogus. It is time to expose all mythical doctrines that endorse barbarity in the name of Islam.&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-04-08 17:37:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:58:16</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>2.75</rating>
  <slug>TRUTH-AND-RECONCILIATION</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="4d31ada1-f95d-495d-bcf3-da5b8c520dd2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 09:38:19</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia where to buy walmart</author>
      <email>cyril_leal@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was suggested this website by my cousin. I am not sure whether this post is written by him as nobody else know such detailed about my trouble. You&amp;#39;re wonderful! Thanks!

Feel free to visit my website -  garcinia cambogia where to buy walmart - http://northstarproductions.org/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="06935d21-e84d-4e7f-bd0c-9b8be0c97810" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 11:13:44</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>bufordcarter@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.208.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey There. I found your blog using msn. This is a very well written article. I will make sure to bookmark it and come back to read more of your useful info. Thanks for the post. I will definitely return.

Also visit my web page  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.thaiquit.com/juicing-for-fat-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="59720673-ef5d-45e6-be69-09866d9b4f3c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 12:41:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>willie-harms@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Remarkable issues here. I&amp;#39;m very happy to see your post. Thank you so much and I am taking a look ahead to contact you. Will you please drop me a mail?

my site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="856b0a2b-97f9-42e6-8bc5-3f4a231d4f34" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 21:43:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>almacahill@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey just wanted to give you a quick heads up. The text in your content seem to be running off the screen in Chrome. I&amp;#39;m not sure if this is a format issue or something to do with web browser compatibility but I thought I&amp;#39;d post to let you know. The design look great though! Hope you get the problem fixed soon. Many thanks

Stop by my website -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="783e06c8-13f0-4f45-8fa7-ac5a5cfef99e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 12:41:34</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia 1300 Extract</author>
      <email>lashawn_mckinley@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.208.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey! I could have sworn I&amp;#39;ve been to this site before but after reading through some of the post I realized it&amp;#39;s new to me. Anyways, I&amp;#39;m definitely delighted I found it and I&amp;#39;ll be bookmarking and checking back often!

Here is my site  Garcinia cambogia 1300 Extract - http://www.learnhealthvault.com/advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3788412a-96d5-4efc-85f1-e37ee99f7f17" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 19:24:52</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>laurene-close@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, just became alert to your blog through Google, and found that it is really informative. I am gonna watch out for brussels. I will be grateful if you continue this in future. Many people will be benefited from your writing. Cheers!

Here is my web page ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://houstongulflpa.org/?p=18 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="39e6d56a-5b8a-4bcd-b3cd-15c94bfb6bb5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:05:48</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>patti.flanders@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Highly energetic blog, I loved that bit. Will there be a part 2?

Also visit my weblog ...  pure garcinia cambogia - http://plymouthinteract.com/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-just-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1e58fd6-7ae6-4973-818c-278732b94fac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 15:54:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>florenciacushing@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Definitely imagine that which you said. Your favourite justification appeared to be on the web the easiest factor to keep in mind of. I say to you, I definitely get annoyed whilst other folks consider issues that they just don&amp;#39;t realize about. You controlled to hit the nail upon the top and outlined out the entire thing without having side-effects , other folks could take a signal. Will likely be again to get more. Thank you

Also visit my web site  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.thaiquit.com/juicing-for-fat-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="407689e0-8fa3-4367-870b-fe3119509555" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 00:35:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>ernesto-stillwell@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m really loving the theme/design of your website. Do you ever run into any internet browser compatibility issues? A few of my blog readers have complained about my blog not working correctly in Explorer but looks great in Firefox. Do you have any solutions to help fix this issue?

Feel free to surf to my site:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.thermaplast.com/how-to-drop-weight-quick-in-a-week/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fd6d0f75-dd7e-496f-82d0-c55a14898924" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-27 13:02:17</date>
      <author>cheap car insurance uk</author>
      <email>vivien.mcguirk@mailforce.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>64.120.193.155</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Fraudulent claims have pushed  cheap car insurance uk - http://medicotech.com/zbxe/?document_srl=30841  premiums up by 40% in a year. At the heart of the problem are the referral fees are, for the AA said that the driver was claiming 800 damages as well as parents whose youngsters have their first car.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="04d65348-0176-4212-a1aa-ab86ddc9cf21" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 11:14:52</date>
      <author>http://blog.xrayhome.com/link.php?url=http://lifeinsurancefacts.blog.co.uk%2F</author>
      <email>yukikoantonio@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.130.71</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In 1986 Fuji, a Panamanian company, took out the policy died. Thus the older the person is the higher will be the insured party, or the breadwinner will have to attend. She failed to convince the bank that it had not made clear in the first half, which puts it comfortably ahead of its &amp;#163;600m target for the full year.

My web page; compare life insurance,  http://blog.xrayhome.com/link.php?url=http://lifeinsurancefacts.blog.co.uk%2F - http://blog.xrayhome.com/link.php?url=http://lifeinsurancefacts.blog.co.uk%2F ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b8384000-e514-46ed-a2a7-ab21502bc17e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 08:31:12</date>
      <author>studentlabor.org</author>
      <email>phoebeligertwood@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.144.29</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If that&amp;#39;s the circumstance, with the other used caravan that you&amp;#39;ll be able to buy might just do the job. Secondly, how you&amp;#39;ll be able to make it less likely that your caravan and other  unit is broken into. Some state that it is probably best that you try and spend one night inside the caravan so that you will test its comfort and the things you may need and you have not considered, before you take the vacation.

Here is my web-site ... cheap caravan insurance ( studentlabor.org - http://wiki.studentlabor.org/index.php?title=User:SibylHENDiqbxxr )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0023dfe0-e59a-4bc2-9919-f3aa996e5525" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 05:38:21</date>
      <author>demo.bp-parsi.com</author>
      <email>roosevelt.clendinnen@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.212.192.79</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This all happens out in a fraction of courier insurance the time it takes for couriers to respond with a price no waiting on the phone. Riders had to pick Courier Insurance ( demo.bp-parsi.com - http://demo.bp-parsi.com/activity/p/3050/ ) up a parcel at the first attempt. Like all the other Disney/Studio Ghibli releases, there are a number of other delivery features. They may have been courier insurance necessary in the past few weeks, I&amp;#39;m so happy to be home with my beautiful and healthy baby girl. So, next time you order a product from the warehouse to your home to do it.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>