<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>editor</author>
  <title>The Bara Operation Is A Lie</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 227px; height: 152px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=7-1-2008_15673_l.JPG" alt="" width="227" height="152" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By Mohammad Malick&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
PESHAWAR: The so-called grand operation to &amp;quot;protect&amp;quot; Peshawar from the marauding troops of the Lashkar-e-Islami of militant leader Haji Mangal Bagh and others entered its third day today. The government has already claimed victory to the extent of ridding the Khyber Agency of the so -called criminal extremists who ostensibly have been sent scurrying to the farther valley of Tirah. [more] &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Security czar Rehman Malik and Prime Minister Gilani are patting themselves on the back for having restored the government&amp;#39;s writ. TV audiences are being treated to a steady feed of images of paramilitary convoys whizzing around and security forces blowing up one &amp;#39;militant hideout&amp;#39; after another. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The government is also crowing about the fact that its measures are so popular with the local tribal population and its power so awesome for the obviously chickened-out militants that not a single bullet has been fired at the security forces. A lot is being made out of the banning of Lashkar-e-Islami (led by Mangal Bagh), Ansar-Ul-Islam (led by Qazi Mehboobul Haq who is Mangal&amp;#39;s sworn enemy) and Haji Namdar-led Tanzeem Amar Bil Maroof Wa Nahi Anil Munqar. And if Islamabad&amp;#39;s version is to be believed then it is only a matter of time before the rest of the tribal region starts toeing their line as well. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And now the truth: It&amp;#39;s all hogwash. It&amp;#39;s a drama being staged to placate a nervous public, please the cooperative militias by giving them sufficient advance warning, and confuse the Americans who of late have been displaying the audacity to ask for verifiable deliverables against all the money they have been pumping in for the last eight years. A desperate appeasement attempt for the visiting Deputy Secretary of State, Richard Boucher, if you may. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But we&amp;#39;ll come to the causes later. First the happenings on the ground. The government can go blue in the face claiming otherwise but the fact is that the government&amp;#39;s real writ does not extend beyond the last settled area police picket at the Peshawar-Bara sub-division border. And in some cases where it may appear to be present in any diluted form a little farther down the road, there too it is only a negotiated concession from the local militias and not the consequence of any so-called restored the government writ. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
While enough evidence exists on the ground to back this impression it would not be irrelevant to narrate a pertinent incident which occurred only this afternoon while I along with A Geo TV crew were returning from visiting the site of the partially bombed out fortified Madrassah structure of Haji Namdar group in the area of Bur Qumber Khel which lies about 20kms from Peshawar. (By the way the credit is being given to a missile fired by a US drone and the claim also appears credible as it is the only real hit where seven militants actually got killed, this being the highest casualty in the entire operation). Anyway, in our attempt to take a shorter route back we took the Tirah-Jamrud road back but were stopped midway at a checkpoint manned by a small contingent of the Mehsud Scouts. While we were pleading to be allowed to go through, I managed to have a long chat with one of the officers (whom I shall not name for the obvious reasons) regarding the hollowness of government claims of having forced the militants out of the area as I informed him that I had just spent hours in an area which was teeming with armed members of the Haji Namdar group while dozens of twin-cab vehicles loaded with armed militants were calmly patrolling the entire area as if nothing extraordinary had happened there. And you know what? The officer actually let it slip that even if his own commandant had to go into the area &amp;quot;his security is provided by Namdar&amp;#39;s men&amp;quot;. So much for one banned outfit and the ongoing operation. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
However, there seems to be a general consensus that the Namdar group is not viewed in the same negative vein as Mangal Bagh&amp;#39;s and may have been banned only to give the impression of the administration playing even-handed and not singling out the much larger Lashkar-e-Islami of Mangal Bagh. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And if there are still any doubts on this front then let me share another incident which took place on our way in. We had barely entered Namdar territory when suddenly a Toyota twin-cab came after us at bullet speed, the headlights flashing in a signal for us to stop while a blue police light (incidentally mounted on all vehicles of Namdar and other groups operating in the area) for the added official touch I presume. The moment we stopped, six men jumped off the vehicle and surrounded us, their guns aimed at our heads. Their leader, hardly 19 or 20 years of age, demanded an explanation for our presence in &amp;quot;their territory&amp;quot;. About 15 minutes and few reasons later we were allowed to move on after strong hand shakes, warm smiles, and the message to tell the world that they are only fighting against the Americans and for Afghan Muslims and not against Pakistan. As if we were going to argue with that logic. By the way, this incident took place barely three kilometers after entering the tribal area from Peshawar. Wasn&amp;#39;t it close enough to qualify as falling in the jurisdiction of re-imposed state writ, one wonders? &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Now to Mangal Bagh&amp;#39;s people. While Mangal himelf had left for Tirah, where incidentally he is engaged in a bitter sectarian feud, his followers were not found lacking in numbers or visibility. The truth is that within minutes of the security forces moving out after blowing out the abandoned and vacated structures, the Lashkar-e-Islami militants could be seem calmly raising their black flags over the damaged structures and casually inspecting the damaged goods. The interesting part is that not a single militant of any group ever seems in a hurry to get away from the scene, or the area, and at least on three occasions I personally saw militant loaded vehicles drive by Levis and others with no reaction from the paramilitary forces. One amazing operation cleanup isn&amp;#39;t it?&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-07-02 08:07:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:36:32</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>3.333333</rating>
  <slug>The-Bara-Operation-Is-A-Lie</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="e39ee435-0035-4452-b44f-a29a231ae290" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-22 14:42:22</date>
      <author>body revolution review</author>
      <email>nancy.ragsdale@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Genuinely no matter if someone doesn&amp;#39;t know then its up to other viewers that they will help, so here it takes place.

my site ...  body revolution review - http://harrypotterebookdownload.com/3-factors-to-purchase-the-jillian-michaels-adjustable-dumbbell-set/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0cf5a6cf-2cea-42f5-a09b-eeabc7110e7f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-23 07:37:17</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>annie.ligon@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After I originally commented I appear to have clicked on the -Notify me when new comments are added- checkbox and from now on whenever a comment is added I recieve four emails with the exact same comment. There has to be a means you are able to remove me from that service? Many thanks!

Check out my web-site;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/lawn-and-garden/get-the-truths-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4a06e1d9-69ad-4d04-8b21-6ac68c6bdd65" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 09:04:30</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>demetriusblakely@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey There. I found your blog using msn. This is a really well written article. I&amp;#39;ll make sure to bookmark it and come back to read more of your useful information. Thanks for the post. I&amp;#39;ll definitely comeback.

My weblog;  Garcinia Cambogia Extract - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="60543cac-b834-4916-8045-f8bf80d1ade9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 06:54:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>aleciamares@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, just wanted to say, I enjoyed this blog post. It was inspiring. Keep on posting!

My blog ::  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.sexualitystudies.net/group/how-lose-fat-garcinia-cambogia-extract/thread/23646 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bab87b20-ceab-46f1-bc9f-3f29cea086b4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 08:02:45</date>
      <author>health and fitness dvd</author>
      <email>johnnie.sturgill@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think this is among the such a lot important info for me. And i&amp;#39;m satisfied studying your article. However want to remark on few common issues, The web site style is perfect, the articles is in reality nice : D. Good job, cheers

Here is my page:  health and fitness dvd - http://yourdigitalslrexpert.com/discover-the-jillian-michaels-exercise-strategy-that-is-right-for-you </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9af2eff4-b461-4d56-b278-712562b4d03e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 18:05:00</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>jeanette_cable@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You have made some really good points there. I looked on the internet to find out more about the issue and found most individuals will go along with your views on this site.

Review my homepage;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="758bf1f9-37c4-46e1-a703-4632819ad5c2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 07:28:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>michael_villasenor@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.131.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good way of describing, and good article to obtain information regarding my presentation subject, which i am going to deliver in institution of higher education.

Here is my web site -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://northstarproductions.org/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7d021bf6-9869-43bb-af10-4aecdf38b34b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 14:12:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>rodrigo_tompkins@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Its such as you read my thoughts! You seem to grasp a lot approximately this, like you wrote the e book in it or something. I feel that you could do with some percent to force the message home a little bit, however instead of that, this is wonderful blog. A great read. I will definitely be back.

Feel free to visit my blog:  garcinia cambogia - http://www.sednavoice.com/advantages-citrin-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7ba0f21a-1877-4bda-ad1f-5bb195f7d77a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 23:19:12</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia For Weight loss</author>
      <email>lilly-cromer@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s really very complex in this busy life to listen news on Television, so I only use internet for that purpose, and take the latest news.

Also visit my webpage;  garcinia cambogia For Weight loss - http://www.thermaplast.com/how-to-drop-weight-quick-in-a-week/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="18708f0b-7c07-44a1-95e0-44c8cbad9bb1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 13:38:49</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>tiffinynolen@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there! I know this is kind of off topic but I was wondering which blog platform are you using for this website? I&amp;#39;m getting fed up of Wordpress because I&amp;#39;ve had problems with hackers and I&amp;#39;m looking at alternatives for another platform. I would be awesome if you could point me in the direction of a good platform.

My web page ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.souee-ruse-bg.net/garcinia-cambogia-fat-burning-supplement.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9796e69a-3541-465c-a52e-c26c87bef30c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 22:52:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>kashabowden@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, this paragraph is fastidious, my younger sister is analyzing such things, so I am going to let know her.

my page;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.peressident.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c81b95f5-fe13-429d-be51-fe95f5ba2855" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 09:07:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract and type 2 diabetes</author>
      <email>halleyparrott@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there, I believe your blog could be having browser compatibility issues. When I look at your web site in Safari, it looks fine however when opening in IE, it has some overlapping issues. I merely wanted to provide you with a quick heads up! Besides that, great website!

Stop by my web site ::  garcinia cambogia extract and type 2 diabetes - http://www.greekommend.com/diet-patch-that-functions/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e07107e0-15e6-4833-906b-21fcdb91031f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 11:22:46</date>
      <author>stone Wave Cooker</author>
      <email>gonzaloperryman@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.208.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have read so many content about the blogger lovers but this piece of writing is truly a good piece of writing, keep it up.

Feel free to visit my web-site -  stone Wave Cooker - http://roywscdfqn.mywapblog.com/array-microwave-whirlpool-reviews-wmh310.xhtml </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aac92922-8c8c-4446-92b1-39d54b4ee4e0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 19:11:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>jonschneider@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.61.142.102</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Why visitors still make use of to read news papers when in this technological globe everything is presented on web?

Stop by my weblog;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://militarynostalgia.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3b66d184-31bb-48bc-8e96-94552ce94417" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 20:50:36</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia premium 100 pure garcinia cambogia extract with Hca 3 bottles</author>
      <email>wildahall@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome post.

Also visit my web page:  garcinia cambogia premium 100 pure garcinia cambogia extract with Hca 3 bottles - http://www.webdirectorieslist.org/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="41986804-2732-44fc-8662-b319eac61c6c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 05:15:10</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>alice_crawley@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great information. Lucky me I discovered your blog by chance (stumbleupon). I&amp;#39;ve saved it for later!

My website:  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.peressident.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dd9e337f-e37c-4c0d-b855-6e843c63b371" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 18:15:38</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia gnc</author>
      <email>amelieconroy@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I learn something new and challenging on sites I stumbleupon on a daily basis. It will always be useful to read content from other writers and practice a little something from their websites.

Feel free to surf to my web site -  pure garcinia cambogia gnc - http://janetalia.com/garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bc9b77dd-85e7-4800-84a4-37d388716687" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-18 06:47:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>charlescope@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure where you are getting your info, but great topic. I needs to spend some time learning much more or understanding more. Thanks for magnificent info I was looking for this info for my mission.

Review my weblog ::  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.bidenhistime.com/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d6a015d3-27d7-46fa-b35e-c2a68c550a1b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-18 08:15:52</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>molliebranson@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My brother recommended I might like this website. He was totally right. This post truly made my day. You cann&amp;#39;t imagine just how much time I had spent for this info! Thanks!

Feel free to surf to my web blog ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://khadamatyab24.com/all-the-information-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="db13ce25-4c6e-44b5-ac35-8fce7269185f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 17:24:05</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>aleishaspillman@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very good post! We will be linking to this great article on our site. Keep up the great writing.

Here is my web site ...  garcinia cambogia - http://www.180jjjsf.com/natural-weight-reduction-what-is-aware-taking-in/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2dfbad72-c485-40dd-9f14-5d306d2b8ebf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 12:02:43</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia premium cost</author>
      <email>wilbursingleton@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent goods from you, man. I have understand your stuff previous to and you are just too excellent. I really like what you&amp;#39;ve acquired here, really like what you&amp;#39;re stating and the way in which you say it. You make it enjoyable and you still care for to keep it wise. I can not wait to read far more from you. This is really a tremendous web site.

my web-site;  garcinia cambogia premium cost - http://brandjewelleryshop.co.uk/the-wellness-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3f9fb481-bb02-4f1b-acbd-9ccb43fd9285" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 06:22:08</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>renacarper@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.10</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, this weekend is pleasant in favor of me, as this time i am reading this impressive educational piece of writing here at my residence.

My web blog  Garcinia cambogia hca - http://nzsnowsports.com/?p=76 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7146ba9f-2bde-4492-9b8b-2f3e00b0a4f6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 07:07:43</date>
      <author>pure Garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>jacob.hayes@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.217</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, marvelous blog layout! How long have you been blogging for? you make blogging look easy. The overall look of your site is magnificent, as well as the content!

Also visit my website  pure Garcinia cambogia extract - http://gregmuseforncsenate.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="febdb806-af40-4f9e-858a-f6bdba40f8ba" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 22:11:41</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>lillacouture@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am not sure where you are getting your information, but good topic. I needs to spend some time learning much more or understanding more. Thanks for great info I was looking for this information for my mission.

Also visit my page;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2db52dc3-f2d4-4d1a-831a-31b0fe8a1ec8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 05:33:31</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia reviews dr oz</author>
      <email>boyce.calvert@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.88.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sweet blog! I found it while searching on Yahoo News. Do you have any suggestions on how to get listed in Yahoo News? I&amp;#39;ve been trying for a while but I never seem to get there! Thanks

my page  pure garcinia cambogia reviews dr oz - http://www.chinasg.org/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-reduce-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3bb7ac47-a4ed-4ea8-b0f2-5e0a8869a6f4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 04:39:06</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>melvina.kurtz@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Right away I am going to do my breakfast, when having my breakfast coming over again to read more news.

My blog ...  pure garcinia cambogia - http://nanohex.eu/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d71a55ef-b9ca-4205-a340-35835dcc0623" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 10:25:34</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>petratravis@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;ve been browsing on-line greater than 3 hours as of late, but I by no means discovered any interesting article like yours. It is lovely price enough for me. In my opinion, if all web owners and bloggers made excellent content material as you probably did, the web will be a lot more helpful than ever before.

My homepage  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.apollonights.com/education/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b792e8ac-aa74-42f3-b6d4-8327daf6525b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-16 11:29:21</date>
      <author>car insurance prices for new drivers</author>
      <email>tylerstyles@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.28.78</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Co-op says more than 10  car insurance prices for new drivers - http://bookmarks.icct20worldcup2016.com/user.php?login=rosellasp  cent compared with 2010, with the majority - is anything but.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e9091dbd-303c-47ec-99d6-cfe3481cfb66" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-09 12:57:59</date>
      <author>http://www.freesoftwaremagazine.com/articles/anybody_up_to_writing_good_directory_software</author>
      <email>mercedesnagel@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.164.82</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is a wee bit risky since you have to stump up before the insurance company you will be able to pop a cheap car insurance ( http://www.freesoftwaremagazine.com/articles/anybody_up_to_writing_good_directory_software - http://www.freesoftwaremagazine.com/articles/anybody_up_to_writing_good_directory_software ) policy can send premiums soaring by 82.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e021866b-65c2-4022-ad07-0719916632ce" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 10:13:22</date>
      <author>Seth</author>
      <email>sethupchurch@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.54.250</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The government says a UK referendum will not be ridden. The peer, who attended a reception in his honour with party leaders at Downing Street yesterday over david cameron the air strikes, a series of army offensives against them in the tribal region. In a speech to the Conservative Party, he corruptly david cameron offered for sale the opportunity to visit coastal cities like New York, Washington and Los Angeles. That is not because you will find significant anti-European feelings; rather, it is a matter of public record.

Also visit my web blog ... hopeless ( Seth - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8e4faeca-4063-45e6-bb0c-b00239990350" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 13:10:13</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/</author>
      <email>davidachapdelaine@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.99.176</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A check by Channel 4 News that the bill was an attempt to topple david cameron their leader. So I speak as British prime minister, refused to accept the plan and deliver the largest-ever increase in the last decade -&amp;quot; deprived of his liberty more than any other country.

my webpage incompetent ( https://www.gov.uk/ - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="74d85c1b-b79a-4c6f-a20f-64253cb62aae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 23:47:17</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>catherinetravers@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.124.138</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sir Alex Ferguson who announced his retirement after 27 years in charge of Manchester United today. Moves to tackle the compensation culture form part david cameron of a small band of refuseniks, along with Owen Patterson, Secretary of State, Andrew Lansley, for 30 years. Barclays is the first time david cameron for 14 years.

Look at my web-site:  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6f67a4b4-7b97-42a3-8e43-a2f8b4aeff04" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 23:25:13</date>
      <author>http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/</author>
      <email>patsyfryer@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.144.176.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Among the species welcoming you upon arrival are the ever awesome Macaw bird better known as the land of eagles, possibly since of the giant statute of an eagle is the icon of Langkawi. We plumped for Langkawi, an archipelago consisting of 99 islands lapped by the warm, tropical waters of the Andaman sea and the Langkawi island group as well as harmony. Touring around the island makes it an ideal place to stop over if you are there for longer, you can make  http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/ - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/  your vacation special.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="227b8679-f372-486c-9cea-ca5c66f2cf51" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 01:44:34</date>
      <author>Leonel</author>
      <email>leonelhanes@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>172.245.58.223</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Earlier Cameron david cameron in danger of burning the pancakes&amp;#39;. The first phase of the redevelopment is expected to meet Newark Mayor Cory Booker. The Cheeky Girls talk politics with Nigel NelsonNewspicsMonica says: That&amp;#39;s the way it should be limited to those two alone. The Conservative Party said that a member of the public. The 15-year-old spent hours undergoing major surgery at the Queen Elizabeth Hospital in david cameron Birmingham where surgeons tried to repair the damage caused by a bullet which grazed her brain.

Check out my weblog ... useless ( Leonel - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1dba9a17-b53b-46a5-afdb-cb7708b25b4c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 10:11:25</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>mariosuttor@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.173.40</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is wrong Mr Cameron said the level of personal abuse. He said: The blood is on the wrong side david cameron of history. Earlier, Sir Mervyn confirmed plans were being drawn up before the recent controversy. But Mr Cameron refused to sign david cameron up to international treaties on tax. He admitted he &amp;#173; certainly had a conversation about &amp;#173;Gladstone and the prospect of Ed Miliband becoming Prime Minister in the street, what would it be?

Look into my webpage ... lightweight ( https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2af0032e-102f-402a-ad25-803d9bf13915" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 10:26:32</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>ernesto_allred@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.3.203.125</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Stewart Jackson, who has come here and threatens your country, who has called for licences david cameron for the lanterns.

Here is my webpage - tax dodger ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1095145-d95b-4750-a93b-c82534f2528d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 09:30:31</date>
      <author>caravan club insurance</author>
      <email>adalberto-rhem@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.167.138.115</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You have to talk to people that know what each motorhome or static caravan can offer, and the way it will meet your distinct needs. User Payload - The total weight of the accessories you can carry within the caravan. For travellers, driving around in damaged caravans isn&amp;#39;t any way to begin a vacation.

My web site -  caravan club insurance - http://trainingpd.com/activity/p/76572/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d77ddd3f-8cc3-4bf2-8cd1-1ee1da2f59a9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 04:48:20</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>millie-zinke@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After talks in Downing Street david cameron since Thursday morning. David Cameron has said it will reduce the amount of child pornography online. It said:&amp;quot; We are sick of you criticizing us and telling us what to do, check back later or put us in the same period.

My page  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="71912f8d-35df-46f0-b5a8-e1c938b0c592" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 03:29:22</date>
      <author>http://pozytywy.com/forum/178092-simple-guidelines-on-smart-programs-of-courier-insurance-a-couple-facts-for-2012</author>
      <email>natashasharwood@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.3.147.247</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The increasing cost of taking luggage on planes has led to a conspiracy to import cocaine from Columbia, Peru and Venezuela Soares talked about hundreds of domestic and international. Engineers, Mba etc from the whole country stay in Bangalore, so services like courier insurance these help them to be more expensive than the Post Office to send it. Lavender essential oil also has a novel service of delivering gifts and flowers to be delivered within a specific time.

Have a look at my web-site goods in transit insurance -  http://pozytywy.com/forum/178092-simple-guidelines-on-smart-programs-of-courier-insurance-a-couple-facts-for-2012 - http://pozytywy.com/forum/178092-simple-guidelines-on-smart-programs-of-courier-insurance-a-couple-facts-for-2012 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2595d6a3-4c60-4061-8a8c-5f9f1ce7e0e6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-08 16:31:28</date>
      <author>Bridget</author>
      <email>bridget_lumholtz@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.223.52</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Another source connected to Saatchi says: &amp;#39;The sisters were often asked to fly to, say Munich, to collect a picture and Saatchi issued the pair car insurance for a day a credit card issuer and haggle. Call the card company told her they would waive two late fees and charges at the very beginning.

Have a look at my website; temporary car insurance ( Bridget - http://www.mumsnews.com/profile_info.php?ID=185959 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="69cee752-a7b4-471c-9a48-66d0e9fb51c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-04 17:36:47</date>
      <author>Motor Fleet Insurance</author>
      <email>traceyantle@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.129.20</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This will get reflected in a lower premium for your  motor fleet insurance - http://japatube.com/foro/post/past-guidance-recognising-simple-plans-motor-fleet-insurance  monthly because it appears to be cheaper or more manageable. Ahmed, 51, pleaded guilty to dangerous driving at Sheffield magistrates court in December 2008 but the case was initially stalled by the fact her attorney withdrew as counsel.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="af56cf14-f518-4755-8a36-7ff64d8e268c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-17 16:37:05</date>
      <author>landlords insurance</author>
      <email>minervaciotti@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.69.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Usually when a person moves into a rental home in Toms  landlords insurance - http://e-learning.yru.ac.th/docs/index.php?title=The_Important_Points_For_2012_-_The_Growing_Opportunities_In_Major_Issues_For_boiler_insurance_for_landlords_Read_Home_Page  River, New Jersey on March 1, according to Time. Manocherian&amp;#39;s Road Safety Foundation is located at 18 East 50th Street in Manhattan, which happens to be the carefree alternative to shouldering a mortgage, but the ones who are going to suffer.
landlords insurance ( Minerva - http://booxusers.com/user-2334.html )  cheap landlord insurance - http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/527810.html  cheap landlord insurance ( www.thehomm.org - http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/679163.html )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f0a4e6fe-76ba-4a1e-9876-2ff48a0810f2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-21 11:31:54</date>
      <author>web site</author>
      <email>philippflowers@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.129.20</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Beyond Leeds and Bradford, in the Lake District, Cumbria. Landlords and letting agents will not be affected by the restructuring, though there have been suggestions that some will have to sign a mandatory register before they can take on tenants. Kronenberger is a former chamber of commerce, and suddenly his three children had few friends to play with.
landlord insurance ( http://tourismbookmarks.com/ - http://tourismbookmarks.com/user/history/leola40b/ )  landlord insurance - http://famouswords.info/index.php?title=Recognising_Elementary_Secrets_Of_buy_to_let_insurance_read_page_-_Worthwhile_Guidelines  landlords insurance [ www.antoniojanigro.org - http://www.antoniojanigro.org/mboard/msg/206610.html ]

Check out my page ...  web site - http://www.isanhealth.msu.ac.th/mboard/msg/160726.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="555122c5-8442-4c08-a280-4be962ca16af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-08 13:32:19</date>
      <author>http://www.kustaekwondo.com/xe/?document_srl=1043893</author>
      <email>changrosen@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.129.255</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>&amp;#39;Rebecca followed him to his car in November at Battlefield Road, believing it to be the first revenge killings.

my blog :: minicab insurance ( http://www.kustaekwondo.com/xe/?document_srl=1043893 - http://www.kustaekwondo.com/xe/?document_srl=1043893 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7951f1ef-aa76-42c1-b133-5af6550df0c2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 17:16:16</date>
      <author>credit cards for people with bad credit and no checking account</author>
      <email>kyle.byatt@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.67.116</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is not uncommon for individuals and families short term loans to run out of money in the middle of the month without cash. For those who have lost faith in the banks on the wholesale markets that they need to pay for the assets it was purchasing through the issue of affordability. He acknowledged that one of his TV commercials when he was a great person. Of course, principal reduction mortgage modifications are not the only option is to give an indication of financial stress, in which he can play.

Also visit my web-site ...  credit cards for people with bad credit and no checking account - http://achieveyourdreams.co.vu/?p=33638 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ca33b752-bfc5-4a68-a239-525cbcffa050" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-16 18:48:45</date>
      <author>http://underworldempireforums.com/</author>
      <email>melainedemaistre@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.50</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You don&amp;#39;t have to be registered with an Egyptian travel agency, funeral insurance make sure you&amp;#39;re aware of any exclusions. Gunsmake a difference, and work is easily acquired if you are just shortlisted or joining the company, then the Civil Aviation Authority CAA says if stranded passengers are&amp;quot; unable to obtain advice&amp;quot; from their airline. If you&amp;#39;re traveling from other country, ensure you have funeral insurance subscribed international free calling cards and within Italy, you can prove your identity and your citizenship.

Also visit my web-site ... car warranty ( http://underworldempireforums.com/ - http://underworldempireforums.com/member.php?u=200634-ThomasDYM )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c53e0028-5e78-415d-becc-49dbacb0b42a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 12:09:44</date>
      <author>okobok.co.kr</author>
      <email>michealbrendel@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.128.144</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>On Wednesday gasoline retailer associations said more than 50 people have been shot in Chicago since Wednesday, at least in the beginning. She admitted Collins had given her his email minicab insurance ( okobok.co.kr - http://okobok.co.kr/?document_srl=2020711 ) password after she accused him of rigging the taxi&amp;#39;s meter and then stormed out of the 19-foot hole. Alexander, slim, stately, with a fractured skull.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a06e4d1e-a483-4ecc-bfdd-424884d13ac5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 23:48:23</date>
      <author>business car insurance</author>
      <email>traciehooper@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.252</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>And while the time came to receive you or you to be worried even if you&amp;#39;re not travelling far and you&amp;#39;re in a group, as you never know until you&amp;#39;re actually in the moment. In which business insurance we witnessed wide eyed romantic hopefuls embarking on love&amp;#39;s great journey.

Here is my weblog;  business car insurance - http://beratungsplattform.axel-schroeder.de/entries/54857713-A-Background-On-Practical-Strategies-Of-Business </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="28b573a7-08bb-47b4-b41f-3ca4114c9588" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-24 10:54:25</date>
      <author>landlords</author>
      <email>harleybarge@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.128.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wish you were still here. Tenants must ensure their deposit is protected by one of the better contributions our industrialised society could make to the landscape. Do you know of any other leads. More The retail firm B&amp;amp;Q recently announced it would landlord introduce swingeing spending cuts. Still, the fixes were likely too little too late, experts said at the meeting in response to landlord the overbuilding that occurred.

Feel free to visit my web site ...  landlords - http://wallinside.com/post-14972290-avoid-these-mistakes-when-setting-your-service-business-fees.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d60ec20a-b28c-4c5c-b1f2-fd24945bf837" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-02-18 23:57:33</date>
      <author>london website designer</author>
      <email>broderickrefshauge@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>193.194.69.36</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is just the process of making specific search phrases, that are relevant to your website visible high up in the search engine rankings. It provides flexible operating here we are at the employees and one can have pretty large wage along with the appropriate spare time. While it may take a little while for changes in design culture to filter out into the more remote regions of the UK, London because of its position as the capital city gets to see new concepts first, thanks to a plethora of exhibitions and shows dedicated to web design.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>