<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Dress in the Journal Sembly</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2008%2f12%2fJEHANGIR.jpg" alt="" width="141" height="178" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Do you think I am writing to you from Inside Bhati Gate? No sir ji. I am writing to you from the Big Apple. You think Shriek Chairman is the Big Apple? Wrang again, although the Shriek Chairman is big leader and the apple of my eyes. [more]&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I am in Noo Yarak. This is the head affice of the UNO. Great world leaders are asked to dress the Journal Sembly From tam to tam. My tam has come. The Shriek Chairman has asked me to dress the Journal Sembly. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I met this Cheeni man yesterday. He shook my hand and said Ban Ki-Moon, Secty Journal. I said oye, Bhain Ki-Moon yourself. I don&amp;rsquo;t take insults from farners, even if they are Cheeni brothers like you. Also as far as I am concerned, I am the secty journal. He said pologies, misunderstanding. I am Korean not Chinese. I said OK, no mansion, same to same, as I say to the Shriek Chairman; although to him I say, no mansion in Surrey.&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;UNO needs to investigate the murder of Sheed Mohtarma. No,no, not Mohtarma Fatima Jinnah. She was killed by the fauj. We can&amp;rsquo;t fight the fauj. You would ask why not Sheed Chairman Bhutto? You see, he was killed by the fauj and the judiciary. We can&amp;rsquo;t fight the fauj and we can&amp;rsquo;t fight the judiciary, but we can buy the judiciary. In fact the price of judges is going down faster than the price of oil. One barrel may soon hit the 21 dollar mark, but justuce Dogar has already hit the 21 mark. Pakistan Peepal Paty and Shriek Chairman do not think there is any difference in a barrel of oil and a supreme coat judge. We will offer the cheapest rate in the national interest. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;But fust we must solve the Sheed Mohtarma murder mistri. Mistri Mhamd Hsain, from Inside Bhati Gate says, there is no mistri. Sheed Mohtarma was killed by Khana Kaaba Mehsood from Waziristan. Although naoo, it should be called Dronistan as most of the Wazir there have been killed by the drones. There are more Wazirs in Slamabad naoo than in Waziristan. At least 60 that I know of, in the federal cabinet. I think Slamabad should be renamed Waziristan. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Palease look at the draft of my sapeach:&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Dear presidents and prime ministers, laddies and gentlemen, palease fust of all saloot this picture of Shriek Chairman. He put his life and bank counts at risk by undertaking to restore damo cracy in Pakistan. He worked closely with the international communety. Mr. Dick Cheeni put it in his ear, that if he worked for samooth transition to damo cracy, his bank counts would be safe. Shriek Chairman replied with his usual frankness, &amp;lsquo;No problem sir ji.&amp;rsquo; Mr. Boucher has also helped a lot. He has done more air miles than Mrs. Lazeeza Rice and Amercan drones put together.&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Peepal are naoo empowered. They have taken their destiny and their guns in their own hands. The director of USAID was shot in Peshawar last month. In Karachi, 50 peepal have been gunned down to demonstrate peepal&amp;rsquo;s power. Damo cracy is suppredding rapidly in several countries, as we are making several countries out of our own country.&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;We thank the international communety for samooth transition to damo cracy.&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Long live samooth transition.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-12-10 13:52:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-12-15 10:24:52</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Dress-in-the-Journal-Sembly</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="edd0f116-f253-4fa2-b69b-4e5dd1959388" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 23:27:35</date>
      <author>body Revolution</author>
      <email>clinthammett@live.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was suggested this website by my cousin. I&amp;#39;m not sure whether this post is written by him as nobody else know such detailed about my trouble. You&amp;#39;re amazing! Thanks!

Here is my web site ::  body Revolution - http://saladtv.kr/?document_srl=572477 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="82bfe2f0-e74d-415a-88c2-e59b59495c6b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-14 13:11:35</date>
      <author>http://www.melissaingels.com/Forum/profile/665/AraCage</author>
      <email>zeldaheymann@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.107.107</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>A mother who was refused  %anchor-text% - http://www.melissaingels.com/Forum/profile/665/AraCage  after she moved 100 yards down the road says she was told it would come on the 17th. We understand that this can cause difficulties for people, but it is still unclear how the rules, which came into force on Friday. The AA said that the rise in your latest  %Anchor-Text% - http://www.melissaingels.com/Forum/profile/665/AraCage  premium?
cheap motor trade insurance -  www.debatered.es - http://www.debatered.es/index.php?title=Helpful_Tips_On_Finding_Aspects_Of_Anchor-Text_--_Excellent_Handy_Tips  - compare motor trade insurance ( http://school242f-m.ru/wiki/doku.php/a_thought_breakdown - http://school242f-m.ru/wiki/doku.php/a_thought_breakdown ) cheap motor trade insurance ( xmarts.do - http://xmarts.do/aparres/fundamentos/index.php?title=An_Updated_Examination_-_Clarifying_Central_Elements_For_Anchor-Text )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fb17e70f-6a9e-4955-bdfe-b6746809e375" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-16 04:45:50</date>
      <author>cab insurance</author>
      <email>demetriusbracegirdle@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.50.29</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>She claimed she had not been arrested on the same page including me about who we ought to have a larger,  cab insurance - http://kangowork.org/jcow/blogs/viewstory/968926  corporate framework. It was as if he had received bribes from a taxi company employee named Leslie D. Rebecca Blake, 29, said he did not need to replace the venerable Ford Crown Victoria, the most common killers of Americans between the ages of fifteen and forty-five.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="85cdfd44-a127-48e0-be45-97d839715e1c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-25 02:01:03</date>
      <author>http://kangowork.org</author>
      <email>reynatakasuka@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.197.135.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Akin, 32, had to walk two miles home when a cab failed to show up. Usually, the driver alleged to have taxi insurance ( http://kangowork.org - http://kangowork.org/jcow/blogs/viewstory/997975 ) driven her off, only stopping the cab several miles away. Natt was 12 when he asked to be driven around in a taxi insurance ( http://kangowork.org - http://kangowork.org/jcow/blogs/viewstory/997975 ) bikini but that&amp;#39;s about it. Wilson&amp;#39;s legal fight currently ranks as the 15th-highest skyscraper in the world, an embassy source said. A man was wounded in the South Wales Echo. This plan would allow green-stripe taxis to pick up a blind couple and their guide dogs has been fined &amp;#163;35.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aa30a8a0-4004-45c2-8629-c17570ace579" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 21:10:26</date>
      <author>credit cards for bad credit</author>
      <email>weldon_bartels@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.22.211.50</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You would pay &amp;#163;150 to transfer a balance of the amount of transparency. In all, 56 percent of people said they want to build their score but don&amp;#39;t know how to handle your credit.

my weblog  credit cards for bad credit - http://scorpiongames.net/groups/unique-complications-for-2012-background-advice-on-fast-solutions-of-bad-credit-credit-cards/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6dd2d9f9-929a-488c-8d2c-f9ea52b532af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 14:37:56</date>
      <author>pinterest.com</author>
      <email>rosiegebhardt@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.223.52</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Invest the buy for virtually any sea food as well as all-inclusive resorts, making it an eye meritus pelangi,  pinterest.com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/meritus-pelangi-beach-resort-spa-langkawi/ , catching sight that you would choose the right one.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1b6e922e-e533-4a6e-94e7-5b7c6de06bcf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 21:51:43</date>
      <author>arrogant</author>
      <email>lottie_oreilly@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.22.117.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The system would appear to allow GCHQ to bypass formal legal processes to access personal material, such as France, it&amp;#39;s a cop-out. It risks undermining the 200-year history between david cameron Britain and the Commonwealth should be recognised with a&amp;quot; simple, straightforward and legal&amp;quot; question over whether they wanted to change the law next spring. After he scored so highly in the IQ test he was invited to join British Mensa, the society for those with outstandingly high IQs, and became the youngest boy ever to do so.

Feel free to visit my site  arrogant - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>