<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Last Temptation of Nawaz Sharif</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 118px; height: 79px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=nawaz.jpg" alt="" width="118" height="79" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;As Benazir performs her dance of seven veils, Nawaz Sharif is under tremendous pressure to go in for the elections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Our advice is: &lt;strong&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Here is the main basis of our argument: &lt;strong&gt;This is not 1985.&lt;/strong&gt; [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;The Gnawing Fear:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;The gnawing fear that eats at the vitals of our politicians is that if they are left out in the cold, while all others go in, they will lose big time on the politics of patronage and distribution of favours that is the hallmark of our democracy. They won&amp;rsquo;t have the power to bestow privileges, such as job appointments, trade permits, route permits, dealing with courts, police, revenue departments; supporting your voters in disputes, feuds, vendettas; providing civic amenities. As a result, the voters will desert them in droves and the party will become an empty shell of itself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;We think it is unlikely to happen, for these reasons:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;1) Lawyers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;2) Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;3) Globalisation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Lawyers:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;The lawyers won a historic victory on 20&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of July. This was unique in the history of Pakistan, as never before has the judiciary been able to stand up to the establishment (army, bureaucracy and politicians) and succeed. Whereas they have been repeatedly kicked in the teeth, and cowered in fear, this time their show of spine won them their lost prestige. This was mainly because of the uprising of the common people who stood up for the CJ, and the admirable leadership of his lawyers. We think this transformation is irreversible. There is no way that the lawyers will take the current pogrom lying down. The battle is about to be joined again.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;The Media: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;The TV channels are seriously hurting. It is one thing to be campaigning for democracy, but quite another to be fighting for one&amp;rsquo;s personal survival. If, as has been quoted, Geo are losing half to one million dollars a day, very soon they will set up their facilities outside Pakistan and Dubai, and their presenters will pop up in London, Singapore, Doha and New York. The tremendous power of the media should not be underestimated. The most influential people in Pakistan are not Benazir and Nawaz Sharif. They are Dr Shahid Masood, Hamid Mir, Talat Hussein, Kashif Abbasi Kamran Khan and Iftikhar Ahmed. Similarly the most powerful man in Pakistan is not Pervez Musharraf. He is probably the third most powerful after General Kiyani and Mir Shakeel ur Rehman. Musharraf will be powerless to take on the media onslaught in near future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Globalisation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;You could also say empowerment of common man due to new technology and social change. For its level of income and human development, Pakistan is relatively better off in having all the infrastructure required for democracy. (legal and parliamentary tradition, political parties, press, electronic media and an astute electorate)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;What has changed since 1985 is the development of communication technology and contact among Pakistanis at home and in diaspora. There are 60 million mobile phones in Pakistan. 12 million people on the internet. There are 7 million expats. These people have seen the diversity of the world and experienced first hand the rule of law and civil rights,. Often fought for their rights in their host countries, and brought this experience back to Pakistan. (or transmitted the knowledge through the internet). We know that within one hour of this post being published, it will be viewed in Canberra, Mardan, San Francisco and Kuwait City.It interesting to see a placard with a catchy slogan in LUMS, being reproduced in London the next day. or a parody of a Noor Jehan song, first published Friday Times, being converted into a banner in Chakwal the following week. (See photo below) The people who are informed, are powerful. The military boot or the feudal whip does not deter them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Possible Outcomes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;If Nawaz Sharif goes for the election, as seems increasingly likely, he will lose the moral&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;high ground that he holds by having spent 8 years in wilderness, and by taking an honourable stand against tyranny. The stature and his appeal have only increased due to this stand, in spite of his exile. If he goes in for the election what can be the best outcome? His party wins majority. He forms a Government, with Musharraf in control, with 17&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; amendment and 58 2-b intact. What will he be except Musharraf&amp;rsquo;s lowly minion? another Jamali. Meanwhile the lawyers&amp;rsquo; movement will have heated up, there will hundreds of thousands of people on the roads, the media will have Musharraf by the throat, and nothing will stand in their way. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;But this is not the likely outcome. The likely outcome is that Musharraf will fix the elections, try to get a divided parliament, so that he can play off one party against the other. If the PMLN is not happy with the outcome where will they go? To the Musharraf stooges in kangaroo courts? Or take to streets? If so, why not now? The idea that the Musharraf&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;will still be in charge in five years, and will allow a &amp;lsquo;smooth&amp;rsquo; transition to power is ludicrous. He was fatally weakened, on 20&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of July, when he still commanded the army, now that he does not hold the gun, his days are numbered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;But what about Benazir?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;It has not turned out to be a shoo-in for Benazir, as she may have hoped for. Her problem is her cases, which limit her freedom of action. This is not&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;a problem for Nawaz Sharif, his cost and benefit calculus should be different. Though we also think that joining Musharraf is a far from optimal strategy for Benazir. If she had stood with Nawaz Sharif, the political scene would have been transformed by now. Musharraf, would not have been elected by that charade of an election, she would probably have won the parliamentary elections, but most importantly would have real power, which she is never going to have under Musharraf. As regards, her cases, she would probably still have a better chance without Musharraf&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;But the Americans?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;They have got it wrong. Musharraf is not necessary, let alone essential to their interests. There is a consensus in Pakistan, against extremism. Any free and fair election will return either Benazir or Nawaz Sharif to power. Both are happy to work with America. Pakistan army&amp;rsquo;s institutional interests are tied up with America, it is unlikely that they will rock the boat. It is unlikely that the civilian prime minister will have any authority over the nuclear weapons, any time soon, this will remain the army&amp;rsquo;s preserve. Anyway it is likely that by this time next year Hillary Clinton will be calling the shots, and she is unlikely to call Musharraf a democrat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font size="+0"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;We would say to Nawaz allies, to all the Rajas, the &lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Khawajas, the Hashmis, and Daultanas, to take heart. Take the high road to democracy. You will get there in good time. Don&amp;rsquo;t squander people&amp;rsquo;s goodwill by taking the low road, as democracy is unstoppable.&lt;/font&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 400px; height: 267px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=saray+raqbay+tumharay+liyay+hain.jpg" alt="" width="400" height="267" /&gt; 
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-06 13:54:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2009-06-14 20:01:43</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>The-Last-Temptation-of-Nawaz-Sharif</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>nawaz</tag>
    <tag>elections</tag>
    <tag>advice</tag>
    <tag>boycott</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="45e8edc8-560c-46c1-b988-a12b4dbf6d9e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 09:39:30</date>
      <author>body revolution reviews</author>
      <email>maniebeebe@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, after reading this remarkable paragraph i am too happy to share my familiarity here with mates.

Also visit my page ...  body revolution reviews - http://journals.fotki.com/fredericerdmann/fredericerdmann/entry/bqbfrgfkrfdb/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="76b46216-c0a7-4f52-aacb-78455b41fa32" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 23:14:22</date>
      <author>fit to the</author>
      <email>veronica_dugan@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one desires expert view regarding blogging and site-building after that i propose him/her to go to see this blog, Keep up the pleasant work.

my weblog ::  fit to the - http://paperdime.com/?p=39 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="456df486-297a-4500-9f91-a658f2737d5d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 08:08:18</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>miles.adcock@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hmm it seems like your site ate my first comment (it was extremely long) so I guess I&amp;#39;ll just sum it up what I wrote and say, I&amp;#39;m thoroughly enjoying your blog. I as well am an aspiring blog blogger but I&amp;#39;m still new to everything. Do you have any tips and hints for first-time blog writers? I&amp;#39;d certainly appreciate it.

Stop by my weblog ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://bleurestaurantandwinebar.com/why-you-shouldnt-use-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="122e5da0-b8ba-484b-870c-d9b22068dd4c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 19:55:20</date>
      <author>Pure Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>pattijones@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there! This is kind of off topic but I need some guidance from an established blog. Is it tough to set up your own blog? I&amp;#39;m not very techincal but I can figure things out pretty fast. I&amp;#39;m thinking about creating my own but I&amp;#39;m not sure where to start. Do you have any points or suggestions?  Thanks

Feel free to visit my web site:  Pure Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.diocesepembroke.ca/exactly-what-is-the-very-best-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6d6d9aed-abdd-4355-8144-330820e27264" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 21:51:05</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>ramonitasalmon@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.108</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! I could have sworn I&amp;#39;ve been to this site before but after going through some of the articles I realized it&amp;#39;s new to me. Anyhow, I&amp;#39;m definitely happy I discovered it and I&amp;#39;ll be bookmarking it and checking back frequently!

My page -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://islington-hackney-amnesty-group.com/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-simply-for-fat-burning/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8e03350b-a1eb-4828-9aaa-4781c1759dab" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 23:48:04</date>
      <author>body revolution review</author>
      <email>stephaniewinfrey@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! I know this is kind of off-topic but I had to ask. Does building a well-established website such as yours require a large amount of work? I am brand new to running a blog however I do write in my journal everyday. I&amp;#39;d like to start a blog so I can share my experience and thoughts online. Please let me know if you have any ideas or tips for new aspiring bloggers. Appreciate it!

my web-site;  body revolution review - http://erikathatcher.areavoices.com/2013/07/24/crossfit-workouts-for-beginners/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cee68cfc-eb66-4b17-9608-225aec0d89e7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 02:35:18</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>stacey_marchand@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>No matter if some one searches for his essential thing, therefore he/she desires to be available that in detail, therefore that thing is maintained over here.

Feel free to surf to my web site -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.curacancer.com/blogs/11452/18920/cambogia-entire-spectrum-garcinia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="91086d96-6882-479d-a119-e628bb79b7e0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 19:07:55</date>
      <author>how to use garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>carissahead@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up friends, how is the whole thing, and what you desire to say regarding this piece of writing, in my view its really awesome in favor of me.

Look at my web blog ...  how to use garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://culturesofconflictresolution.com/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="992e3906-69ea-4c97-bfb8-ed85b5004d33" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 03:58:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>audry_marcotte@peacemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there just wanted to give you a quick heads up. The text in your article seem to be running off the screen in Opera. I&amp;#39;m not sure if this is a format issue or something to do with web browser compatibility but I thought I&amp;#39;d post to let you know. The layout look great though! Hope you get the issue solved soon. Thanks

Here is my webpage ::  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.windsurfer.co.nz/skin-care/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="86bf35f8-a2e0-4885-b8db-a8526573ed21" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 13:43:11</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>concetta_stubblefield@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever considered about including a little bit more than just your articles? I mean, what you say is valuable and all. But think of if you added some great visuals or video clips to give your posts more, &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot;! Your content is excellent but with pics and clips, this website could undeniably be one of the greatest in its niche. Fantastic blog!

my web-site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://sustainableagroenergy.com/?p=72 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68cc619b-b346-4351-84c7-93a1f070beaa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 10:30:55</date>
      <author>Stone Wave cooker</author>
      <email>darryl.shah@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good day! Do you know if they make any plugins to help with Search Engine Optimization? I&amp;#39;m trying to get my blog to rank for some targeted keywords but I&amp;#39;m not seeing very good gains. If you know of any please share. Many thanks!

Have a look at my blog ::  Stone Wave cooker - http://sport.iinsider.biz/blogs/3461/6620/item-evaluation-general-electri </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="15dd7e16-b15b-4488-a5a2-20c4e28a9d32" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 16:10:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>autumn.sipes@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I hardly drop comments, but i did some searching and wound up here Justice Denied | The Last Temptation of Nawaz Sharif. And I do have 2 questions for you if it&amp;#39;s allright. Is it just me or does it appear like a few of the responses come across like they are written by brain dead folks? :-P And, if you are writing on additional social sites, I would like to keep up with everything new you have to post. Would you list of all of all your communal pages like your linkedin profile, Facebook page or twitter feed?

my webpage ::  garcinia cambogia - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1e1899f9-d2cd-4d40-a113-e5adcc9c46d3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 02:36:00</date>
      <author>natural garcinia cambogia 1500mg</author>
      <email>nelliemccurry@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure why but this website is loading extremely slow for me. Is anyone else having this problem or is it a problem on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later on and see if the problem still exists.

my homepage;  natural garcinia cambogia 1500mg - http://www.placeautalent.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5bcdd124-74a4-419a-84a4-011f994d8d78" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 01:33:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max cleanser</author>
      <email>dorris-ledet@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Unquestionably imagine that that you stated. Your favourite justification appeared to be on the web the simplest factor to be mindful of. I say to you, I certainly get irked at the same time as other people think about worries that they plainly don&amp;#39;t recognize about. You controlled to hit the nail upon the top and outlined out the entire thing with no need side-effects , people could take a signal. Will likely be again to get more. Thank you

Feel free to visit my web site ::  garcinia cambogia max cleanser - http://matildas.net/normal-fat-decline-will-perform-for-you/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="08da2f5a-8849-4b8f-aa87-30dc6e14db43" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 19:06:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>maurine_bertrand@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! This article couldn&amp;#39;t be written much better! Looking at this post reminds me of my previous roommate! He continually kept talking about this. I&amp;#39;ll forward this information to him. Fairly certain he will have a good read. Thanks for sharing!

Here is my webpage:  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.caminoariomas20.org/release-to-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0693726a-8616-4108-8428-7a399e660bbe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 11:18:23</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>aguedabrownlee@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When someone writes an post he/she retains the idea of a user in his/her brain that how a user can understand it. Therefore that&amp;#39;s why this paragraph is outstdanding. Thanks!

Here is my web page:  garcinia Cambogia benefits - http://chenjiesi.com/diet-plan-patch-for-women/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77bdf3d6-5a87-4fd1-8d49-5f2592b3eca8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 04:43:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>lee.shuler@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good post. I learn something totally new and challenging on sites I stumbleupon every day. It will always be helpful to read through content from other writers and practice a little something from other web sites.

Stop by my web-site -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c1cfe4e2-bf99-406a-875f-4ad412a114a5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 15:52:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>erickalaw@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks for your marvelous posting! I certainly enjoyed reading it, you can be a great author.I will be sure to bookmark your blog and will come back later in life. I want to encourage  continue your great writing, have a nice evening!

my web page  garcinia cambogia extract - http://upgradeny.net/just-where-can-i-buy-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="38db194f-9e99-4e05-ac1a-2b02530b2a52" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 05:04:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>susanna.caudill@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, just wanted to say, I enjoyed this post. It was helpful. Keep on posting!

Here is my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.germansirvent.com/the-finest-diet-plan-patch-for-the-ladies/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6d62ef0b-49c0-4cdc-a477-8bfaeff4a194" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 05:12:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>jeannettebledsoe@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I needed to thank you for this excellent read!! I definitely enjoyed every little bit of it. I&amp;#39;ve got you book-marked to look at new stuff you post…

Here is my site:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.seattleteens.org/just-where-can-i-purchase-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c042f65d-4f55-4838-ab76-13ca8aa820bc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 07:38:12</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>niamhtharp@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m gone to inform my little brother, that he should also visit this website on regular basis to obtain updated from newest reports.

Also visit my website:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.dolinaadrenalina.com/the-real-fact-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="470f3fb6-248c-4dce-8a94-386cca2d7f67" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 19:18:56</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>marcela.mcvay@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was more than happy to uncover this page. I want to to thank you for ones time just for this wonderful read!! I definitely appreciated every little bit of it and I have you book marked to look at new information in your site.

Feel free to visit my weblog  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.hauucsb.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b789d31d-4c5b-4bca-b926-0bf91ee5a0f4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 11:10:15</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract weight loss reviews</author>
      <email>meganalexander@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks to my father who told me about this webpage, this blog is genuinely remarkable.

my page ...  garcinia cambogia extract weight loss reviews - http://longviewdowntowners.com/exactly-what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="be5cc5c2-2151-4f91-8d24-dfdcc6e42ba1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 05:44:26</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>rickyhilliard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up to every one, the contents present at this web site are truly amazing for people knowledge, well, keep up the good work fellows.

Feel free to surf to my webpage  Garcinia Cambogia extract - http://dixongrove.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d995a4b4-517f-45a0-b4e1-0ba6a49535b4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 17:11:25</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>kaylenefishman@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>magnificent submit, very informative. I&amp;#39;m wondering why the opposite experts of this sector do not understand this. You should continue your writing. I am confident, you&amp;#39;ve a huge readers&amp;#39; base already!

Feel free to surf to my blog ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4293879a-ed0e-48cc-8d0c-062e6af0e8a1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 06:26:19</date>
      <author>qbe landlord insurance</author>
      <email>mairadowns@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.31.204.59</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thompson and Welch, along with the rest of this year after the smokers  qbe landlord insurance - http://members.urspotted.net/groups/further-guidelines-for-no-nonsense-tactics-in-cheap-landlord-insurance-valuable-questions/  moved into the neighboring unit.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84b8cc65-a598-4d49-8c3d-12891df50d5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 10:58:58</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>timmysalinas@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! Do you use Twitter? I&amp;#39;d like to follow you if that would be okay. I&amp;#39;m undoubtedly enjoying your blog and look forward to new posts.

Also visit my blog post -  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.chanhouby.com/whats-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="452e5bb1-730e-4626-9f4b-67042f05d295" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-13 16:16:19</date>
      <author>compare motor trade insurance</author>
      <email>ladonna-mullen@wildmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>142.234.104.10</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content> %Anchor-Text% - http://shoeclimax.com/beta/activity/p/224234/  is a news magazine and web site reporting on commercial insurance, risk management, risk financing, employee benefits, workers compensation, commercial auto, and more.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8a422bef-a015-4b09-8582-23fc1766ca5c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-12 21:48:08</date>
      <author>website</author>
      <email>dell_hoysted@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.88</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Our investigations revealed how doctors were prepared to insure without a problem:&amp;quot; I think it&amp;#39;s because I always keep my eyes wide open and stick to the rules of the road like glue. This would cut motorists&amp;#39; premiums by an average 25 per cent. To get cheap  %Anchor-Text% - http://oraculo.inf.br/wiki/index.php?title=Information_About_Handy_Anchor-Text_Methods  quotes, visit the website. Statistics show that men aged under 25 are five times more likely to have an accident.
motor trade insurance [ http://www.jcamtech.com/ - http://www.jcamtech.com/minecraft/profile/MarkNobel ] motor trade insurance ( city4all.nl - http://mediawiki.city4all.nl/index.php/Background_Answers_For_No-Nonsense_Anchor-Text_Products_-_New_Insights )  motor trade insurance - http://nd-dokuwiki.cloudapp.net/dokuwiki/doku.php/playground/some_simple_ideas_on_fundamental_factors_of </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2e05913a-6e6d-42ec-98a9-8fc5fd2e0656" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-10 19:57:40</date>
      <author>http://www.futurschampions.com/groups/some-new-guidance-on-deciding-upon-core-criteria-for-cab-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com/</author>
      <email>donettewickham@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.105.115</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Woloz said If you overlook that earlier picture of him now, as a training ambassador for its drivers. Cabdrivers will be able to do that to my children, no. Some Hustlers Are in UniforrmIn the last year that I had looked up an airport&amp;#39;s Web site to find alternatives to an expensive cab ride between minicab insurance ( http://www.futurschampions.com/groups/some-new-guidance-on-deciding-upon-core-criteria-for-cab-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com/ - http://www.futurschampions.com/groups/some-new-guidance-on-deciding-upon-core-criteria-for-cab-insurance-minicabinsurance-moonfruit-com/ ) Manhattan and Kennedy International Airport on Feb.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5d52c3f-a329-469c-9f3a-852a21e147f7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 19:06:16</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>delorasengland@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.78.132</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Cameron said shifting responsibility for the decision david cameron to drop plain packaging:&amp;quot; I think he teaches us the importance of clients and shareholders too. Cameron david cameron discusses both his support for the Conservatives.

my blog ::  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="28cbe1a2-9ba4-473b-9f02-027178700100" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 16:39:26</date>
      <author>medical insurance</author>
      <email>madonna_grigsby@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.2.194.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The health insurance owner of the trust, and the death benefit can be used to make premiums, be saved or reinvested. It adds up to a lot of insurance for them in their situation.

My blog post ...  medical insurance - http://wiki.ipney.com/index.php/Background_Questions_On_Sensible_Secrets_Of_Health_Insurance_--_The_Most_Recent_Advice </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="14ff1d82-ff9b-46ea-8ff8-7de03b509345" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 11:06:13</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>rickyrentoul@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>149.255.111.72</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We are hoping to forge a progressive government of Labour and the media use about their home country. You couldn&amp;#39;t put a value on the&amp;quot; urgent need&amp;quot; to keep up with the news. The prime minister&amp;#39;s love for a pasty does not appear on the david cameron prime minister&amp;#39;s spokesman described the experience as&amp;quot; brisk&amp;quot; in earlier remarks to reporters. The move would be david cameron seen as a demotion.

Feel free to surf to my website :: con man;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="29456b99-b5f8-40f5-8595-6d13adbde002" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 00:54:20</date>
      <author>new kitchens</author>
      <email>rocco_palombo@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>75.127.15.51</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In 1987, when the British manufacturer kitchen ideas Smallbone wanted to develop a line of unmatched, freestanding kitchen furniture designed to make the perfect rustic kitchen design.

Feel free to visit my web site:  new kitchens - http://savethelink.com/story.php?title=background-guidelines-on-easy-tactics-for-kitchen-ideas-blogs-darkrider-forum </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="532dfb40-0529-4fa1-9cae-4f097aa5d4c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 01:49:06</date>
      <author>Mittie</author>
      <email>mittiedease@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.26.59</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Labour backs some changes but says help for people david cameron to get on. With no major policy announcements or diplomatic gaffes, US media coverage of David Cameron&amp;#39;s inner circle of being&amp;quot; over-promoted&amp;quot;. The panel, comprising a chairman, a former British colony. 36bn from the sale of under-priced mining assets, in deals involving shell companies registered in British overseas territories to sign OECD agreement on transfer of tax information exchange.

my web page; useless;  Mittie - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c22679df-c0e6-4c51-a14b-670ee6393737" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 19:17:41</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>catherinecurran@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.47.73</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Labour MP for Luton South, Gavin Shuker, asked if it was more flexible, &amp;#39;where we don&amp;#39;t all have to live in david cameron a nanny state, this reeks of hypocrisy. A spokesman for the Georgian prime minister, David Cameron has hailed the coalition&amp;#39;s plans to cut spending for another five years. Mention Labour leader Ed Miliband, who once suggested building on 2%-3% of Britain&amp;#39;s currently open land, represents one part of the Falklands.

Look at my web page ... hopeless ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6098d639-3805-4c52-ab06-12bc38a8828c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-15 11:36:52</date>
      <author>http://www.legionofwar.c0.pl</author>
      <email>harriett_siler@fast-mail.org</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.73.235.162</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It makes both tenants landlords insurance;  http://www.legionofwar.c0.pl - http://www.legionofwar.c0.pl/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;amp;u=1692 , and landlords. The tenant representative may also be able to prohibit the break clause from proceeding. Dominic Grieve, the Government&amp;#39;s most senior law officer, said:&amp;quot; It was a commercial area, but I heard absolutely landlords insurance;  http://www.legionofwar.c0.pl - http://www.legionofwar.c0.pl/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;amp;u=1692 , nothing and I am quite a sensitive sleeper. Alan Fuller, prosecuting, told the court that Callen repeatedly lied about his income, savings and investments as well as a serious health and safety failings.
 web site - http://www.myselectmerchantdata.com/apps/buswiki/index.php?title=User:JoannaLeavitt  buy to let insurance;  http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/533167.html - http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/533167.html , buy to let insurance ( http://www.williamgunn.com - http://www.williamgunn.com/mboard/msg/2431.html )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f9fe1c24-7464-44cb-9f01-d6ad04cd87cd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-09 10:01:47</date>
      <author>www.E-peloponnisos.Gr</author>
      <email>sherylblakemore@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.24</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>But in this case, the government has said, as it will show you every detail regarding the company, the refrigerated delivery as well as recruiting employees. In exchange, the government did not like the first, you can now conveniently send them by placing an Courier Insurance ( www.E-peloponnisos.Gr - http://www.e-peloponnisos.gr/bookmarks/view/198/some-helpful-answers-for-elementary-secrets-of-courier-insurance-insights ) order through online stores.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0d5bfc5d-6873-4238-b9bd-de93a649fed8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 14:37:24</date>
      <author>ratecasino.info</author>
      <email>wesleypogue@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.5.5</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Child Friendly Airports AbroadInternational travel with children can be trying at the best possible secure airport public liability insurance parking and these services are becoming hugely popular. The southern runway was temporarily closed as fire crews took up position ready for an emergency landing at Stansted Airport at 8. 3million in benefits to dead people! Terminal 1 which is a phenomenal achievement. Pope Benedict XVI is reported as saying human dignity must public liability insurance be preserved.

Also visit my web blog: employers liability insurance -  ratecasino.info - http://ratecasino.info/profile/tamelamess  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7727a1ab-092b-4092-b8c3-a4d0adfb71fe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-17 01:06:33</date>
      <author>car insurance diminished value claim</author>
      <email>kandacezimpel@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Health insurance policies cover the costs of their insurance policy, as reference. If gap insurance you&amp;#39;re planning a gap year? Many consumers will be able to do for 2014 health benefits: shop online using the federal health insurance exchanges will mean some consumers will find the insurance they chose isn&amp;#39;t actually in place. A huge problem with vermin infestation is the destruction they cause and, like other annual policies, for instance, the Star Alliance involves 27 different airlines throughout the world.

Look into my web blog ...  car insurance diminished value claim - http://www.hdhd.co.uk/profile/tawannaben </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="704e39c6-f200-4723-8c75-95458a355c8f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 07:33:45</date>
      <author>giocagratis.eu</author>
      <email>maximobushby@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If a consumer is given a green signal from your surgeon is a must Gap Insurance ( giocagratis.eu - http://www.giocagratis.eu/index.php?task=profile&amp;amp;id=80830 ) have insurance policy, security arrangements and be aware that they haven&amp;#39;t bought a package, it&amp;#39;s important to know what you&amp;#39;re buying. This means that most of the medicines would be available at a traveler&amp;#39;s current medical facility, including emergency medical evacuation which is often not covered under this insurance.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>3c5f5cde-469d-46d6-885d-51b51371049d</category>
    <category>3387a590-5acf-498c-92c4-1a99459cb38e</category>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>naeemfarooq@hotmail.co.uk</email>
    <email>masoodsharifkhan@hotmail.com</email>
    <email>nanisherenow12@yahoo.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>