<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Qisas or Bust </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;img style="color: #000000; font-size: 10px;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2014%2f11%2fQisas+or+Bust++.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #3e454c; font-size: 13.5pt;"&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #3e454c; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13.5pt;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;The angels of Allah SWT carried my throne from Chaklala International Airport to the JFK. There were prominent leaders of Islam gathered in force to greet Yours Truly, including Rev. Jerry Falwell and Pat Robertson, may Allah be pleased with them. These are the people who have undergone privations and hardship, but have lit the candle of Islam in dark corners of the North American television.&amp;nbsp; I have started a coast to coast journey, where I will pay homage to our foregone heroes especially John Wilkes Booth and Lee Harvey Oswald who fought against the oppression of their day, against the egregious violations of articles 62 and 63 and brought a revolution to provide justice to the masses. If we follow in their footsteps, we can bring the same revolution to our beloved country, Canada, for which our ancestors had laid down their lives. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;Our dissolute leaders are completely oblivious to the threat facing us across the border. They have thrown national interest to the wind in pursuit of the so called trade and building their own business empires. We will resist the aggression and the cultural degradation of our society by our large neighbour by all possible means. It should be remembered that we are a nuclear power and our resolve and determination should not be underestimated. We will fight them in El Passo. We will fight them in Rio Grande and will fight them in Tijuana. The sanctity of the Line of Control in Arizona will not be allowed to be violated. Anyone trying to cross into the land of the pure will be shot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;A million people will march onto our capital which has been made a seat of infamy by those who are in power. We demand qisas for the atrocities committed in the name of governance by the mayor Mr. Rob Ford. Diyat is not an option. He has made a mockery of Islam by appearing drunk in public by dragging the name of Islam&amp;rsquo;s greatest capital in dirt. He will face Allah&amp;rsquo;s justice. I invite people from all corners of the country to come to the capital. They should come on their power bikes, on their SUVs on their vacation homes and on their snow sledges. We will bring revolution to the country by constitutional means. We will, inshallah, ask Maulana Tahir Ashrafi, (whilst sober), to sit on the mayor in a peaceful manner, till he reforms his ways. Islam is a religion of peace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;The community in the UK is the backbone of the Ummah. On my return journey, I will make a sojourn in the holy harem of London. I will go and kiss the hem of the Shamsul Ulama, Rt. Hon. David Lidington MP, who heads the Foreign and Commonwealth office and is happy to be milked by the faithful of the Ummah for large sums of sterling pounds in lieu of issuing fatwas against the barbarians who dictates of sharia in the far reaches of the empire. There will be an awesome qawwali in the DIFID office.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif; color: #222222;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13.5pt; font-family: Helvetica, sans-serif; color: #3e454c;"&gt;All night long.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-11-02 09:55:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-11-02 09:57:28</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Qisas-or-Bust-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="55da5b62-949a-471a-b2f5-80dacc0bbf39" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-08-01 03:44:23</date>
      <author>compare lorry insurance</author>
      <email>ila_mccartney@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>155.73.2.142</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Every weekend i used to visit this web site, for the reason that i want enjoyment, as this this website conations in fact fastidious funny stuff too.

my site:  compare lorry insurance - https://www.instapaper.com/read/602375545 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c408e0e0-6687-4fe1-bc81-500cc6d2cace" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-02-20 14:04:37</date>
      <author>famous war speeches in movies</author>
      <email>partheniafogarty@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>191.101.107.208</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>As you continue scanning, you&amp;#39;ll uncover some hints that ought to be quite useful as you try to write a speech that the folks in your viewers will always remember.  Look into my web blog -  famous war speeches in movies - http://bestsns.kr/main/?document_srl=1569697 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="23e8d329-af4c-4e2a-b68b-24216f3318fb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-04-01 21:11:40</date>
      <author>http://adostina.eu/</author>
      <email>rosaria_scott@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.182.231.92</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s especially hard if you think like you&amp;#39;re only teacher with your school to attempt fitting technologies into the planning and classroom delivery. Make any final announcements (for example, the following webinar in a very series).  Depending on the size and scope of the organization, these improvements can yield significant ROI.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e751c87e-30dc-4105-bf72-68d46edc5329" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-03 23:21:54</date>
      <author>workwithbryanbracken.com</author>
      <email>lashundacrick@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>176.115.100.135</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Job hunters could also setup their very own account, upload their resume, and setup notifications. Make any final announcements (for instance, the subsequent webinar in a very series).  It was foreseen that this quantity of 3D printers in homes and business establishments increases rapidly.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="029a7ef5-f92f-4330-ad4f-d882ab7a3228" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-27 23:32:25</date>
      <author>ECU Failures</author>
      <email>elwoodreddy@t-online.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.158.148.146</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up mates, good piece of writing and fastidious urging commented at this place, I am really enjoying by these.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6a3d9673-10e0-4e2d-a870-3d8b2447d7e7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-08 12:40:24</date>
      <author>paintball</author>
      <email>waylonmerrett@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>179.218.219.204</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I read this post fully regarding the difference of newest and previous technologies, it&amp;#39;s awesome article.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7ccc8823-d78d-440e-aac8-fc4cd75fb061" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-21 16:08:18</date>
      <author>Chris</author>
      <email>diannebloomfield@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>191.101.73.234</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>You can certainly see your expertise in the work you write. The arena hopes for even more passionate writers such as you who are not afraid to mention how they believe. All the time follow your heart.  Also visit my website ... Аренда квартир в Аликанте ( Chris - http://www.zgyssyw.com/home.php?mod=space&amp;amp;uid=160737&amp;amp;do=profile )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2f4b990a-e3c4-4e34-b14d-510776eb265a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-29 11:39:29</date>
      <author>backlink for amazon</author>
      <email>chastityfountain@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>179.159.225.77</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>My favorite websites that supply a reverse phone lookup are Redgage (that offers a second income via page views rather that Ad - Sense), She - Told - Me and Xomba (despite links being No - Follow, the links are rapidly listed in Google). Backlinking and choosing the best keywords go further to giving you better google search rankings.  The number of quality backlinks a specific website has can dictate its overall popularity among engines like google and its particular visibility  backlink for amazon - https://www.fiverr.com/cldisplay_seo/build-25-to-30-real-high-authority-backlinks-for-your-site  potential buyers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6bf6443b-a7b1-471a-972e-5059ba21e80d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-01-12 09:54:28</date>
      <author>Johny Jackson</author>
      <email>ceciliaheysen@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>88.80.20.195</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>When I originally commented I appear to have clicked the -Notify me when new comments are added- checkbox and now every time a comment is added I recieve 4 emails with the same comment. Perhaps there is an easy method you can remove me from that service? Cheers!  Check out my page  Johny Jackson - http://bit.ly/2EWLfYx </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>