<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Pious Goats of Southall</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style="border: 0px initial initial;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2011%2f4%2fgoat400x300.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Letter to Brother Abdullah&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Jalalatul Mulk, Malik Abdulla bin Abdul Aziz Sahib, please accept greetings from you fond brother, pining in your love and longing to be with you. Also, Salama Laikum from your Bhabi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I am very well in the holy city of London and partaking of the divine gifts such as nihari in the holy borough of Southhall. The angioplasty has gone well. Brother Shahbaz &lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;has a firm hand at the helm in Raiwind and Brother Davis is cooling his heels in Colorado. God bless the hands and heels of the faithful of the Ummah and feed them the heads and feet of the pious goats of Southhall, so that they prosper in this world and the next. [more]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I hear that Brother Field Marshal has promised two infantry divisions. I am overjoyed to hear the news. The indomitable soldiers of Islam will never demur from opening fire on the enemies of the Ummah, as they surge towards the Riyadh Palace shouting democracy, human rights, freedom of speech and similar decadent slogans. They will use the G3 rifles produced in the blessed Wah factory to snuff out these dangerous notions. The enemies of the Ummah will be given no quarter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I congratulate Your Majesty to have applied your steadying hand in Bahrain. Decisive action needs to be taken to prevent the poison from spreading. Bother Hammad needs support. If he leaves on board the Fifth Fleet, it will be an unmitigated disaster for the Ummah. Woe betide the day that people with dubious faith take control in Bahrain and impious, reprobate women drive in the streets of Riyadh in open top cars, with their abayas trailing in the wind. This will be a setback for the Ummah, the like of which has never been seen since the fall of Bagdad at the hands of Halaku Khan, or the loss of the Islamic Republic in the Semi Finals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I must admit your Majesty, that there is a fear, gnawing at your brother&amp;rsquo;s heart. There are examples in our history where our soldiers have disregarded the law and teachings of the True Faith and taken the reins of the Ummah in their own hands. In the contemporary history of the Ummah, the latest example of that is when your bother was sent on a compulsory Haj, although he had been to several voluntary Hajs already. After Bairam Khan, your brother was the first leader in the Ummah to have suffered this appalling travesty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;It would be wise counsel to guard against such a possibility by posting the two divisions at the Yemen border or at the Dhahran base, and not in Riyadh. If you hear as much as whiff of the phrase &amp;lsquo;90 days&amp;rsquo;, you should act swiftly and sit your royal person on the GOC, till he comes back into the fold of the True Faith. &lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;May God preserve your shadow on Earth. May God preserve the pipeline to the Islamic Republic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Your True Brother,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;MMN Sharif,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Of the Order of the Pious Goat,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Currently domiciled in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The Islamic Republic of South Hall&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;img style="border: 0px initial initial;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2011%2f4%2fimages.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;a href="http://justicedeniedpk.com/JDP/search.aspx?q=hazik&amp;amp;page=1"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: &amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;; mso-ascii-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-hansi-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-bidi-font-family: Arial; mso-bidi-theme-font: minor-bidi;"&gt;More articles by &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: &amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;; mso-ascii-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-hansi-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-bidi-theme-font: minor-bidi;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; line-height: 115%; font-family: &amp;quot;Arial&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;; mso-ascii-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-hansi-theme-font: minor-bidi; mso-bidi-font-family: Arial; mso-bidi-theme-font: minor-bidi;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2011-04-16 01:48:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-04-16 20:08:22</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>The-Pious-Goats-of-Southall</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="60462522-609f-41cb-ac4a-0374ac029e89" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-16 11:08:22</date>
      <author>M Saqib </author>
      <email>saqib50@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>24.115.199.131</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Absolutely brilliant! </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="867d08d3-bb7c-4a44-af3a-5ac2d5beabf2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-17 04:25:29</date>
      <author>ayub</author>
      <email>ayubawan@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>92.17.37.130</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:white list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>amazing.
Ayub</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="35f1eec1-6a93-4d29-9efe-42389966a71b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-07-07 03:27:25</date>
      <author>ricky</author>
      <email>themebazaar@gmail.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>119.152.36.195</ip>
      <website>http://www.themebazaar.net/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is excellent post, I know it will help me personally. I am going to share this with my friends.

We develope high end themes, we provide the finest WordPress Themes and continuous support so you can continue your website and update it with no hassle! Our Magento, Wordpress, Drupal themes are upto date with current trends and are very professional. We design very clean, elegant and futuristic designs that can be fully custimezed to any CMS. We also provide custome development for Magento, wordpress, Drupal.Theming, Development and Installation.

services:

website design, ecommerce website, shopping cart website, logo design, web designs, CMS, web design agency, application developer, mobile applications developer, online shopping sites, psd web designs,xhtml, css designs, magento designs</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="65b364cc-9731-44b4-a210-05b23f2c86e2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 14:57:48</date>
      <author>Acheter Air Jordan 3 Pas Cher</author>
      <email>maurice.bethea@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.106.178</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The first time I met with the shoes is very fashion and nice, all are the new style for the Nike Considered line utilized in its viral marketing campaign. Now that you have a Nike maillot air jordan pas cherv Styles. Considering that 1987, Nike Airforce 1&amp;#39;s are one more superior brand of sneakers which present superb assistance in addition to cushioning mid soles. According to Kicks on Fire, one of the best brand in the market for an exclusive girls only footwear brand. For Nike, these football shoes is more and more people to buy it.

My web page ::  Acheter Air Jordan 3 Pas Cher - http://idris-c.com/Acheter-Air-Jordan-3-Pas-Cher.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bf7991c0-ebf4-4179-abd2-3c45b763af6b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 15:05:02</date>
      <author>Air Jordan 4 White Cement Achat</author>
      <email>abelmasterson@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.106.178</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In addition to a distinctively sexy aesthetic, air jordan retro shoes are well-known for being dressy and fit for evening gown. Blahnik Boots How surprise for you, If you want to have excepting for this pair of shoes that I adore.

Feel free to visit my weblog:  Air Jordan 4 White Cement Achat - http://piscinassanchez.com/Air-Jordan-4-White-Cement-Achat.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3aa1358d-33ff-4af7-9adc-25bea5f00561" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-21 11:04:27</date>
      <author>ankara matematik dersi</author>
      <email>dominga_storey@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>69.12.66.40</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>My brother suggested I may like this website. He was entirely right. This submit truly made my day. You cann&amp;#39;t believe just how much time I had spent for this info! Thanks!

Feel free to visit my website -  ankara matematik dersi - http://matematik-dersi.8ra.org/tag/cayyolu-matematik-ozel-ders/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="21ac7167-920f-4bf6-999a-3b4266642b9e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-08-19 06:31:42</date>
      <author>START EARNING MONEY ONLINE TODAY</author>
      <email>larrytapp@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.240.207.244</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one wishes expert view on the topic of blogging then i recommend him/her to pay a visit this weblog, Keep up the good work.

Stop by my web page;  START EARNING MONEY ONLINE TODAY - http://bonusbagging.ra6.org </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f0490005-ddb9-4852-95fa-5098fb941d58" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-14 04:16:51</date>
      <author>ankara icra avukatları</author>
      <email>katlynrohu@ftml.net</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.94.23.18</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks for sharing your thoughts on peasant. Regards

Visit my web blog ...  ankara icra avukatları - http://ankaraavukat.6ra.org/page/3/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e417cecb-cf5e-4cd6-abb5-630839204d9c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-08 23:08:43</date>
      <author>weight loss acupuncture</author>
      <email>shauntebaynes@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.232.255.63</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Family and friends may be the best resource in accomplishing your goal. Before you could start along with your  weight loss acupuncture - http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Weight_cutting  loss program and burning off surplus fat from the body generally, you must learn why you have fat around your belly in the first place. You will quickly realize that there are lots of things which need to come together in order to get rid of the weight in case you select one thing to truly master at a time you will discover your confidence soars.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77e011be-037c-4209-a765-33a6f94de771" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-02 16:58:14</date>
      <author>boşanma avukatı ankara</author>
      <email>sherryl_kaufman@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.94.248.22</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Fantastic beat ! I would like to apprentice while you amend your web site, how can i subscribe for a weblog site? The account aided me a applicable deal. I have been tiny bit acquainted of this your broadcast provided shiny clear concept</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4f241a21-be00-4575-81d3-0beeaa420e61" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-23 08:24:44</date>
      <author>bosanma avukatlari ankara</author>
      <email>carl_augustine@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.102.103.190</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Today, I went to the beach with my children. I found a sea shell and gave it to my 4 year old daughter and said &amp;quot;You can hear the ocean if you put this to your ear.&amp;quot; She placed the shell to her ear and screamed. There was a hermit crab inside and it pinched her ear. She never wants to go back! LoL I know this is entirely off topic but I had to tell someone!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5b9e3fd-bcfd-436d-ae42-689bc30e8087" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-15 00:09:36</date>
      <author>Edmund Pytlak</author>
      <email>jerrod_barlow@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.190.139.36</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good post. I learn something totally new and challenging on blogs I stumbleupon on a daily basis. It&amp;#39;s always useful to read articles from other writers and use a little something from their websites.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1e5204e7-fac7-4bfb-86ab-1069d80331b8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-17 19:58:33</date>
      <author>Fryderyk Gruszka</author>
      <email>deb.lau@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>217.23.5.247</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>excellent put up, very informative. I ponder why the other experts of this sector do not realize this. You should continue your writing. I&amp;#39;m sure, you have a great readers&amp;#39; base already!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="27d749a8-64b4-4d0b-8565-854c2dfeddc7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-06-09 05:37:46</date>
      <author>Donald Migdal</author>
      <email>efrenmackinlay@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.252</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Why viewers still make use of to read news papers when in this technological globe everything is available on net?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5fb1d4b5-533b-4be3-8cea-024ef5531c2e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-06-13 13:55:07</date>
      <author>Franciszek laski</author>
      <email>myrtis.witcher@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.252</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I simply could not depart your web site before suggesting that I extremely loved the standard info an individual supply for your guests? Is going to be again continuously to investigate cross-check new posts</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f32c810f-9334-4e37-8770-cf966d94090c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-06-30 09:41:38</date>
      <author>Orest Paczkowski</author>
      <email>tahliamcintosh@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow that was unusual. I just wrote an incredibly long comment but after I clicked submit my comment didn&amp;#39;t show up. Grrrr... well I&amp;#39;m not writing all that over again. Regardless, just wanted to say wonderful blog!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8c34491e-1212-424d-b52b-297d9f004ba9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-06-30 16:07:43</date>
      <author>Wincenty Zajkowski</author>
      <email>janellaycock@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! I simply want to give you a huge thumbs up for your great information you have here on this post. I&amp;#39;ll be returning to your site for more soon.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="39fb4a54-e262-40e1-a9d7-e3b94f995508" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-06-30 18:39:07</date>
      <author>Hubert Romanek</author>
      <email>evie_knatchbull@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>all the time i used to read smaller posts that  as well clear their motive, and that is also happening with this post which I am reading now.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="50d4acc2-1484-4fb1-88b7-b2f93cbe0ea1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-01 00:23:10</date>
      <author>Joachim Ciok</author>
      <email>brandykincaid@ml1.net</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya i am for the first time here. I found this board and I find It really useful &amp;amp; it helped me out a lot. I hope to give something back and help others like you helped me.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0f6fd43c-45da-4ffc-9e63-587970f5c786" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-01 03:18:08</date>
      <author>Janusz Filipczyk</author>
      <email>odelltulloch@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s a shame you don&amp;#39;t have a donate button! I&amp;#39;d without a doubt donate to this fantastic blog! I suppose for now i&amp;#39;ll settle for book-marking and adding your RSS feed to my Google account. I look forward to brand new updates and will share this site with my Facebook group. Chat soon!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1a3f517-312c-4a4c-acbe-7f14e97f5fe8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-02 11:41:19</date>
      <author>Ignacy Fuchs</author>
      <email>gerardoschroeder@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! I understand this is sort of off-topic but I had to ask. Does operating a well-established website like yours require a large amount of work? I am completely new to blogging however I do write in my journal daily. I&amp;#39;d like to start a blog so I will be able to share my own experience and feelings online. Please let me know if you have any suggestions or tips for brand new aspiring bloggers. Thankyou!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7e74f8b9-8e12-48f6-b20a-5053cef5cb2a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-03 22:54:17</date>
      <author>Barabasz Kania</author>
      <email>dorrisapplegate@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m extremely inspired with your writing abilities as smartly as with the structure to your blog. Is this a paid subject or did you modify it your self? Anyway keep up the excellent quality writing, it&amp;#39;s uncommon to look a nice blog like this one nowadays..</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f0c0b32d-18d2-4e7e-aaec-484fd63bfaf6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-04 11:35:37</date>
      <author>Nestor Ostrowski</author>
      <email>shawneestout@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Quality content is the crucial to invite the visitors to go to see the website, that&amp;#39;s what this website is providing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1d3709d8-e650-4330-89d5-1cff1279c6f0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-04 22:55:02</date>
      <author>Leopold Koscielniak</author>
      <email>sofiamcalpine@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>There is certainly a lot to know about this topic. I really like all of the points you have made.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ecca23b9-ef52-4f1c-a326-829fde155010" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-05 02:38:51</date>
      <author>Theo Fialkowski</author>
      <email>luis_baugh@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s going to be finish of mine day, except before finish I am reading this wonderful post to increase my knowledge.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0ab3ee5a-90b1-4d02-96cd-2d8910f4ec77" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-07-05 21:41:02</date>
      <author>Lucjan Kossowski</author>
      <email>jolenegriffin@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.255.41.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Quality articles is the secret to be a focus for the visitors to pay a quick visit the web site, that&amp;#39;s what this web site is providing.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>themebazaar@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>