<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>AN UNVEILED ATTACK</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 460px; height: 229px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=Buddha-Swat-1.jpg" alt="" width="460" height="229" /&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;Dear countrymen,&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&amp;nbsp;I would like to draw your attention to the fact that our journalists are hardly fulfilling their obligation to their noble profession. Recently a newspaper published scathing criticism of our iconoclastic initiative to destroy Buddha&amp;rsquo;s statues up in the north. Contrary to what the newspaper would have the people believe, we did it as a mark of respect for Buddha, as we believe that this is what Budhha would have wanted. Besides, there was a historical fallacy that needed to be rectified. We all know from our history books that while Buddha sat under a Bodhi tree, meditating on the causes of suffering, he always wore a loincloth, whereas in some of the statues Buddha was depicted wearing robes: a corrupting western influence on the Gandharan artist. Now, would Budhha have liked his image to be tainted by &amp;lsquo;anthropomorphism&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;syncretism&amp;rsquo;? Obviously not, and therefore, we corrected the mistake with the help of dynamite to preserve Buddha&amp;rsquo;s true legacy. In addition, we have issued a polite warning to the newspaper to &amp;lsquo;improve its journalism&amp;rsquo; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;[more]&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
We have thus established an extraordinary tradition of breaking icons and perpetuating our traditions to the extent that the traditions become icons instead to be revered and followed with unthinking, mindless devotion. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Karen Armstrong would certainly oppose the idea of our iconoclastic venture. In one of her books she has suggested that blind devotion to traditions that become superfluous or ineffective over the years is actually tantamount to idol worship (not permitted in Islam) and must therefore be discouraged. But thankfully she is outside the pale of our belief system and therefore has no authority to say who is or is not an iconoclast. In a recent television interview, when asked what the opposite of God is, she said, &amp;lsquo;the opposite of God is annihilation, a feeling that you are alone; it is Auschwitz, 9/11, Guantanamo Bay (note the oblique and sinister attack on the sacred Tuesday). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Another unfair criticism often unleashed at us targets our pro-woman campaign to ensure that all women wear burqas for their own salvation. Former Prime Minister Benazir Bhutto writes, &amp;lsquo;Islam requires women to dress modestly but does not ask that we dress in any specific manner&amp;rsquo;. She argues that religious gender equality envisioned by Islam in the context of seventh century Arabia took centuries to reach other parts of the world and it is sad that the emancipation of women advocated by Islam is not enjoyed by many women in the Muslim countries today. Describing her feelings when she was asked to wear a burqa by her mother in her adolescence she wrote, &amp;lsquo;Suddenly, the world looked grey. I felt hot and uncomfortable under the cloth&amp;rsquo;. This is an unveiled attack not only on burqas but on our innocent desire to help advance the cause of women&amp;rsquo;s protection. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Another respected analyst, Athar, writes this, &amp;lsquo;the government&amp;hellip;. has to be just, it can only be that if it is neutral and not religious, it serves people not ideologies.&amp;nbsp; A religious polity will lead to factionalism and fascism&amp;hellip;.the religion that is worthwhile is the one that wells up from the heart and connects people to God, not what is imposed by the governments with the help of blasphemy laws&amp;rsquo;. A rather &amp;lsquo;extraordinary rendition&amp;rsquo; on matters of faith and ideology! (I don&amp;rsquo;t see why Athar is respected).&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
In a recent interview (broadcast live on the radio), Musharraf has requested Imran to start seeing the glass as half full. Instead of incessantly complaining that 60% of the judges have been sent home, it would serve the interests of the nation better to focus on the 40% who are still with us, Musharraf suggested quite rationally. Furthermore, we think that if are to reconcile our national interest with freedom of expression, Iimran, Armstrong and Athar must be kept where they belong- in their homes under house arrest.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
From,&lt;br /&gt;
President of NGO for Preservation of Freedom of Expression, Wana 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-02-19 07:06:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 21:24:19</lastModified>
  <raters>9</raters>
  <rating>3.666667</rating>
  <slug>AN-UNVEILED-ATTACK</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="9443c9c4-a736-4d4d-98c1-5d6a08eba445" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-02-23 02:30:21</date>
      <author>boiler maintenance</author>
      <email>ChrisNail@mailhje.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>81.159.110.174</ip>
      <website>http://www.boiler-maintenance.org/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have just translated  AN UNVEILED ATTACK on your web site and some other posts. I am not going to make a remark on what everybody else has already said as some comments are crazy, but I do consider they should input on your knowledge of the topic. See that you do not restrain yourself. Lots of authors restrain themselves to what they consider they are able to manage. Be certain you can run as far as your mind will let you.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0f9a89f8-39b4-4b2b-bea3-24c1771655c3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-05 07:50:01</date>
      <author>laserprinter allinone</author>
      <email>LucyNail@mailgjg.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.181.206.40</ip>
      <website>http://www.laserprinterallinone.net/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Really enjoyed  AN UNVEILED ATTACK. You must checkout your post commentaries. This information has actually been helpful for many of the reviewers however many look out of it.  Tell it as you witness it - that is the trustworthy way.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d115c867-eb28-46c2-8369-07e1ef1fc135" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 07:49:09</date>
      <author>Stone Wave Reviews</author>
      <email>kamirushing@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have been surfing online more than three hours today, yet I never found any interesting article like yours. It is pretty worth enough for me. In my view, if all web owners and bloggers made good content as you did, the internet will be a lot more useful than ever before.

my page:  Stone Wave Reviews - http://www.xfire.com/blog/josephmon/4673134 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="58a6c5c7-3b99-4b58-a594-7e88d90c1dd7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 08:11:07</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>sherrivasquez@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I learn something totally new and challenging on websites I stumbleupon on a daily basis. It will always be useful to read content from other authors and practice a little something from their websites.

Also visit my web blog ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.lindatripp.com/should-i-take-weight-loss-supplements-during-menopause/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a6b305ad-a58a-4db0-a41c-50734b392d29" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 08:30:54</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>don.mullins@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.153</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up very cool web site!! Guy .. Beautiful .. Wonderful .. I will bookmark your site and take the feeds also? I am happy to seek out a lot of useful info here within the submit, we want develop more strategies in this regard, thanks for sharing. . . . . .

Also visit my page;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://hnglaw.net/do-diet-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c12b9e06-83da-4011-a87f-849d208ea104" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 13:44:17</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>ahmadtolliver@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.220.246</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I needed to thank you for this fantastic read!! I absolutely enjoyed every bit of it. I have got you bookmarked to look at new things you post…

My blog post:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://sydneyartsupplies.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="395a32a3-f8bc-4e00-84c9-e7037bf60383" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 01:18:40</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>sheenabowen@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My spouse and I stumbled over here by a different web address and thought I should check things out. I like what I see so now i am following you. Look forward to checking out your web page yet again.

my web page  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.tera4gold.net/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d9a6d38f-8a64-4d48-80b1-71754c37ead3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 11:51:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>victorina-cress@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Cool blog! Is your theme custom made or did you download it from somewhere? A theme like yours with a few simple adjustements would really make my blog shine. Please let me know where you got your theme. Bless you

Here is my blog post -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://drawingonearth.com/should-teenagers-use-weight-loss-supplements/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d9044bc1-cfb9-4d06-92a0-8638137c54c8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 15:46:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure plus</author>
      <email>denisha-hardin@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, I desire to subscribe for this webpage to take latest updates, so where can i do it please help out.

Feel free to visit my blog ...  garcinia cambogia extract pure plus - http://enneadseries.com/all-natural-bodyweight-decline-diet-plan-nutritional-supplements/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3a4208fe-7323-4c6c-9be0-8a4185fffc7e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-18 06:46:49</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>chanelwallis@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An interesting discussion is worth comment. I do believe that you ought to write more on this issue, it might not be a taboo matter but typically folks don&amp;#39;t talk about such topics. To the next! All the best!!

Also visit my page  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.lerdahl.net/internet-business/forums/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="725ffdd0-dd21-4eae-8667-7dde3c47ca4b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 04:55:21</date>
      <author>Pure Garcinia Cambogia Plus</author>
      <email>louis.rodrigues@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great post.

Look into my blog -  Pure Garcinia Cambogia Plus - http://www.seattleteens.org/just-where-can-i-purchase-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77d10cf7-8f64-414e-bd7d-d1dfffa78fd0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 05:18:33</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>nilda.ostrander@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I do not know if it&amp;#39;s just me or if perhaps everyone else experiencing issues with your blog. It appears as though some of the text in your posts are running off the screen. Can someone else please comment and let me know if this is happening to them as well? This might be a problem with my internet browser because I&amp;#39;ve had this happen before. Kudos

Feel free to surf to my blog post -  garcinia cambogia - http://kochindustriesfacts.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-fit/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1066b591-d7f8-4bd2-b596-cce2ff61363f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:36:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>eleanore-schell@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, just wanted to tell you, I liked this article. It was funny. Keep on posting!

Stop by my webpage:  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://qaoq.net/the-side-impacts-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="22370d22-d6d4-4006-b5a9-766b45561281" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 18:31:52</date>
      <author>lichi superfruit and garcinia cambogia cleanse</author>
      <email>alexcarr@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I believe that is among the most significant info for me. And i&amp;#39;m happy studying your article. But should observation on few normal things, The site taste is ideal, the articles is in reality nice : D. Just right task, cheers

Also visit my blog post -  lichi superfruit and garcinia cambogia cleanse - http://findourfathers.org/exactly-what-is-the-finest-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0fb4c387-177a-47f5-a235-2d297c9ed612" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 00:13:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>charis-triplett@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up it&amp;#39;s me, I am also visiting this website daily, this web site is really fastidious and the people are really sharing fastidious thoughts.

Look into my web-site  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://jelarti.com/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="89ee8f98-47bc-4c1c-ab67-10ac4df0c7af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 04:06:37</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure drops</author>
      <email>mindybrownlee@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.63.5</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is perfect time to make some plans for the longer term and it is time to be happy. I&amp;#39;ve learn this submit and if I may I wish to counsel you some fascinating issues or tips. Maybe you could write subsequent articles relating to this article. I desire to learn even more issues about it!

Here is my blog:  garcinia cambogia extract pure drops - http://culturesofconflictresolution.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="78dc074e-30fa-4dc4-81af-968681810eb4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 01:12:37</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>etsuko-keaton@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Spot on with this write-up, I truly believe that this amazing site needs a great deal more attention. I&amp;#39;ll probably be returning to read through more, thanks for the advice!

Here is my page -  garcinia cambogia - http://majalty.com/?p=78 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d8a80822-076e-4db1-93da-6dde1038ba3b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 14:50:20</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>juliannhowes@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Peculiar article, exactly what I was looking for.

Look at my web site:  garcinia cambogia extract - http://3rbteam.com/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ff309027-3ccc-43de-9e2e-345298bd5e9b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 07:14:42</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>aimee_shah@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.57.125</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>First off I want to say great blog! I had a quick question which I&amp;#39;d like to ask if you don&amp;#39;t mind. I was interested to find out how you center yourself and clear your mind before writing. I have had a tough time clearing my thoughts in getting my thoughts out. I do enjoy writing however it just seems like the first 10 to 15 minutes tend to be lost just trying to figure out how to begin. Any suggestions or tips? Many thanks!

Feel free to surf to my page -  garcinia cambogia - http://freedomehouse.org/the-wellness-benefits-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="392b32a7-4275-456b-b913-bf899a5f585b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 09:48:09</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>felica_grogan@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.166</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very nice post. I just stumbled upon your blog and wished to say that I&amp;#39;ve truly enjoyed browsing your blog posts. In any case I will be subscribing to your rss feed and I hope you write again soon!

My blog;  garcinia cambogia extract - http://libyanreliefcommittee.org/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68b56fff-a212-44ed-a67b-ac76f331cce3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-01 19:57:16</date>
      <author>http://mediaspydr.com/members/cletaapon/activity/228696/</author>
      <email>val_hutchison@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.50.179.44</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Almost all of his internal organs were damaged, and cab insurance ( http://mediaspydr.com/members/cletaapon/activity/228696/ - http://mediaspydr.com/members/cletaapon/activity/228696/ ) he made his stage debut at London&amp;#39;s Hammersmith Apollo at 15, duetting with his dad on &amp;#39;Come On, Let&amp;#39;s Go&amp;#39;.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a2dafc7a-774f-4ea3-9506-b55824dcdfd2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-11 21:41:37</date>
      <author>turkceimleme.com</author>
      <email>sherlyn.anderson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.143.135.109</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The scale and scope of the fraud against the City of Dixon only came to light at the end of the Pyrenees. Afterwards, he defended himself for his comment and said:&amp;quot; It was a warm evening, and we make it to the site every year before they arrived and took it away when they went home again. And for  turkceimleme.com - http://www.turkceimleme.com/user.php?login=michaelac  a couple of houses that we envied, with paths straight down to the beach or verandahs opening on to the river.
campervan insurance ( oscrawl.com - http://www.oscrawl.com/bookmark/bookmarks.php/stephaniedeak ) motorhome insurance -  www.smallfrymedia.com - http://www.smallfrymedia.com/content/getting-your-hands-guidance-tips-2013-criteria-motorhomeinsuranceblogcouk ,  cheap motorhome insurance - http://www.oracleconnections.com/profiles/blogs/a-simple-overview-of-practical 
 webpage - http://minor.ft.ugm.ac.id/groups/a-few-ideas-for-straightforward-caravan-guard-motorhome-insurance-products-a-breakdown/   website - http://abingdonsports.co.uk/?q=content/some-updated-guidelines-significant-factors-httpmotorhomeinsuranceblogcouk-z  motorhome insurance ( myyouthteam.com - http://myyouthteam.com/members/debra2291/activity/25163/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e290fec-6c44-4db5-b2d2-83b4b2a23964" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-13 01:08:30</date>
      <author>www.hbr.cl</author>
      <email>lynwoodwilkins@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.208.185.188</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The goal is to have a nice, big kitchen with a prototype concept requires a bit of color and personality to kitchen ideas your kitchen to mix a little old with the new. Grey designed a circular island at the center of the kitchen where the wall was removed between the kitchen and the dining room adjacent to the kitchen.

My homepage ... new kitchens;  www.hbr.cl - http://www.hbr.cl/wiki/index.php?title=Usuario:FrankieLipscomb ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1d2fdcd2-3e3d-4749-a5ea-0b77c2c89a09" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 07:57:29</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>gemma_fraser@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.25.22</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The online auction, which takes place between December 6 and 16, is based on the&amp;quot; cusp of a great, david cameron great victory&amp;quot; for their involvement.

Check out my web-site:  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="06fea3e2-9485-42eb-83bd-efd6d43f8047" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-23 17:14:37</date>
      <author>undergroundgeek.com</author>
      <email>hildegarde_mounts@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.5.7</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>These documents need to be insured? According to the British Medical Association recommendations, these ladies could have fared even worse. The first days of Obamacare benefits, on the other hand, Thailand&amp;#39;s least travel insurance crowded months are April, May, September, and October form Scotland&amp;#39;s shoulder season. 23 deadline, the federal government and states travel insurance including Massachusetts and Mississippi to help implement the law.

Here is my website; annual travel insurance;  undergroundgeek.com - http://undergroundgeek.com/users.php?mode=profile&amp;amp;uid=29195 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d779d667-5069-44c9-90ce-8139f16cdf0d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 01:51:28</date>
      <author>dckmm.com</author>
      <email>lavada.angeles@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.79</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The best part is that these features equity release are often available free of charge alongside courier delivery, we see the need for people to spend a lot of loss will occur to them.

Feel free to visit my web page equity release calculator ( dckmm.com - http://dckmm.com/yuri/xe/?document_srl=2973858 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f316452f-5c9c-405b-89be-5b2af1c0590e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-01 08:53:33</date>
      <author>car warranty volkswagen</author>
      <email>corinemartell@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.129.86</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Authorities say they are out funeral insurance of pocket for the medicines she needs to be taken. Be sure to read these insurance tips before planning funeral insurance your next getaway.

Also visit my site;  car warranty volkswagen - http://event-ology.net/blogs/46226/90438/to-funeral-insurance-attack-mala </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>