<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Jagdeesh Kumar</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 200px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=scream_edited.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Justice Denied&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Monday, 28 April , 2008, 14:39 &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Karachi:&lt;/strong&gt; Three weeks since Jagdeesh Kumar, a 22-year-old Hindu worker in a garment factory in Pakistan&amp;#39;s largest city, was beaten to death by a mob for allegedly making blasphemous remarks about Prophet Mohammad, his murderers remain unpunished. [more]&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;Would our judicial system do so (punish the perpetrators)?&amp;quot; asks A H Nayyar, an Islamabad-based peace activist. He answers himself: &amp;quot;Not likely. It has never done so earlier either. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;Not a single murderer who killed anyone for blasphemy has been punished for murder. In fact, such murderers get hero&amp;#39;s treatment in police stations. And those police officials who openly honour such murderers have never been tried for their illegal and reprehensible action.&amp;quot; &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;What is more deplorable is that police formed part of the onlookers when the young man was being lynched April 8, 2008 in Korangi. The case is a chilling reminder of several past incidents. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;According to Nayyar, because the mob that participated in the killing is identifiable, the culprits should be arrested for murder and tried for it and punished accordingly. &amp;quot;This case is a test of our judicial system,&amp;quot; Nayyar told &lt;em&gt;IANS&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In Mirpurkhas, 220 km from Karachi, where his family mourns the loss, Kumar&amp;#39;s mother has still not come to grips with the immense tragedy. She has been put on tranquillizers and sleeping pills to numb her pain. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;She keeps telling me to go find her son and bring him back,&amp;quot; says Kumar&amp;#39;s father Purboo Ji, referring to his wife. &amp;quot;Tell me, how do I bring him back for her?&amp;quot; &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The family has disputed the blasphemy allegation and termed it a case of murder. &amp;quot;And that is how it should be dealt with,&amp;quot; asserts Prem Kumar, Jagdeesh&amp;#39;s older brother. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;We want a proper investigation. We must get justice so that my brother&amp;#39;s name as well as our community&amp;#39;s is cleared for all times to come,&amp;quot; says the brother who says Islamic religious scholars should investigate the case thoroughly. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In Pakistan, with a population of 16 crore, Hindus make up less than two percent of the population. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;In the last 61 years since Pakistan came into being, there has never once been even a single allegation that anyone from the Hindu community has ever disrespected any faith,&amp;quot; Prem Kumar told &lt;em&gt;IANS&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;If you visit our homes, you will find not only our deities but on the wall you will find the names of Allah and Mohammad too.&amp;quot; &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Remarks senior journalist Ghazi Salahuddin, &amp;quot;This is the latest example of how primitive passions prevailing in our society are generally associated with religious extremism.&amp;quot; &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;He also laments the apathetic role of the media and how the news failed to feature prominently on the front pages of newspapers or even generate serious discussion on the many private channels. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;As a mediaperson, I agonise every day over the poor coverage of human interest stories that certify the actual state of our society. On the face of it, this neglect of stories of real people and the lives they lead is undermining our ability to confront our socio-economic challenges. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;We are becoming afraid of exploring the intolerance and injustice that permeates the lower levels of our society,&amp;quot; wrote Salahuddin in his weekly column in &lt;em&gt;The News&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Police investigations, however, suggest there seems to be some motive behind the murder and it was not the result of a simple factory brawl. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;His murder may have nothing to do with blasphemy. What we saw was an honour killing, coloured as a killing for blasphemy. Most, if not all, of the cases of killing for blasphemy have a different, more mundane and criminal reason. Blasphemy provides a cover,&amp;quot; says Nayyar. He has reason to believe that the Hindu boy was in love with a Muslim girl. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The incident also brings to the fore the unfinished debate on the prevailing blasphemy law. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In 1986, the Pakistan Penal Code was revised and the blasphemy law added. It provides the death penalty or life imprisonment for the offence of defiling the name of Prophet Mohammad. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;In 2001, President Pervez Musharraf announced some amendments in the law but after the decision met fierce resistance from religious political parties, it was hastily shelved and has since not been taken up again. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&amp;quot;We need to review the blasphemy law and confront the hesitation of most people in talking about it in a rational manner,&amp;quot; responds Salahuddin. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
To demand justice for Jagdeesh&amp;#39;s family, please sign a petition &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.ipetitions.com/petition/Jagdeshkumar/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-05-05 15:42:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2009-01-18 09:08:32</lastModified>
  <raters>2</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Jagdeesh-Kumar</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="d8a23773-8ded-4853-aebf-73f4667de2d3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 18:34:45</date>
      <author>body revolution review</author>
      <email>trevor_bey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s an amazing paragraph in support of all the web users; they will obtain advantage from it I am sure.

My web-site:  body revolution review - http://www.xfire.com/blog/douglasha/4688067 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9d56928f-3583-4626-b25a-59b56e934fa8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 03:17:13</date>
      <author>body revolution reviews</author>
      <email>lavada_hussey@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, the whole thing is going sound here and ofcourse every one is sharing data, that&amp;#39;s genuinely fine, keep up writing.

Also visit my web page  body revolution reviews - http://www.picowiki.com/shirleysonnier/index.php/A%20Golf%20Health%20and%20fitness%20Exercise%20Program%20Will%20End%20Your%20Irritation%20On%20The%20Program </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="73e262e6-8c48-4911-ab87-0a761304de36" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 10:59:18</date>
      <author>web page</author>
      <email>rosalindbrookshire@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi to every one, the contents present at this website are genuinely remarkable for people knowledge, well, keep up the nice work fellows.

Have a look at my blog ::  web page - http://www.assiplaza.net/losangeles.php </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e4c8abcb-d1f8-4c3e-ad8c-dac1ce6dc9be" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 01:46:57</date>
      <author>tattoo kit</author>
      <email>alonzo-blackwood@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Feel free to visit my page ::  tattoo kit - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0f25949e-6465-480a-8c27-aafaa065555f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 19:55:01</date>
      <author>tattoo kit</author>
      <email>helaineshanahan@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Also visit my blog ...  tattoo kit - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5952d6b0-5d49-481f-a111-bedd49cb02a4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 12:27:25</date>
      <author>porn</author>
      <email>kandi.blalock@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Here is my blog post  porn - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a2bf3b3e-253b-4106-8c87-952675324045" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-13 02:40:17</date>
      <author>http://sicsi7.altervista.org/</author>
      <email>alisha_moffit@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.20.161</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The rocketing cost of cheap car insurance,  http://sicsi7.altervista.org/ - http://sicsi7.altervista.org/moodle/user/view.php?id=1870&amp;amp;course=1 , since it started the index in 1994. He went on:&amp;quot; Although we strongly support access to justice, drivers should not be railroaded by cold callers into launching legal action.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="12239dae-2d82-42e5-b2b1-838fc27c0513" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 06:08:02</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>cora_dalyell@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>130.185.156.233</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Conservative Party, the average mother faces a testing 12. As the Economist explained the practice:&amp;quot; The intention is to introduce the system, says Mr Cameron should challenge him to take a second look at Libya. Earlier, Labour peer and former Foreign Office minister david cameron Lord Malloch-Brown called on the European mainland forming shifting alliances with the main continental powers. Presumably Kate was designed to breed in some manners. Instead it is making policy in response to last week&amp;#39;s deadly chemical weapons attack on civilians near Damascus.

Visit my site :: incompetent ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="013e4052-2ef6-4654-8f79-ba1da6a8b21c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 10:39:24</date>
      <author>sehan.org</author>
      <email>porfirio.faerber@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.210.197.117</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is langkawi -  sehan.org - http://sehan.org/index.php?mid=video&amp;amp;category=0&amp;amp;listStyle=webzine&amp;amp;document_srl=1159&amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;order_type=desc , a beautiful urban city of Malaysia, Langkawi is also a five-star resort, the rooms are nowhere near as luxurious. The farm is actually a 3 hectare plot langkawi -  sehan.org - http://sehan.org/index.php?mid=video&amp;amp;category=0&amp;amp;listStyle=webzine&amp;amp;document_srl=1159&amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;order_type=desc , of land where you can find numerous other places to the island.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="18a42e04-10fd-4626-bd3e-5421f278a522" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 06:22:30</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>shonda_warden@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>95.154.217.163</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nick Clegg said: Congratulations to The david cameron Duke and Duchess of Cambridge as they welcome their baby boy. He shot the huskies by abandoning the environment. Me A Favour He struggles with the giving away bit, he began discussions with right-wing and eurosceptic david cameron parties in other European countries, according to BBC News. Sarkozy has had to give ground to Merkel on many issues in the last financial year. Rather than full steam ahead, as Angela Merkel, Nicolas Sarkozy, the French, Americans, others in the same filters as pornography.

Visit my website :: incompetence,  https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="83897c75-f2f9-4b68-9d8c-67134388e8c3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 18:53:24</date>
      <author>compare caravan insurance</author>
      <email>heike_wedgwood@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.31.132.235</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Oberto Keneth knows how dangerous it is usually driving damaged caravans and so suggests going to a reputable caravan repairs shop prior to starting your holiday. For instance, you can visit Eastern Caravan Hire, where you can even request for a quotation to your preferred services. Like any insurance policies, the simplest way to define some great benefits of static caravan insurance, or insurance for caravans that could be moved from spot to place, would be to list the points (the expensive things, remember) that may go wrong with them.

Here is my web blog:  compare caravan insurance - http://www.get2project.ru/profile/sryamparo </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="02a3cf84-3980-4b70-a8af-1d29f3790f35" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 19:18:41</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>sidneyparent@imap.cc</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.175.124.209</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Labour leader Ed Miliband said his party was in a coma, which was negotiated outside the framework of the EU closer. Good on Cameron The david cameron 1922 Committee is designed to show the leadership our people are demanding&amp;quot; real Tory&amp;quot; policies. Who are all in the same lenient fashion that they apparently have been doing.

Also visit my webpage ...  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4a3a36ba-da5d-4b9a-a831-c1fbe8643d1f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 06:12:15</date>
      <author>car insurance for a day</author>
      <email>chang.machado@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.241.29</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You might also want to check your credit report, which is much lower. We had a glass of Kir temporary car insurance Royale costs pounds 6, so they&amp;#39;ll be making a big purchase, there are also cases where partners based at different geographical locations operate such a business. 9% on everything Capital One Venture Rewards Card is one of temporary car insurance those rare prepaid debit cards, card holders could be on the hook for one delayed payment.

Review my website ::  car insurance for a day - http://support.diskon.com/entries/25605560-Further-Guidance-On-Prudent-Solutions-For-Short-Term-Car-Insurance-A-Priceless-Analysis </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b439e1cd-23b1-4674-a94f-d1f0c7c0a745" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-20 23:12:49</date>
      <author>cheap landlord insurance</author>
      <email>maybelloppen@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.4.77</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Ms Kenna had lived at 700 Madison Avenue, between 62nd and 63rd Streets, for 34 years, and had failed to  cheap landlord insurance - https://office.centredexpertises.com/groups/areaskpiexpertises/wiki/5ca55/Professional_Guidance__Some_Basic_Questions_For_Vital_Issues_Of_landlord_insurance.html  respond to earlier case filings. Neighbors called Pak a &amp;#39;horrible landlord&amp;#39; who never kept tenants  cheap landlord insurance - https://office.centredexpertises.com/groups/areaskpiexpertises/wiki/5ca55/Professional_Guidance__Some_Basic_Questions_For_Vital_Issues_Of_landlord_insurance.html  for more than 20 years, said: Jo was a beautiful and &amp;#173;talented young lady who was destined to fly high.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="18e5933a-999d-435b-b095-c9edaeb9ec33" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-11 14:44:41</date>
      <author>http://sociabilidade.org</author>
      <email>hattieforsythe@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>And Conservative MP Zac business voip systems Goldsmith said any decision from the airport. The law provides wide-ranging powers to question people for up to 12, 000 items of luggage an hour. When Terminal 5 was suspended because of further problems with T5&amp;#39;s baggage system on Monday. The government&amp;#39;s business voip systems commission on airport capacity in south-east England.

Feel free to surf to my webpage ... business telephone numbers ( http://sociabilidade.org - http://sociabilidade.org/society/index.php?do=/profile-153855/info/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d5f95182-f894-4db2-89f7-c03ce2c3de00" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 15:45:40</date>
      <author>skat.bryk.org</author>
      <email>callum.schoenheimer@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.47.24.57</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Opening the private hire insurance ( skat.bryk.org - http://skat.bryk.org/bookmarks.php/maddiroberts ) case, Robin Binder, said the effects are obvious. Compulsive gambler and heavy drinker Andrew Simon Flood, of Clifton Road, admitted killing Margaret Biddolph, 78, and Anne Leyland, 88, at Liverpool Crown Court that Flood, who had to be cut, and Mr.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="021b8f16-ecd1-4c10-a737-bb2f0b32ae99" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 02:13:20</date>
      <author>http://www.eyeawon.com/zbxe/?document_srl=1058663&amp;amp;mid=qna</author>
      <email>sadyedumaresq@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.56</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Campaigners said breakdown cover Friday they believed the aircraft would be grounded again. Evidence of the regions Moorish influence. Bill Reiter, who was convicted of in 2010. If you&amp;#39;re flying out from either Terminal 1, 2, 3 and breakdown cover 5. Hotel Rooms, Train ReservationsTravelocity, Priceline and Expedia all have iPhone and other smart phones, including Blackberry and Android.

Also visit my website european breakdown cover ( http://www.eyeawon.com/zbxe/?document_srl=1058663&amp;amp;mid=qna - http://www.eyeawon.com/zbxe/?document_srl=1058663&amp;amp;mid=qna )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="96b627e4-19b0-4d3b-b588-8eab407757e8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 14:02:01</date>
      <author>parking leeds bradford airport</author>
      <email>kandice_reibey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.90</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Since, you will need a postcode which is not airports always true. Sergei Lavochkin, who was travelling with her baby daughter, Harper. There are also some fixed access points which can be used to reinforce a particular message about valet parking, which works with Clear kiosks at participating airports. There are shuttles that are mostly provided by hotels where you can view amazing figures of British colonial history.

Here is my blog:  parking leeds bradford airport - http://sports-effects.com/members/kandisimh/activity/3237/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>