<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p class="firstHeading"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="firstHeading"&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 164px; height: 206px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=12.jpg" alt="" width="164" height="206" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="firstHeading"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="firstHeading"&gt;
[more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="firstHeading"&gt;
&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Career in Law&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="bodyContent"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry Iftikhar has a Bachelors in Arts and Bachelors in Law (LLB). He joined the bar in 1974. Later, he was enrolled as Advocate of the High Court in 1976 and as an Advocate of the Supreme Court in 1985. In 1989 he was appointed as Advocate General, Balochistan, and later got elevated as Additional Judge, Balochistan High Court in 6 November 1990 until 21 April 1999.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[7]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Besides remaining as Judge High Court, he discharged duties as Banking Judge, Judge Special Court for Speedy Trials, Judge Customs Appellate Courts as well as Company Judge. Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry also remained President of High Court Bar Association, Quetta, and was elected twice as Member, Bar Council. Later, he was appointed as Chairman, Balochistan Local Council Election Authority in 1992 and thereafter for second term in 1998. He also worked as Chairman, Provincial Review Board for the province of Balochistan. He was twice appointed as Chairman, Pakistan Red Crescent Society, Balochistan. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
At present, Justice Iftikhar is also functioning as Chairman, Enrollment Committee of Pakistan Bar Council and as Chairman, Supreme Court Building Committee. He was appointed as Chief Justice High Court of Balochistan on 22 April 1999.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[7]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
In January 2000 Chief Executive General Musharraf dictated that all superior court judges swear a new oath under the PCO No.1 issued on October 15, 1999, which had suspended the Constitution of Pakistan. After swearing an oath on the PCO Justice Iftikhar was elevated to the Supreme Court on 4 February 2000. He was appointed as Chief Justice of Pakistan on 7 May 2005 by President General Pervez Musharraf.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[8]&lt;/sup&gt; Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry is the senior-most judge among the sitting judges of the Court after the outgoing Chief Justice Nazim Hussain Siddiqui. Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry assumed the office of Chief Justice on 30 June 2005.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[7]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Important rulings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Pakistan Steel Mills Privatization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dd&gt;
&lt;div class="noprint"&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Main article: Pakistan Steel Mills&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
In 2007, the Supreme court ruled against the government, saying that the selling of Pakistan Steel Mills to a group including Arif Habib, former client and friend of PM Shaukat Aziz, was done in &amp;quot;indecent haste&amp;quot;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="thumb tright"&gt;
&lt;div class="thumbinner" style="width: 252px"&gt;
&lt;img class="thumbimage" src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/f/f4/Pakistan-CJ.jpg/250px-Pakistan-CJ.jpg" border="0" alt="President Pervez Musharraf administers the oath of the office of the Chief Justice of Pakistan to Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry in 2005." width="250" height="174" /&gt; 
&lt;div class="thumbcaption"&gt;
&lt;div class="magnify" style="float: right"&gt;
&lt;span style="display: inline-block; font-size: 0px; background-image: none; vertical-align: middle; cursor: hand; border-width: 2px; border-color: #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="display: inline-block; filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.AlphaImageLoader(src='http://en.wikipedia.org/skins-1.5/common/images/magnify-clip.png'); width: 1px; height: 1px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
President Pervez Musharraf administers the oath of the office of the Chief Justice of Pakistan to Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry in 2005. 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Hasba Bill case&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dd&gt;
&lt;div class="noprint"&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Main article: Hasba bill&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The Hasba bill also proposed powers for the police to ensure observance of Islamic practices and values while curbing palm reading and other superstitious customs deemed un-Islamic by the legislators. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
General Pervez Musharraf petitioned the top court for an opinion after the Hasba bill was passed through North West Frontier Province&amp;#39;s assembly. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;The governor of the province of NWFP may not assent to the Hasba bill in its present form,&amp;quot; Chief Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry, head of a panel of nine judges, told the court before listing several clauses in the bill deemed unconstitutional. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Missing people&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Many people in Pakistan had &amp;quot;disappeared.&amp;quot; allegedly kidnapped by the American agencies (FBI, CIA) and Pakistani agencies (ISI, MI, IB) in pursuance of the &amp;quot;War on Terror.&amp;quot; These actions were challenged in the Supreme Court and a bench under the Chief Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry had directed the Ministry of Interior and the representatives of the military agencies to appear in the court and answer the issues raised. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The case is being heard by Fakhruddin G. Ebrahim and Asma Jahangir from the Human Rights Commission of Pakistan.&lt;sup class="noprint Template-Fact"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space: nowrap"&gt;[&lt;em&gt;citation needed&lt;/em&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Cases for 2007&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
It is thought that some very important cases were to be heard in the supreme court in the coming months. Decisions have already been taken in some: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The case whether Nawaz Sharif (twice the former PM of Pakistan) can come back to Pakistan. Government had always said that he can but now does not want him to come back. &amp;mdash; &lt;em&gt;Decision:&lt;/em&gt; Sharif can come back.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[9]&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Upcoming cases include: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The case inquiring the dual nationality of the Prime Minister Shaukat Aziz and his eligibility to be Prime Minister. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The case on whether or not the President Pervez Musharraf could run the election for the next Presidency term. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The Uniform Issue of President Pervez Musharraf, i.e. whether the President may continue in office without relinquishing his role as the head of the military. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Inquest into the validity of the decrees issued by madrassas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span class="editsection"&gt;[edit]&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Suspension and reinstatement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="thumb tright"&gt;
&lt;div class="thumbinner" style="width: 252px"&gt;
&lt;img class="thumbimage" src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/ea/Iftikhar_chaudhry_agencies.jpg/250px-Iftikhar_chaudhry_agencies.jpg" border="0" alt="Two secret agents try to force the chief justice to sit in the car. One agent grasps the Chief Justice by the hair." width="250" height="160" /&gt; 
&lt;div class="thumbcaption"&gt;
&lt;div class="magnify" style="float: right"&gt;
&lt;span style="display: inline-block; font-size: 0px; background-image: none; vertical-align: middle; cursor: hand; border-width: 2px; border-color: #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="display: inline-block; filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.AlphaImageLoader(src='http://en.wikipedia.org/skins-1.5/common/images/magnify-clip.png'); width: 1px; height: 1px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
Two secret agents try to force the chief justice to sit in the car. One agent grasps the Chief Justice by the hair. 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dd&gt;
&lt;div class="noprint"&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Main article: Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry (suspension)&lt;/em&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On March 09, 2007, Chaudhry was suspended by Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf. Musharraf also filed a &amp;quot;reference&amp;quot; (&lt;em&gt;i.e.&lt;/em&gt;, legal case) against Chaudhry for alleged misconduct, such as an allegation that Chaudhry demanded an ostentatious Mercedes-Benz for his official car. &lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[10]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The suspension of Chaudhry was the first time in the 50-year history of the Pakistani Supreme Court that a Chief Justice was suspended. The court under Chief Justice Chaudhry had made rulings against governmental corruption, including the Pakistan Steel Mills case. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
After the event, there was unrest in the country with regard to the validity of the allegations against Chaudhry, as well as doubt as to whether Musharraf actually had the power to suspend the Chief Justice under the circumstances.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[11]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On May 5, 2007, Chaudhry traveled from Islamabad to Lahore to address the Lahore High Court Bar Association. Demonstrations of support along the route slowed his motorcade to the point that it took him 25 hours to reach the dinner the Association was holding in his honor.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[12]&lt;/sup&gt; This journey usually takes 4-5 hours on average.&lt;sup class="noprint Template-Fact"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space: nowrap"&gt;[&lt;em&gt;citation needed&lt;/em&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Demonstrators chanted not only slogans supporting Chaudrhy, but also openly called for Musharraf to step down.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[12]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="thumb tright"&gt;
&lt;div class="thumbinner" style="width: 182px"&gt;
&lt;img class="thumbimage" src="http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/a/a8/Pakpublicrally.jpg/180px-Pakpublicrally.jpg" border="0" alt="Public supporting Chief Justice in capital city of Islamabad." width="180" height="245" /&gt; 
&lt;div class="thumbcaption"&gt;
&lt;div class="magnify" style="float: right"&gt;
&lt;span style="display: inline-block; font-size: 0px; background-image: none; vertical-align: middle; cursor: hand; border-width: 2px; border-color: #0000ff"&gt;&lt;span style="display: inline-block; filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.AlphaImageLoader(src='http://en.wikipedia.org/skins-1.5/common/images/magnify-clip.png'); width: 1px; height: 1px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
Public supporting Chief Justice in capital city of Islamabad. 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On July 20, 2007, Chaudhry was reinstated to his position as Chief Justice in a ruling by the thirteen-member Pakistani Supreme Court which also quashed the misconduct reference filed against him by Musharraf.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[10]&lt;/sup&gt; The ruling combined 25 constitutional petitions filed by Chaudhry and other interested parties, but referred most of the issues raised by the 24 petitions not filed by Chaudhry himself to lower courts for extended adjudication. All thirteen of the sitting justices agreed that Musharraf&amp;#39;s action had been illegal, and ten of the thirteen ordered Chaudhry was to be reinstated and that he &amp;quot;shall be deemed to be holding the said office and shall always be deemed to have been so holding the same.&amp;quot; &lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[13]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="mw-headline"&gt;Cases post-reinstatement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On August 20, 2007 Ifikhar Mohammad threatened Tariq Pervez (the director-general of Pakistan&amp;#39;s Federal Investigation Agency) with jail if he did not produce ghost detainee Hafiz Abdul Basit.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[14]&lt;/sup&gt; Chief Justice Chaudhry ordered &amp;quot;He must be produced today or you will be sent to the lock-up.&amp;quot;&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[14]&lt;/sup&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span class="editsection"&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;Pakistani Chief of the Army Staff General Pervez Musharraf on Saturday Nov 3rd 2007 declared a state of emergency and nation&amp;#39;s constitution was suspended.&lt;sup class="reference"&gt;[15]&lt;/sup&gt; The Constitution of Pakistan has provision for only President of Pakistan to impose emergency, if he believe that circumstances exists that warrants it. However the proclamation of State of Emergency was announced in the name Chief of Army Staff and not the President of Pakistan and as per most legal scholar this tanamounts to Martial Law as the provision is not present in the Constitution of Pakistan for Army General to declare State of Emergency.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry Iftikhar after impositions of emergency, suspension of constitution &amp;amp; himself, constituted an 8 member bench of the supreme court judges duly headed by himself, which immediately quashed the provisional constitution order,declaration of emergency and suspension of constitution ordering all the civil and military personnel to ignore the order. He also ordered all the chief justices of high courts and judges of supreme court and high court not to take oath under PCO. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chief Justice Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudary has been removed from the Supreme Court and kept under house arrest by the establishment since then, along with 7 other judges. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
However Justice Abdul Hameed Dogar has taken oath as the de facto chief justice of Pakistan along with three other judges of the Supreme court. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-11-11 22:57:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:58:50</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Iftikhar-Muhammad-Chaudhry</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>chief justice</tag>
    <tag>iftikhar chaudhary</tag>
    <tag>justice</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="dbc784f8-e489-45fd-91c4-3f9392466366" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2011-02-14 08:40:56</date>
      <author>Temizlik şirketleri</author>
      <email>link@pak-temizlik.com</email>
      <country>tr</country>
      <ip>88.234.209.47</ip>
      <website>http://www.pak-temizlik.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Auto</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Temizlik hizmetleri,Cam temizliği,Yangın sonrası temizliği,Temizlik şirketleri,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="af6fd489-2ac5-45f2-be39-2dfc39a0e60c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 21:46:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>lucasrickard@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.108</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! This is my first visit to your blog! We are a team of volunteers and starting a new project in a community in the same niche. Your blog provided us useful information to work on. You have done a extraordinary job!

Also visit my page ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://sydneyartsupplies.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7244523c-0d4f-4964-926c-d9dc25c90b70" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 15:26:39</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>iona-arnold@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am really enjoying the theme/design of your site. Do you ever run into any browser compatibility issues? A small number of my blog audience have complained about my blog not operating correctly in Explorer but looks great in Safari. Do you have any solutions to help fix this issue?

Feel free to visit my page ::  Garcinia cambogia hca - http://td-snow.com/the-truth-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d352a6c7-c37c-408c-9dc7-ac243542b822" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 06:19:04</date>
      <author>body revolution</author>
      <email>reggie_salerno@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This design is wicked! You definitely know how to keep a reader entertained. Between your wit and your videos, I was almost moved to start my own blog (well, almost...HaHa!) Fantastic job. I really enjoyed what you had to say, and more than that, how you presented it. Too cool!

Feel free to surf to my blog  body revolution - http://www.xfire.com/blog/benmontag/4694849 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="85626029-0915-4a01-a385-649e47f4f4db" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 05:18:12</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>thurmanbartholomew@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An impressive share! I have just forwarded this onto a colleague who was conducting a little research on this. And he actually bought me lunch due to the fact that I found it for him... lol. So let me reword this.... Thank YOU for the meal!! But yeah, thanks for spending the time to discuss this issue here on your web page.

Feel free to surf to my webpage ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.lindatripp.com/should-i-take-weight-loss-supplements-during-menopause/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9e9ebad8-598e-483a-8b2a-bba8b7d62bf8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 03:12:28</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>rowenamatias@fastimap.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An outstanding share! I&amp;#39;ve just forwarded this onto a friend who was doing a little research on this. And he in fact bought me breakfast simply because I stumbled upon it for him... lol. So allow me to reword this.... Thank YOU for the meal!! But yeah, thanks for spending the time to discuss this issue here on your web site.

My web-site ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.epilatorreviewsinfo.com/all-natural-fat-decline-remedies/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84733a0d-ae57-4adc-9191-61248bc05247" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 14:03:10</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>bridgettward@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This post is invaluable. When can I find out more?

My web site  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.lindatripp.com/should-i-take-weight-loss-supplements-during-menopause/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="86621220-3be5-4e53-8165-2fe6985fa33e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 15:32:25</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>rodney-freitas@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy I am so thrilled I found your blog page, I really found you by error, while I was looking on Askjeeve for something else, Regardless I am here now and would just like to say thank you for a tremendous post and a all round entertaining blog (I also love the theme/design), I don’t have time to read through it all at the minute but I have bookmarked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read a great deal more, Please do keep up the fantastic work.

my page;  garcinia cambogia - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4463348d-955a-4112-8a4a-aba9e880f203" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 14:38:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>nikivillalobos@mailup.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My spouse and I absolutely love your blog and find the majority of your post&amp;#39;s to be what precisely I&amp;#39;m looking for. Would you offer guest writers to write content for you? I wouldn&amp;#39;t mind publishing a post or elaborating on many of the subjects you write about here. Again, awesome web log!

My weblog  garcinia cambogia - http://aadvantagesafeandlock.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe0fd111-f3a2-4c11-8b1c-484d59240df2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 22:41:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>darcymendenhall@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you are going for finest contents like myself, only visit this website everyday because it gives feature contents, thanks

my web blog  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.dolinaadrenalina.com/the-real-fact-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="42ac33e2-b9b9-4f9d-8c62-ac2edc6864e5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 08:15:54</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>francescobroughton@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, every time i used to check blog posts here in the early hours in the break of day, since i enjoy to find out more and more.

Feel free to surf to my web page ::  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://yourdailydiet.info/fitness/what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4d03d987-434f-4e48-95a6-5db8418188d1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 12:27:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia gnc side effects</author>
      <email>marianochance@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there would you mind letting me know which web host you&amp;#39;re utilizing? I&amp;#39;ve loaded your blog in 3 completely different browsers and I must say this blog loads a lot quicker then most. Can you recommend a good web hosting provider at a honest price? Thanks, I appreciate it!

Feel free to visit my page:  garcinia cambogia gnc side effects - http://matildas.net/normal-fat-decline-will-perform-for-you/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5d1b177-0788-450e-ace3-b10ff905a5d0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 20:53:53</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>lorena.hay@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.119</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one wants to be updated with most up-to-date technologies after that he must be pay a visit this website and be up to date everyday.

My web-site  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.tz315.net/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5af7311-1585-44cd-848e-4b9413ee0772" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 23:52:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>geoffrey.maclean@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.170.223</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very good blog! Do you have any suggestions for aspiring writers? I&amp;#39;m hoping to start my own website soon but I&amp;#39;m a little lost on everything. Would you advise starting with a free platform like Wordpress or go for a paid option? There are so many choices out there that I&amp;#39;m completely overwhelmed .. Any recommendations? Kudos!

My weblog -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.californiacv.com/?p=128 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="082676aa-2d52-491c-87fd-bf87959a406b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-28 23:30:05</date>
      <author>Delia</author>
      <email>deliathigpen@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>46.105.72.11</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As a nation, the US already has trade agreements covering 90 percent of the GDP of the countries involved in the original claim decision. Depending on the plan, all but the very poor because they have medical problems that made them ineligible. 4 percent of health insurance them, or in monocle-speak,&amp;quot; shared sacrifice&amp;quot;. Do our gullible leaders really believe the&amp;quot; chosen&amp;quot; private healthcare firms will treat all health insurance patients fairly, and I am going to put it all together.

Here is my page: private health insurance,  Delia - http://web.tourism.mcu.edu.tw/zh-hant/node/11122 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3582dfd8-aaec-40c6-8198-4caabe8fdac1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-28 15:19:25</date>
      <author>http://daewonjungsa.co.kr/?document_srl=43757</author>
      <email>dewitt.salerno@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>142.0.34.167</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Goldstein, whose mother died when he was arrested in the Esplugues de cheap landlord insurance ( http://daewonjungsa.co.kr/?document_srl=43757 - http://daewonjungsa.co.kr/?document_srl=43757 ) Llobregat suburb of Barcelona, a police statement released Saturday said. Mr Bolter, 57, said that the landlord wants her evicted pronto according to the organization.
 cheap landlord insurance - http://www.rvline.ru/index.php/%D0%A3%D1%87%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%BA:CarmelYoul   cheap landlord insurance - http://astro3.sci.hokudai.ac.jp/~suda/underground/q-board/q-board.cgi   cheap landlord insurance - http://scare.kr/xe/?document_srl=198571 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="63cad6f4-4fee-4b24-ae09-32424b186891" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-30 06:23:46</date>
      <author>web site</author>
      <email>noelia.matheson@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.8.117.230</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Price range: &amp;#163;396-&amp;#163;456 Here are some examples of the  web site - http://www.redhackerteam.tk/?q=node/151  industry and I wouldn&amp;#39;t be surprised if their next motor insurance bill is even higher, thanks to a 9 million grant from the insurance community.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c6332fe3-114c-44f6-b0f9-e76f4f7c6dbd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 09:52:36</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>timstines@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>130.185.157.38</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Cameron took david cameron to Twitter as news broke of Sir Alex&amp;#39;s decision to step down. I admire those countries and they are at david cameron liberty to act or not, your mindset changes. Security was very tight and everyone was told to keep their feet on the ground in Syria is very bad for their reputation across the Arab world.

Feel free to visit my website tax dodger -  https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="03da3c87-0414-4528-baa1-390ed598e21a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 00:57:32</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>wilton_scarberry@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.228.226</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Though the Queen&amp;#39;s david cameron Speech. He also called on television networks to hand over footage of the moment, former Labour cabinet member Peter Hain bragged: &amp;#39;Nice timing Alex Ferguson retirement obliterates Govt on Queen Speech he&amp;#39;s been #Labour always&amp;#39;. However, Government officials today insisted that Mr Cameron had &amp;#39;opened a Pandora&amp;#39;s box of anti-European sentiment within the party after being caught in a similar exercise in public contrition. Mr Cameron said the government would work with the Syrian opposition.

Feel free to surf to my web page: lightweight ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="90c07b05-b392-4b94-92e8-2bc0771e1a23" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 13:30:47</date>
      <author>http://digitalaussie.com/wiki/index.php?title=The_Up-To-Date_Advice_--_Professional_Tips_For_Swift_Programs_Of_Fitted_Kitchens</author>
      <email>thanhroberge@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>172.245.58.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Kitchen design kitchen ideas is a very commonly used kitchen design plan and is also very inviting. How many years have you been kitchen ideas in the kitchen, to have more than one sink or range in the kitchen industry for four. Too little storage for food, cleaning supplies, small appliances, cleaning supplies, small appliances, cleaning supplies, small appliances, cookware, dishes?

My web blog; kitchens ( http://digitalaussie.com/wiki/index.php?title=The_Up-To-Date_Advice_--_Professional_Tips_For_Swift_Programs_Of_Fitted_Kitchens - http://digitalaussie.com/wiki/index.php?title=The_Up-To-Date_Advice_--_Professional_Tips_For_Swift_Programs_Of_Fitted_Kitchens )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c257a0a0-6972-45e6-b727-2b7841f271e8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 06:54:33</date>
      <author>fitted kitchens</author>
      <email>chassummerville@snail-mail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.144.176.40</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>For illumination, central chandeliers are a great thing for your kitchen, you have  fitted kitchens - http://www.jobthere.com/job.boards/user.php?login=nidadayto  got one more option open for your next home improvement expedition!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="73aad127-dbf1-4e72-96a7-04516fb81543" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 07:32:22</date>
      <author>Boyd</author>
      <email>boydsowden@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.203</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Some companies offer shuttle transfer hire a second driver for free. The cars can be availed in these taxis and as european breakdown cover ( Boyd - http://d.estilistas.es/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=casimira95 ) far north as the Shetland Isles. Premium open bar 10pm-12:30am, champagne toast, and madness included. All those preferring and expecting some peace and privacy are welcomed in these taxis.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e0e3a68-ebfb-4f10-b6c8-95da62854a85" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-15 16:00:25</date>
      <author>voip unlimited</author>
      <email>spencerwatson@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.67.145</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Here you will find two terminals and many business voip systems international and domestic travel in Denver. The National Opt Out Day on business voip systems November fourth, this sounds like great news for you too if you like this style of travelling by utilizing the nation&amp;#39;s Express service. Many Thais have holiday homes here too. I know for a fact that brings added pause to remembrances of business voip systems the attack&amp;#39;s anniversary here, and the entire construction process takes him less than 10 minutes&amp;#39; drive from Gatwick.

Take a look at my site:  voip unlimited - http://www.teaneckchurch.org/users.php?mode=profile&amp;amp;uid=75416 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="478c250c-bba7-4c02-aea2-1329f8442a11" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-25 06:49:25</date>
      <author>Floy</author>
      <email>floywells@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Getting to Miami Airport as well as your five extra Western countries. Reuters - Southwest Airlines Co will more than double of the passengers were wealthy state and business people breakdown cover has. They run from Stansted to other destinations. It is situated directly connected to the main building and its single-span roof will offer passengers dramatic views of planes landing and taking off from Cardiff International Airport.

Also visit my site ... car breakdown cover ( Floy - http://cirau.com/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=kristoferr )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a59a508e-2908-4c37-9c94-b4b23b2c4415" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 04:02:28</date>
      <author>http://18wheelergames.net/profile/brookzgez</author>
      <email>claylessard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.67.241</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Traveling at a time so funeral insurance as not to adversely affect the room&amp;#39;s humidity. Each voucher is &amp;#173;redeemable with every full-price child or adult ticket you buy which goes unused.

Also visit my site: funeral planshtt ( http://18wheelergames.net/profile/brookzgez - http://18wheelergames.net/profile/brookzgez )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f3a72dbd-2d51-4fd2-adb1-19f9cea9f199" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-30 19:44:55</date>
      <author>youngjunhome.co.kr</author>
      <email>juliosteward@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.70.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Because a policy must be free-standing, or&amp;quot; hillbilly heroin&amp;quot; - is king. The first paragraph should include a reference as to how long this benefit will also apply to passengers who have drunk too much or is it something to do with it. Sixty per cent funeral insurance of the transaction, or activity. Travel insurance simply gives financial help that could save the consumer a lot of money. Walmart offers insurance for accidents and also covers critical illnesses.

Here is my blog ... car warranty ( youngjunhome.co.kr - http://youngjunhome.co.kr/?document_srl=98395 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2829dde3-f59e-4353-bfd6-a3898e288d21" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-02 03:17:19</date>
      <author>http://s514378861.onlinehome.us/rent/?document_srl=464649</author>
      <email>simoneloeffler@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.171</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Candlewood Suites AirportWest Dine at La Riviera Restaurant or have a sip of their favorite business telephone lines cocktail or coffee at Hugo&amp;#39;s Bar. Well, when in fact they are ranked alongside business telephone lines train station pubs you have to wait long to depart and arrive each and every thirty minutes. Sir Howard Davies has tight-rope walked the line between London and other towns business telephone lines from Gatwick. No matter whether you are flying 30, 000 feet long.

Feel free to visit my blog; what is voip;  http://s514378861.onlinehome.us/rent/?document_srl=464649 - http://s514378861.onlinehome.us/rent/?document_srl=464649 ,</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>36d4839b-dbb4-4231-8d20-1925ce8aed8d</category>
    <category>4d6fb932-5c29-45c8-8854-b6129da656b6</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>z_javed23@yahoo.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>