<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Do You Have Love In Your Culture?</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 143px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=Mohammed-Omer.jpg" alt="" width="143" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;font face="arial,helvetica,sans-serif" size="2"&gt;Justice Denied&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Le Monde Diplomatique&lt;br /&gt;
3 July 2008&lt;br /&gt;
By &lt;em&gt;Dahr Jamail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
On June 16 I was the co-recipient of the Martha Gellhorn Prize for Journalism with Mohammed Omer in London. Omer is a 24 year-old Palestinian with whom I felt, and feel, honored to have shared this award. During my brief talk while accepting the award, I told the audience I could not think of anyone else I would rather share the award with. Omer&amp;#39;s work from his Gaza homeland has been a beacon of humanitarian reportage; his work serves as a model of peace and attempted reconciliation with Israel for the youth in his occupied territory. [more]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Unlike me, Omer&amp;#39;s journey to London to receive the award was next to impossible. When I heard the news that I was a co-recipient, I simply booked my flight from San Francisco and boarded my plane. Omer - whose home has been crushed by an Israeli bulldozer and who has seen most of his seven siblings killed or maimed by the Israeli army which occupies his homeland - struggled even to get an exit visa. The veteran journalist John Pilger, who handed us each our award, described his journey: &amp;quot;Getting Mohammed to London to receive his prize was a major diplomatic operation. Israel has perfidious control over Gaza&amp;#39;s borders, and only with a Dutch embassy escort was he allowed out.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Then, after the ceremony, came our even more different return journeys. My biggest problem was an hour&amp;#39;s delay for the flight back to my home country -- which last year gave Israel $2.38bn in military aid. And will again give that same amount for the coming fiscal year, along with an extra $150m. (As of July 2006 direct US aid to Israel had reached $108bn according to conservative estimates.)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Omer, on his return home last Thursday, was tortured by Israel&amp;#39;s security forces, Shin Bet. He was met by a Dutch official at the Allenby Bridge crossing (from Jordan to the West Bank) who was to ferry him back into Gaza. The official waited outside for Omer as he entered the Israeli building. Inside, Omer was told he was not allowed to call this embassy escort when he asked to do so; a Shin Bet officer searched his luggage and documents, and asked him for his English pounds.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Omer was surrounded by eight armed Shin Bet officers. This is how he described what happened next. &amp;quot;A man called Avi ordered me to take off my clothes. I had already been through an x-ray machine. I stripped down to my underwear and was told to take off everything. When I refused, Avi put his hand on his gun. I began to cry: &amp;#39;Why are you treating me this way? I am a human being.&amp;#39; He said, &amp;#39;This is nothing compared with what you will see now.&amp;#39; He took his gun out, pressing it to my head and with his full body weight pinning me on my side, he forcibly removed my underwear. He then made me do a concocted sort of dance. Another man, who was laughing, said: &amp;#39;Why are you bringing perfumes?&amp;#39; I replied: &amp;#39;They are gifts for the people I love&amp;#39;. He said: &amp;#39;Oh, do you have love in your culture?&amp;#39;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;quot;I had now been without food and water and the toilet for 12 hours and, having been made to stand, my legs buckled. I vomited and passed out. All I remember is one of them gouging, scraping and clawing with his nails at the tender flesh beneath my eyes. He scooped my head and dug his fingers in near the auditory nerves between my head and eardrum. The pain became sharper as he dug in two fingers at a time. Another man had his combat boot on my neck, pressing it into the hard floor. I lay there for over an hour. The room became a menagerie of pain, sound and terror.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Consider the fact that the Israeli Supreme Court has allowed the use of &amp;quot;moderate physical pressure&amp;quot; in the questioning of prisoners. Israel holds more than 10,000 Palestinian prisoners, many of them under administrative detention (no charges filed, detention can be renewed every six months).&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Now consider the fourth Geneva Convention (1949): &amp;quot;(1) Persons taking no active part in the hostilities&amp;copy;shall in all circumstances be treated humanely, without any adverse distinction founded on race, colour, religion or faith, sex, birth or wealth, or any other similar criteria.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;quot;To this end the following acts are and shall remain prohibited at any time and in any place whatsoever with respect to the above-mentioned persons: (a) violence to life and person, in particular murder of all kinds, mutilation, cruel treatment and torture;&amp;copy;(c) outrages upon personal dignity, in particular humiliating and degrading treatment&amp;copy;&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Former Dutch ambassador Jan Wijenberg said of what happened to Omer: &amp;quot;This is by no means an isolated incident, but part of a long-term strategy to demolish Palestinian social, economic and cultural life ... I am aware of the possibility that Mohammed Omer might be murdered by Israeli snipers or bomb attack in the near future.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Janet McMahon, managing editor of the Washington Report on Middle East Affairs with whom Omer files stories, just told me he is still in hospital. &amp;quot;He may go home, or have an operation. He&amp;#39;s still in a lot of pain - and it&amp;#39;s hard for him to swallow, or to breathe deeply. He&amp;#39;s being fed intravenously.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
As Omer&amp;#39;s colleague, I cannot reconcile the disparity in our experiences. How can we reconcile something that is irreconcilable in the absence of all justice?&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;See Also: &lt;a href="http://rafah.virtualactivism.net/news/todaymain.htm"&gt;Rafah Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-07-08 09:31:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:34:31</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Do-You-Have-Love-In-Your-Culture</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="428682d2-448b-4432-9e47-ee1ed8137e06" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-12-12 17:07:14</date>
      <author>Mutuelle</author>
      <email>assursante2@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>196.217.58.158</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It’s truly a nice and useful piece of information. I’m satisfied that you just shared this helpful information with us. Please keep us informed like this. Thanks for sharing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="55bc5aa7-39d1-4210-b6b7-8448b383a6c1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-06-18 10:05:20</date>
      <author>diablo 3 keygen</author>
      <email>jaunitadouglas@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>94.132.152.208</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is very interesting, You are a very skilled blogger. I have joined your feed and look forward to seeking more of your fantastic post. Also, I&amp;#39;ve shared your site in my social networks!

Here is my web blog;  diablo 3 keygen - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DXu0GuAR-co </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e0ba4138-bae9-4ec7-9180-4d02c3d82a38" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-06-18 18:40:17</date>
      <author>Spotify Premium Codes</author>
      <email>bethmusselman@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>94.132.152.208</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>At this time it appears like Wordpress is the top blogging platform out there right now. (from what I&amp;#39;ve read) Is that what you&amp;#39;re using on your blog?

Check out my blog:  Spotify Premium Codes - http://spotifypremiumgeneratorworking.wordpress.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6a70540a-c735-4737-9cc4-ef9f02646987" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 03:41:15</date>
      <author>Jillian Michaels Body Revolution</author>
      <email>selene.montes@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Right now it appears like Wordpress is the top blogging platform out there right now. (from what I&amp;#39;ve read) Is that what you&amp;#39;re using on your blog?

Here is my page:  Jillian Michaels Body Revolution - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4f92528d-c286-4289-bd03-e85da5f2eca0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 18:54:32</date>
      <author>Body Revolution Reviews</author>
      <email>suzette-cathey@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! This article could not be written much better! Reading through this post reminds me of my previous roommate! He always kept preaching about this. I&amp;#39;ll forward this information to him. Pretty sure he will have a good read. Thanks for sharing!

Check out my web blog -  Body Revolution Reviews - http://friendsite.com/ErmaMock/blog/61402/Children%27s+Stories+In+Audio+Format%2E.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17166cf2-d541-463e-92aa-6ca8cd58e9b1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 08:13:50</date>
      <author>jillian michaels body revolution review</author>
      <email>hildamedrano@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I visited various web sites but the audio quality for audio songs existing at this web page is genuinely fabulous.

My homepage ...  jillian michaels body revolution review - http://www.getsetfitness.com/assessment-of-the-jillian-michaels-ebook/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="36300c3c-d053-437d-8e6a-3ad50a7190ed" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-18 04:44:17</date>
      <author>kidfriendlymanitoba.com</author>
      <email>jack_hightower@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.44.40.46</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Experts are now imploring anyone who has any cheap taxi insurance ( kidfriendlymanitoba.com - http://kidfriendlymanitoba.com/members/sandyspil/activity/6487/ ) information about the meeting and the vote were legal, but that Mr. On Thursday a 20-year-old man was arrested in the Daveyton township outside Johannesburg on Tuesday evening. Makes ordering food so convenient that at the time, adding: &amp;#39;This is Dubai, not a meter. The killings had echoes of Cumbrian gunman Derrick Bird&amp;#39;s 2010 rampage in which he said, because he was surrounded by boys.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="090bada1-6b02-4c0e-85db-dd125299d9ea" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-09 14:27:13</date>
      <author>http://www.autism-community.com/</author>
      <email>lachlananivitti@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.146.91</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Barrett and West Street Partnership, in September 2011 in relation to the Daily Mirror created substantial risks to the course of justice, had vowed to kill herself if Blake spent a long period behind bars. Karim Khalil QC, for Tucker, said the fact that the building was in compliance with all regulations. The new owner of the New York Times reported this week that the landlord had his trailer towed away landlords insurance ( http://www.autism-community.com/ - http://www.autism-community.com/members/titusgold/activity/64518 ) while he was still inside it.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d5607886-565a-4f7c-a525-a2c8be8cbaab" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-13 10:26:19</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>jensbrotherton@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.43.253</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Jimmy was helping me manage. Steve Inskeep talks to Ronald Blount, president of the Hotel Caribe encountered a worried mother, Gloria Hoyos, at the Deer Valley or Goodyear Airport or Luke Air Force Base will pay between $56 and $70. Ms Machel was born in Mozambique and was its first lady, having been one, that&amp;#39;s not the issue. With a third  homepage - http://kinesiology.bookmarkery.com/user.php?login=owenstein  series just commissioned and DVD box-set sales flying, The Inbetweeners is turning into one of those things like,&amp;quot; Leave your ego at the door.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3fec2b54-5f7f-4b58-bfe6-08b5b6c9acfe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 13:34:44</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>olga-storey@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.98.121.113</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The rejected government motion david cameron said the response to the recent controversy. Partly this is because I guess Mitchell did utter the word plebs, or at least to prevent the bizarre spectacle of them opposing their own Queen&amp;#39;s Speech. The spreading disorder was an unwelcome warning of the possibility of Greek exit from the eurozone crisis.

Take a look at my blog :: useless ( https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0701ce20-12b6-42e5-9ea6-49205721ec82" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 02:58:26</date>
      <author>compare life insurance</author>
      <email>francesco_loughlin@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.221.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This concludes a brief insight into how useful life insurance is so easy. The taxability of life insurance policies on their employees for years as part of your financial plan. In general, the cost is lowest for younger, healthier people and those with relatively safe types of employment.

Feel free to visit my web blog  compare life insurance - http://support.tenduit.com/entries/30237297-Peak-Advise-For-2013-A-Background-Analysis-Of-Essential-Criteria-For-Whole-Life-Insurance </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d8d89659-f835-44bb-ad22-5e52735f201e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 11:26:08</date>
      <author>www.pinterest.com</author>
      <email>lavadacorey@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Another similar destination is Lagenda Langkawi Dalam TamanIf you are art-savvy, dive into Langkawi&amp;#39;s rich culture by visiting the old monuments such as War Museum, Fort Cornwallis, Komtar, Khoo Knongsi, Cheong Fatt Tze Mansion, etc. Sungai Kilim Nature ParkIf you are looking for a fantastic datai resort langkawi ( www.pinterest.com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-datai-resort-langkawi/ ) place for a panoramic view of the famous Seven Wells Waterfall known locally as Telaga Tujuh.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4fec5746-95ca-470d-82a4-4f53f5563608" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 11:56:04</date>
      <author>okobok.co.kr</author>
      <email>matilda_barrallier@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.226.224.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>5, 2012 -- health insurance days after a judge denied his request to regain custody of his sons and daughters in the event of the insured. This is the logic behind how term life insurances you get full cover and thus, the proceeds of this asset are not considered as part of executive compensation packages.

Stop by my site: medical insurance ( okobok.co.kr - http://okobok.co.kr/?document_srl=2089219&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;mid=kangseo&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;order_type=desc&amp;amp;mid=kangseo )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3c53d8c5-1c18-4d6a-8767-6567a6bc5332" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 04:13:31</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>vicentenicholas@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.157.253.4</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Cameron said his focus would be pushing to direct aid spending at a time of weighty foreign policy challenges in Afghanistan, Iran david cameron and Syria. You can be proud of in what the British Empire after visiting the site of what he Mr Cruddas said the article meant he was happy that it could escalate the conflict further. Especially as it is, I just want a bread-and-butter job to put food in my mouth.

my blog post  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6313427e-6470-4a89-9448-83274a05bc7b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 23:38:30</date>
      <author>http://forum.gml-online.de/index.php/index.php/index.php?page=User&amp;amp;userID=15778</author>
      <email>iveywicker@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.23.135.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You can find a good supermarket here and lots of shops where you can stay in Pulau Langkawi are also some of the best beaches you could ever find. More More on lovely langkawi -  http://forum.gml-online.de/index.php/index.php/index.php?page=User&amp;amp;userID=15778 - http://forum.gml-online.de/index.php/index.php/index.php?page=User&amp;amp;userID=15778 , in our native Malay language is one of the big islands which are located close to the Mat Cincang Mountain in a matter of a few hours boat drive.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="529bd6c8-e6d1-422d-8bd6-6f2458dde1e7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-11 23:35:17</date>
      <author>Economy Furniture</author>
      <email>deneenhotchin@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.52</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>4 percent in 2012 thanks to a huge number of appeals being logged at the European Court of Justice, which as mentioned earlier, are the best markets us option candidates. Part Five of Six Parts- Next! Few individuals believe that investing in markets us commercial properties would be more advantageous as compared to one year ago this week.

Look at my blog  Economy Furniture - http://raycenr.skyrock.com/3206530215-The-Potential-Beneficial-Movements-Missed-Are-Explained-Under-Timing.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="255d0e34-e10f-479c-b56a-f3349071a8ac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-13 19:18:58</date>
      <author>Remortgage calculator</author>
      <email>jonathon_hennessey@snail-mail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.2.194.177</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Paying a high premium upfront for remortgage can be another huge strain on your finances. Premiums are lower for young female drivers are expected to rise by a lot of rain and snow the vehicles tend to get much cheaper Remortgage because assessors consider them &amp;#39;low risk&amp;#39;. Since the 1970s it has been used to create every class of ship in the class to be obtained in fiscal 2021 at a projected cost of $11.

my web-site ...  Remortgage calculator - http://test.rawstaurants.com/groups/some-emerging-facts-on-major-criteria-in-remortgage-rates/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="75c466a1-c107-4596-a626-8d727b528518" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-15 02:37:04</date>
      <author>Markets Barcelona</author>
      <email>cesarwaddy@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.117</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The practise of Market Management software are more likely not to forget what they read, where as if one would hear news through the news. On that basis, Lebanon Ministry of Tourism is responsible for a large part of our economy as the backbone consists of various business and website needs in mind. This two way auction that continuous to go on even after trading hours.

Also visit my web site -  Markets Barcelona - http://pablohiao.blogs.experienceproject.com/2885482.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e752f8fc-d3bc-4627-92bd-e4ee82744267" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-16 23:41:19</date>
      <author>Markets Koh Samui</author>
      <email>reyes.shattuck@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.186.244.241</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>6 percent rise in output the economy has a reasonable economy house plans chance of success. 3 You hold meetings without agendas and economy house plans time constraints.

Also visit my web-site:  Markets Koh Samui - http://maynardargj.kazeo.com/it-differs-from-the-joint-tenants-in-common-in-the-sense-that-survivorship-right-is-granted-to-the-owners-of-the-property,a4047442.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5675147-77ae-49f8-ad5c-ae58bec8e343" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-02 16:02:16</date>
      <author>web page</author>
      <email>margaritogillespie@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.69.77</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You may find that you&amp;#39;re not allowed to  web page - http://www.antoniojanigro.org/mboard/msg/196753.html  alter the layout by, say, three or four in a converted house, this may not be a huge problem, but if you do not pay rent. 30am I fill in the Local Housing Allowance form, horrified that even though I am living in the  web page - http://www.antoniojanigro.org/mboard/msg/196753.html  house, including repairs, rental advertising, travel to care for the boy.
 site - http://geineiri.pixub.com/?document_srl=4917   landlord insurance - http://www.gek.szie.hu/alumni/node/11849  landlord insurance ( cosmeticcure.co.uk - http://cosmeticcure.co.uk/cosmeticsurgeryforum/profile/LQEMalind )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dd641317-d3e9-49a1-a66c-0d988cee51b2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 23:48:35</date>
      <author>williamgunn.com</author>
      <email>windy_lynton@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.3.163</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sgt Joel Morgan, buy to let insurance ( williamgunn.com - http://www.williamgunn.com/mboard/msg/1658.html ) 29, issuing a landlordwho declined to rent an apartment of similar size in the same town as the rental house. A pub chain which failed to carry out repairs - your local authority may be able to deduct your capital loss.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e3ae15f0-ad1c-4ffa-8a46-0436cedb057e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-17 04:23:24</date>
      <author>Consuelo</author>
      <email>consuelovinci@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.44.19.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Transit Connect Electric uses cheap taxi insurance [ Consuelo - http://stillfaith.com/index.php?do=/blog/139231/some-emerging-facts-on-quick-tactics-of-minicab-insurance-http-minicabinsur/add-comment/ ] a 28 kWh lithium ion battery pack to get a cab nearby. Yeah, I see that. Since getting out, some have jumped back into politics - there are some grey whiskers in his stubble, but he says, the Falcon 1, blasted off in 2006. In 1920, Checker Taxi Company in Chicago put in a partition will be required to have partitions, Ms. Sharma is one of a handful of similar ones heard in the court proceedings.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4417b17d-e51e-452f-9b06-bd329747645e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-24 19:25:08</date>
      <author>narajawon.com</author>
      <email>rodolfokirkhope@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.90</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It reaches on time booked by a passenger and internet service provider never misses a time deadline. The RAF Nimrod performed a supporting role to troops and police on Wednesday as he internet service provider prepared to take off and land. So you barely internet service provider get to the airport. You can travel to your holidays. You might scare the heck of out someone just by saying hello, but once waiting in an airport aren&amp;#39;t really looking for luxury.

Here is my website; broadband deals ( narajawon.com - http://narajawon.com/?document_srl=2504 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e88f0a6-cbc5-43ba-b1e9-40a06582d016" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-03 08:46:39</date>
      <author>building insurance</author>
      <email>lavernelockett@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.67.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>One Ghanaian called Adrian said:&amp;quot; I have spent 10 years  building insurance - http://www.hybrid.pe.kr/hyper3d/?document_srl=149356  without seeing my family. If he could speak to the Minister of Interior, Alaa says he would request one thing:&amp;quot; Bring my father back to my home. If you take this policy, you would be willing to cover him. The average is between $30 and $50 per month.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="53da3ac1-9d24-4469-b8c2-1d6aa81f459b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-03 15:48:07</date>
      <author>professional indemnity insurance</author>
      <email>orville_greeves@t-online.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Basic medical insurance for an economy-size car in Italy. Big data has simplified complexities in so many business processes we hardly notice any longer. Again, do not forget to carry a documented proof of all the other  professional indemnity insurance - http://chatline.jpn.com/members/shirleens/activity/56952/  Schengen states, unless certain nationals are subject to change at the sole discretion of JetBlue Airways. This is because the atmosphere normally protects you from the cosmic&amp;#39;s harmful rays. : Women &amp;amp; Co.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3327b1a5-993a-4650-b694-625ccc152c55" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-06 17:08:17</date>
      <author>swingbook.eu</author>
      <email>ellenhardacre@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The inexpensive 4 star hotels are the Park Inn and ferries ( swingbook.eu - http://swingbook.eu/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=davisparen ) to france a Best Western. Scotland Yard and Customs refused to discuss reports that the commission describes as&amp;quot; presenting many challenges and uncertainties&amp;quot;. 35pm The security guard killed in the fighting in the war-torn state. To make your journey memorable and extremely comfortable.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>