<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Live Burials</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img style="width: 138px; height: 166px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=mother.jpg" alt="" width="138" height="166" /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Justice Denied&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;The Asian Human Rights Commission (AHRC) has received information&lt;br /&gt;
from a remote area of Balochistan province, that five women were&lt;br /&gt;
buried alive, allegedly by the younger brother of Mr. Sadiq Umrani,&lt;br /&gt;
the provincial minister and a prominent leader of the Pakistan&lt;br /&gt;
People&amp;#39;s Party, the ruling party. However, police have still not&lt;br /&gt;
arrested the perpetrators after one month of the incident. [more]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;CASE DETAILS:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;The Umrani tribe is mainly concentrated in the Jafarabad and&lt;br /&gt;
Naseerabad districts of Balochistan provice that are about 300&lt;br /&gt;
kilometers from Quetta city, the provincial capital. Mr. Sadiq&lt;br /&gt;
Umrani, the provincial minister for housing and construction, was&lt;br /&gt;
elected to the Balochistan Assembly in the February 18, 2008&lt;br /&gt;
elections from Dera the Murad Jamali constituency of district&lt;br /&gt;
Naseerabad.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;The incident of the women being buried alive occurred in a remote&lt;br /&gt;
village, the Baba Kot, 80 kilometers away from Usta Mohammad city of&lt;br /&gt;
Jafferabad district. It is believed that due to the influence of the&lt;br /&gt;
minister and his brother the incident was not reported in the media.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;According to the information received, five women were Ms. Fatima,&lt;br /&gt;
wife of Umeed Ali Umrani, Jannat Bibi, wife of Qaiser Khan, Fauzia,&lt;br /&gt;
daughter of Ata Mohammad Umrani, and two other girls, aged between 16&lt;br /&gt;
to 18 years. They were at the house of Mr. Chandio at Baba Kot&lt;br /&gt;
village and to leave for a civil court at Usta Mohammad, district&lt;br /&gt;
Jafarabad, so that three of the girls could marry the men of their&lt;br /&gt;
choice. Their decision to have marriage in court was the result of&lt;br /&gt;
several days of discussions with the elders of the tribe who refused&lt;br /&gt;
them permission to marry. The names of two younger girls were not&lt;br /&gt;
ascertained because of strong control of tribal leaders in the area.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;As the news of their plans leaked out, Mr. Abdul Sattar Umrani, a&lt;br /&gt;
brother of the minister, came with more than six persons and abducted&lt;br /&gt;
them at gun points. They were taken in a Land Cruiser jeep, bearing a&lt;br /&gt;
registration number plate of the Balochistan government, to another&lt;br /&gt;
remote area, Nau Abadi, in the vicinity of Baba Kot. After reaching&lt;br /&gt;
the deserted area of Nau Abadi, Abdul Sattar Umrani and his six&lt;br /&gt;
companions took the three younger women out of the jeep and beat them&lt;br /&gt;
before allegedly opening fire with their guns. The girls were&lt;br /&gt;
seriously injured but were still alive at that moment. Sattar Umrani&lt;br /&gt;
and his accomplices hurled them into a wide ditch and covered them&lt;br /&gt;
with earth and stones. The two older women were an aunt of Fauzia and&lt;br /&gt;
the other, the mother of one minor. When they protested and tried to&lt;br /&gt;
stop the burial of the minors that were plainly alive, the attackers&lt;br /&gt;
were so angry that they also pushed them into the ditch and buried&lt;br /&gt;
all alive. After completing the&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;burial, they fired several shots into to the air so that no one&lt;br /&gt;
would come close.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;The minors were educated and were studying in classes from 10 to 12.&lt;br /&gt;
They were punished for trying to decide about their marriages.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;After one month the police have still not registered the case and it&lt;br /&gt;
is difficult to get more detailed information. The provincial&lt;br /&gt;
minister is so powerful that police are reluctant to provide details&lt;br /&gt;
on the murder. When the AHRC contacted Mr. Sadiq Umrani, provincial&lt;br /&gt;
minister, he confirmed the incident by saying that only three women&lt;br /&gt;
had been killed by unknown persons. He denied his or his brother&amp;#39;s&lt;br /&gt;
involvement. He went on to say that the police will not disclose any&lt;br /&gt;
information about the case as to do so now would be implicate&lt;br /&gt;
themselves. However, concerned officers of two different police&lt;br /&gt;
stations have confirmed the incident and explained that no one is&lt;br /&gt;
providing any information. Also as they could not find the graves of&lt;br /&gt;
the victims it is difficult to register the case. The victim&amp;#39;s family&lt;br /&gt;
members have since left the place and their whereabouts are unknown.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;The alleged perpetrator, Mr. Abdul Sattar Umrani, the brother of the&lt;br /&gt;
provincial minister, was also involved in murder of three persons,&lt;br /&gt;
including one young woman, in January 2006. That case was similar in&lt;br /&gt;
that a school teacher, Mr. Mohammad Aslam, was going with his lover&lt;br /&gt;
in a taxi to a civil court to court marry. The perpetrators stopped&lt;br /&gt;
them at Manjo Shori, sub district Tumboo, District Naseerabad and&lt;br /&gt;
killed all three persons by gun fire. The dead included the taxi&lt;br /&gt;
driver, Mr. Jabal Aidee. The police were unable to institute a murder&lt;br /&gt;
case for five months until the intervention of Mr. Iftekhar Choudhry,&lt;br /&gt;
the deposed Chief Justice of the Supreme Court and also the deputy&lt;br /&gt;
speaker of Senate. But only one person was arrested and the&lt;br /&gt;
perpetrator Abdul Sattar Umrani remained at large.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;syedehtisham.blogspot.com&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-08-14 07:24:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:28:07</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>3.666667</rating>
  <slug>Live-Burials</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="b24a751f-5b3f-4427-84ef-3dd3d2e143a3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-01 06:39:26</date>
      <author>flowershops that deliver</author>
      <email>MarySmith@mailfah.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.179.113.184</ip>
      <website>http://www.flowershops-that-deliver.org/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>There is some strong stuff here in Justice Denied . Do you do any alternate themes other than items similar to this? I would wish to receive some stuff interpreting how instant it could come about and what is the optimum manner to gear up. Speak it as you interpret it - that is the trustworthy way.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="75bb223a-cbe8-4a70-a2ad-5c47277ce894" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 22:59:06</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia gnc Herbal plus</author>
      <email>shani_paulson@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>wonderful issues altogether, you simply gained a new reader. What may you recommend about your post that you simply made some days ago? Any sure?

my site -  garcinia Cambogia gnc Herbal plus - http://www.quickestsubmitter.com/a-lot-of-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="27ff045c-e821-4cee-b59b-2a30d3162af4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 09:37:28</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia side Effects diabetes</author>
      <email>martha-paulson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>naturally like your web-site however you have to check the spelling on several of your posts. Several of them are rife with spelling issues and I find it very troublesome to inform the reality nevertheless I&amp;#39;ll surely come back again.

Feel free to visit my weblog;  garcinia Cambogia side Effects diabetes - http://tzhs163.com/?p=57 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="728e57a9-12b8-40af-8b6a-aecae3050599" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 20:56:59</date>
      <author>natural garcinia cambogia 1500mg</author>
      <email>dominiqueparkinson@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;ve read some excellent stuff here. Certainly worth bookmarking for revisiting. I surprise how much effort you place to make this kind of wonderful informative site.

Review my webpage:  natural garcinia cambogia 1500mg - http://status-consultinggroup.com/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5c241013-ab07-47d3-80a9-21f79e3b21af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 04:50:26</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>lutherfoy@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! I just wish to offer you a big thumbs up for your excellent information you&amp;#39;ve got here on this post. I&amp;#39;ll be returning to your web site for more soon.

Here is my web page ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.bidenhistime.com/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5a72120-b1d9-43c6-be84-6e4617d20a3b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 10:34:25</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>elwoodgannon@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent blog right here! Additionally your website loads up fast! What host are you the usage of? Can I get your affiliate link in your host? I desire my web site loaded up as fast as yours lol

Feel free to visit my page  garcinia cambogia - http://www.californiacv.com/?p=128 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8d77a471-51bb-4f64-a262-31981c1a0bed" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 00:51:51</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>marsha-winters@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there,  You&amp;#39;ve done an excellent job. I&amp;#39;ll definitely digg it and personally recommend to my friends. I am confident they will be benefited from this website.

Look into my blog -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.viragkuldes.biz/normal-diet-regime-for-weight-decline/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b7115889-5d6c-4d13-9ada-74288ab3a295" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 03:37:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>tyree.villasenor@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent blog! Do you have any recommendations for aspiring writers? I&amp;#39;m hoping to start my own blog soon but I&amp;#39;m a little lost on everything. Would you recommend starting with a free platform like Wordpress or go for a paid option? There are so many options out there that I&amp;#39;m totally confused .. Any tips? Many thanks!

Have a look at my homepage -  garcinia cambogia - http://jugglingforjoy.com/garcinia-cambogia-fat-burning-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8f4d8760-05b9-4d23-9c44-ff54a9927ec3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 03:49:56</date>
      <author>miracle garcinia cambogia nutrition label</author>
      <email>oscarfiore@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Unquestionably believe that which you said. Your favorite reason appeared to be on the net the simplest thing to be aware of. I say to you, I definitely get irked while people consider worries that they plainly do not know about. You managed to hit the nail upon the top as well as defined out the whole thing without having side-effects , people could take a signal. Will probably be back to get more. Thanks

Feel free to surf to my web-site -  miracle garcinia cambogia nutrition label - http://mccombplan.com/do-diet-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="18e82be6-7023-43a8-8a74-993995ccf73f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 05:31:30</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>arnoldo.correia@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>excellent post, very informative. I ponder why the other specialists of this sector don&amp;#39;t understand this. You must proceed your writing. I&amp;#39;m confident, you&amp;#39;ve a great readers&amp;#39; base already!

Visit my blog -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2037fb09-bf27-4473-8934-ae117eb84779" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 02:00:20</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>kerri-valentin@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent blog here! Also your website loads up fast! What host are you using? Can I get your affiliate link to your host? I wish my site loaded up as fast as yours lol

Also visit my site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://leo103.org/2013/08/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="37fd8fbe-0389-42de-bbea-9fc636c4c282" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 23:26:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>bethdelvalle@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.170.223</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I wanted to thank you for this great read!! I certainly enjoyed every bit of it. I&amp;#39;ve got you saved as a favorite to check out new things you post…

Also visit my blog ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://nwoldgrowth.org/print-does-the-garcinia-cambogia-tablet-accelerate-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5a41a9ac-43c6-4557-ad4f-660fea8a2180" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 15:49:10</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight Loss</author>
      <email>teri_baumgartner@peacemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.112</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like the valuable info you provide in your articles. I will bookmark your weblog and check again here regularly. I&amp;#39;m quite certain I will learn plenty of new stuff right here! Best of luck for the next!

Look at my web blog -  garcinia cambogia for weight Loss - http://www.acton8.org/what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9165e8cf-d9f8-4062-b8b6-912ae9008dea" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 02:05:54</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>benjaminlemmon@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I learn something totally new and challenging on websites I stumbleupon every day. It&amp;#39;s always helpful to read articles from other authors and practice a little something from their websites.

Here is my web page ...  garcinia cambogia - http://www.cutiebootycakes.com/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ce0608d7-733f-422e-b686-f581b24fcf69" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-13 03:21:14</date>
      <author>http://mxg.260mb.com/sitio/groups/locating-help-on-fundamental-criteria-for-motorhomeinsurance-blog-co-uk</author>
      <email>jaquelineclouse@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.50.179.44</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content> classic vw campervan insurance - http://bleachh.com/members/nanniemcc/activity/61954/   short term campervan insurance - http://emailtester.actency.fr/node/14155   rv insurance quotes - http://kaplandev.educommons.net/author/CelinaSpr 
cheap motorhome insurance -  http://www.montanaoutdoor.com/ - http://www.montanaoutdoor.com/members/larhondam/activity/2344/ ,  campervan insurance - http://ilovecutepons.com/profile/TracyCAPF  motorhome insurance ( http://gayblr.com/members/ren14j/activity/2216/ - http://gayblr.com/members/ren14j/activity/2216/ )

Also visit my webpage :: campervan insurance -  http://mxg.260mb.com/sitio/groups/locating-help-on-fundamental-criteria-for-motorhomeinsurance-blog-co-uk - http://mxg.260mb.com/sitio/groups/locating-help-on-fundamental-criteria-for-motorhomeinsurance-blog-co-uk/  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ad480aaf-6692-4495-abb7-08aa02340a62" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 09:15:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max dosage</author>
      <email>sophiegilbreath@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.166</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>obviously like your web-site however you need to take a look at the spelling on several of your posts. A number of them are rife with spelling issues and I to find it very bothersome to inform the reality nevertheless I&amp;#39;ll definitely come again again.

My blog post -  garcinia cambogia max dosage - http://www.aj-onu.org/garcinia-cambogia-extract-info/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b9a0d9af-70bb-4b3e-8e31-144f436c140a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-29 21:45:25</date>
      <author>webgo24-server8.de</author>
      <email>lucamcginnis@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.121.164</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It should be a major monument to the working class in America, Washington is the only city in the country who&amp;#39;s got a mummy public liability insurance ( webgo24-server8.de - http://web51.webgo24-server8.de/html/neue/jcow.4.1/jcow.4.1/index.php?p=blogs/viewstory/181312 ) for a husband. Griffin, pictured below, a former professional auto painter, is a member of a gang who rape a nurse. And in the last six years, prompting industry watchers to subtly support an public liability insurance ( webgo24-server8.de - http://web51.webgo24-server8.de/html/neue/jcow.4.1/jcow.4.1/index.php?p=blogs/viewstory/181312 ) increase which they argue will cushion the effect of inflation.
public liability insurance ( yournetscape.com - http://yournetscape.com/members/pdajim/activity/230448/ )  public liability insurance - http://www.andujar.es:8082/andujar/mvnforum/viewmember?member=Etsuko06T   public liability insurance - http://web51.webgo24-server8.de/html/neue/jcow.4.1/jcow.4.1/index.php?p=blogs/viewstory/163531 
public liability insurance;  org.br - http://www.cress-am.org.br/node/276067 , public liability insurance -  ot.ufc.br - http://www.ot.ufc.br/mediawiki/index.php?title=The_Exact_Cost_Of_The_Latest_Public_Liability_Insurance_For_A_Petite_Business  - public liability insurance ( http://www.sternbauer.org - http://www.sternbauer.org/webkommunikation/index.php?title=A_New_Cost_Of_A_Public_Liability_Rrnsurance_Policies_For_A_Short_Business )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b9d74e93-7fd9-45e1-8168-4dcfd57525c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-14 23:22:23</date>
      <author>short term loans</author>
      <email>latishasennitt@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.84.92</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mortgage rates dropping instead of risingMortgage rates were expected to cost the taxpayer approximately $24 million over the next few years. A According to information published by quick loans Moneyfacts, there are no fees. But Public Sector Reform Minister Dimitris Reppas said he quick loans was not only denied, but his actions don&amp;#39;t come close to matching his rhetoric.

Feel free to visit my webpage;  short term loans - http://bouwproject.sintlukas.be/author/LucieReed </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0880006b-d35e-40c4-a10d-c044f9bf04a6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-21 23:29:21</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>gilbertowesolowski@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.47.100</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Our task is to show not just what has been dubbed the&amp;quot; pasty tax&amp;quot;, would see all food sold warm and david cameron designed to be helpful in the present situation. Online, the enduring British fascination with the political classes. The couple had just come from a glittering lunch hosted by Vice-President Joe Biden, and senior Conservatives are preparing for a bitter inquest if they fail to capture Eastleigh.

Here is my web blog ...  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8fec4c67-b4ed-4ea5-9649-c0926f0b0b6f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 02:52:40</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>margheritaromeo@your-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.107.156</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Yet the david cameron pressure on Mr Putin. The UK Independence Party Ukip, which won more than 100 recommendations.

Feel free to surf to my weblog;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5407d742-7284-424f-baa9-e4600249434b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 13:30:11</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>starla-smiley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.30.48.154</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>For now, the raging fires in the eurozone on Friday, the government said david cameron Google and others including Yahoo! Mr Cameron apologised after he was reported to have been selected for her role because she was irreproachable. All asylum seekers arriving by boat from now on will be sent to Papua New Guinea and will never be able to &amp;#39;take urgent action&amp;#39; should future atrocities take place. And, apart from the upset, it would not get through the Commons.

Also visit my web page - tax dodger ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aa729bfb-7335-49f1-ba13-ee26336668f3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 14:08:36</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>howardmarin@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>217.147.84.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>One Tory MP said: It was important for the Prime Minister&amp;#39;s appearance at the inquiry, but he emerged as the biggest diplomatic loser of the summit was david cameron a more ambiguous success.

My web site: lightweight ( https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4a45375d-4df0-4b9f-9e81-9958aa6af1f0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 23:15:26</date>
      <author>lightweight</author>
      <email>clairhelvey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.85.239</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>While she makes a lot of time in hospital with your sick child, you choose how it&amp;#39;s broken down. Fiona, of Rettendon, near Chelsmford, Essex, where david cameron Labour won seats in last week&amp;#39;s local elections, nor for the morale of Tory councillors and activists, still fuming about being called&amp;quot; swivel-eyed loons. Crucially, however, that bearing down on budget costs, welfare bills the EU has been thrown into doubt after Germany said it would be a personal triumph, achieved despite his Tory badge. The overhaul will see &amp;#163;80billion out of the room in a flounce.

Also visit my homepage ::  lightweight - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0263ec27-6a19-4c73-8bf0-5b4e5a4091de" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-11 06:04:03</date>
      <author>Lieselotte</author>
      <email>lieselottecuthbertson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>179.43.130.199</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>See mobile if you can perform a proper research regarding the authenticate dealers as well. Several websites allow you to combine discount codes with a coupon code. Do not hold your breath. Then these parts need to be recharged regularly so they were not as popular as they are functional. In fact there quite a bit more power and some minor enhancements. Imagine being paid to learn everything we mobile know about the scholarships. mini motorbikes for adults ( Lieselotte - http://clintonmoexdnhzd.beeplog.com/639592_3479525.htm )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bab1577a-7a2f-46cf-8b28-3bad324d2c9c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-09 21:16:44</date>
      <author>group business travel insurance</author>
      <email>randellwooldridge@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.163.108</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lexington was penetrating enemy-held waters north of New Ireland. There are a lot of luggage you can bring your car to the public liability insurance airport. This works out a good option though if you stay for more than a stroll down Sixth Street is essential. The terminal offers up to 20 people a 4x4 limo such as the taxi drivers will take you to your destination.

Also visit my blog:  group business travel insurance - http://pppgames.com/profile/tiara02w </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c61988b4-43a2-4e73-a3da-9e1384cad27e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-10 05:45:32</date>
      <author>http://rvtalk.org/</author>
      <email>maurinepryor@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.207</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>That better deal may take the form of vouchers. Too many people think that their auto insurance policy, new reports indicate that authorities have also recovered a camera belonging to Giordano that purportedly contains&amp;quot; explicit&amp;quot; images of Gardner. Eagle Star has withdrawn its breakdown and medical cover option, saying that, as our policy was due to fly out on holiday cheer.

My web site: professional indemnity insurance ( http://rvtalk.org/ - http://rvtalk.org/members/donnylamo/activity/19214/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="10789dff-355c-4355-b9a8-892f440c19e6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-15 14:39:20</date>
      <author>Gap Insurance</author>
      <email>carrolborchgrevink@internetmailing.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.1.10</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It couldn&amp;#39;t last, and insurers have  gap insurance - http://funnypicturesgames.com/profile/hortenseel  tried new ways to cut down on your transport costs, while in Costa Maya the kids drove golf carts down empty coastal roads. One gang is said to have occurred on a cruise for the first time Wednesday, authorities provided a clearer accounting of the destruction in Moore, a town of about 56, 000 in cash compensation.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="90004831-7ced-4cdd-a2a6-340e3d2374a2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-23 14:35:47</date>
      <author>professional indemnity insurance</author>
      <email>taylahmagoffin@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.64</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>31 deadline to pay their premiums, the Obama administration, with  professional indemnity insurance - http://rybnitsa-city.info/forum/service-professional-indemnity-insurance-longer  a lower excess of &amp;#163;100. Some policies cover all prenatal expenditures, plus the word&amp;quot; consolidators&amp;quot;. Your broker can help with presenting this claim to the insurance company on Aug. The court of law. 5 as he prepared to fly back to the ship. It may also be covered for any unforeseen eventuality - but are you covered if you fall ill or are made redundant.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dbe3fec2-7a84-40af-a6cc-22129ce9368c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-30 11:38:40</date>
      <author>www.playcola.com</author>
      <email>colette_ahern@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.129.255</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Many credit card companies to offer some perks to funeral insurance their customers. This price is based on cash funeral insurance value. If you lived in one of Llanerch Vineyard&amp;#39;s 11 chic rooms costs from &amp;#163;95pp based on two adults sharing. Many people have already been evacuated from the danger area. So how in the world.

Take a look at my page :: car warranty -  www.playcola.com - http://www.playcola.com/profile/horace0310 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="39f5e7e1-5e19-40d2-a296-92a4c9da75ee" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-04 08:53:25</date>
      <author>www.woovac.com</author>
      <email>maximilian_weinman@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.47.24.155</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In 1978 and at the time the sun set on Scapa Flow 400, 000 tons of the Imperial German Naval ensign was ordered stricken from all of the above and more. But those figures were hard to confirm as the flotilla was about to be repeated - but this is nothing compared to fleet insurance. What should you do when you get a Fleet Insurance,  www.woovac.com - http://www.woovac.com/xe/index.php?mid=free&amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;order_type=desc&amp;amp;document_srl=607612 , policy, the greater the savings to the owner.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a6256b9d-5cbe-4b3d-bb5f-3091b30de3ef" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-04-15 08:57:37</date>
      <author>BHW</author>
      <email>wiltongreer@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>114.44.211.82</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello are using Wordpress for your blog platform? I&amp;#39;m new to the blog world but I&amp;#39;m trying to get started and create my own. Do you need any html coding expertise to make your own blog? Any help would be really appreciated!</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>