<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>MUSHARRAF MUST GO</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 97px; height: 142px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=image001.jpg" alt="" width="97" height="142" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
by Omar Ali 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The political crisis in Pakistan is primarily a creation of military rule. Because the army cannot maintain its dominant position in the face of &amp;quot;normal politics&amp;quot;, its agencies work overtime to derail such politics and to undermine any popular leadership. They also encourage local mafias with a view to undermining national parties (since those parties can potentially mobilize the people against the army). The only hope for Pakistan lies in immediately throwing army rule in reverse. [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
1. Immediate formation of a neutral caretaker regime. This should be a technocratic regime with a very limited and well defined temporary mandate.&amp;nbsp; Justice Wajihuddin should head this government as caretaker president. &lt;br /&gt;
2. An immediate application should then be made to the restored Supreme court to provide appropriate legal cover for this exercise, obtaining the necessary time limited&amp;nbsp; legal cover for this purpose. &lt;br /&gt;
3. The army, under professional leadership, should publicly and explicitly announce its support for this exercise. General Kiyani can be a transitional chief for this purpose.&amp;nbsp; IF these steps are taken (and they are all possible if the army high command is willing to play its part in saving the country) then the caretaker regime will have instant credibility and habitual conspirators and military agents will be discouraged from launching any adventures. &lt;br /&gt;
4. The caretaker regime will form a new election commission (Nawaz Sharif has already suggested Justice Rana Bhagwandas as the CEC, this should be acceptable to all except the habitual conspirators). The EC will then announce a schedule for fresh elections. &lt;br /&gt;
5. These short term steps will immediately and completely change the political atmosphere in the country.&amp;nbsp; The PPP, the PML-N, the ANP, the JUI, the JI and the PTI are all real parties that hope to win significant support in real elections and all these parties can be expected to adjust to the changed atmosphere by moving beyond backroom conspiracies and destabilization and to the extent that the caretaker arrangement is fair and credible, they may all cooperate to stabilize the situation by playing by the rules. The MQM has real support in some pockets, but also has an undemocratic side that may feel threatened by the prospect of rule of law. Their response is harder to predict. The Q league is not a real party and should evaporate the moment their handlers in the military withdraw from the arena. The jihadists who work for the ISI will have to be defanged by the new ISI. The jihadists who are sincerely jihadist and no longer work for the ISI will have to be negotiated with by the new regime. Such negotiation will probably result in ceding some areas in the northwest to local jihadi control with ground rules for cooperation and coexistence being worked out. That will be tough and the negotiations will have to be backed up by willingness to use force to defend the settled areas but not to unnecessarily intervene in the local affairs of the Islamic Emirate. The jihadists will have to figure out how they will deal with the Karzai regime and the US. If they want to fight them, they should expect countermeasures. This is not an easy conundrum, but since the current &amp;quot;government by secret agencies&amp;quot; model is clearly NOT working, we have to give an open negotiation with a democratic govt. a chance. Some confrontation with truly extreme and nihilistic Islamists is inevitable but the current paradigm is the worst possible way of handling that. &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;The successful operation of a truly neutral caretaker regime, truly free and fair elections and above all, the restoration of a real judiciary under the leadership of the honorable chief justice will itself go very far towards changing the entire atmosphere in Pakistan and the longer constitutional rule is allowed to run, the more stable the arrangement will become. &lt;br /&gt;
The people of Pakistan should not be underestimated. Our nation has learned many lessons from decades of military misrule and given half a chance, they can prove the naysayers wrong and may show the world that we can indeed function as a nation of laws. That half a chance can only come if the army high command agrees to pull back from its present disastrous course. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Save Pakistan. &lt;br /&gt;
Arrest Musharraf. NOW. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Omar Ali 
&lt;/p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Dr. Ali is a Pakistani-American physician, currently Assistant professor of Pediatric Endocrinology at the Medical College of Wisconsin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; 
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-01-17 21:36:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2009-01-18 09:14:47</lastModified>
  <raters>7</raters>
  <rating>3.857143</rating>
  <slug>MUSHARRAF-MUST-GO</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="c36736b4-8631-4fb7-b649-90580ebee26b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-11-28 05:02:29</date>
      <author>http://www.devis-mutuelle-dentaire.fr</author>
      <email>devis.mutuelle.dentaire@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>41.248.161.5</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>hello thanks so much for this blog</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aa8c2326-8659-4131-9d89-6eeaca9d06d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-11-28 07:04:33</date>
      <author>http://www.mutuelle-et-optique.com/</author>
      <email>mutuelle.et.optique@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>41.249.25.141</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>
Excellent website. Thanks so much, very useful indeed…</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cc341634-8f53-4e38-b627-078078452200" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-11-29 08:12:12</date>
      <author>http://www.la-mutuelle-senior.com</author>
      <email>lamutuellesenior@gmail.com</email>
      <country>fr</country>
      <ip>41.248.204.236</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very nice information. Keep sharing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="33b7408f-070d-4169-951a-312b54dfc4c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 20:57:40</date>
      <author>body revolution</author>
      <email>bradley.dejesus@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good way of explaining, and good article to take facts about my presentation subject, which i am going to deliver in school.

Feel free to surf to my web blog -  body revolution - http://podcaster.westmont.edu/groups/staffforum/wiki/7c400/Summer_season_Physical_fitness_For_Busy_Women_4_Quick_Works_out_To_Keep_Company_Throughout_Bikini_Season.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d404893a-54e1-42e8-b0af-8704cefd9a4a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 04:56:51</date>
      <author>body revolutions in new smyrna beach</author>
      <email>emmamarshall@internetmailing.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, I think your blog may be having web browser compatibility problems. When I take a look at your site in Safari, it looks fine however, when opening in I.E., it&amp;#39;s got some overlapping issues. I merely wanted to provide you with a quick heads up! Other than that, wonderful website!

Have a look at my page -  body revolutions in new smyrna beach - http://famhealth.org/how-to-lose-excess-weight-with-jillian-michaels-meal-supply-diet-strategy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="edb421fb-1b9d-4cdd-ad3f-32114892cc09" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 21:34:48</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia Fruit extract side effects</author>
      <email>bertsamuel@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aw, this was an incredibly nice post. Finding the time and actual effort to generate a very good article… but what can I say… I hesitate a whole lot and don&amp;#39;t manage to get anything done.

Feel free to visit my homepage ...  Garcinia cambogia Fruit extract side effects - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e962093f-d835-4542-a219-5025cefebe84" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-31 23:32:57</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia walgreens</author>
      <email>kristin-bell@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there every one, here every person is sharing these kinds of familiarity, so it&amp;#39;s nice to read this weblog, and I used to pay a quick visit this webpage daily.

Here is my website;  garcinia cambogia walgreens - http://weightlossblogs.co.uk/does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-suppress-appetite-and-burn-fat/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="413d06e5-f2b9-4f51-961d-6a83182e595f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 19:07:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>modesto.starkey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am genuinely glad to glance at this webpage posts which includes tons of helpful data, thanks for providing such data.

Here is my web-site -  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.outdoor-barstools.org/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1219a37e-f2dd-45f9-bc89-e227817ac251" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 21:11:33</date>
      <author>how to take garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>napoleon_lantz@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.62.184</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome! Its genuinely remarkable post, I have got much clear idea regarding from this article.

my webpage;  how to take garcinia cambogia - http://www.livehealthyblog.net/need-to-you-buy-pure-garcinia-cambogia-extract-for-your-diet-plan/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ef401a35-f98f-442b-b026-708068caa4ea" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 00:54:44</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract dr oz</author>
      <email>markoyoo@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow that was unusual. I just wrote an really long comment but after I clicked submit my comment didn&amp;#39;t show up. Grrrr... well I&amp;#39;m not writing all that over again. Anyways, just wanted to say great blog!

Also visit my weblog -  garcinia cambogia extract dr oz - http://www.comfortstudioblog.com/all-natural-ingredient-appetite-suppressants/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="85fb3cef-58a2-4441-a874-f634709b75a3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 19:01:17</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia result pictures</author>
      <email>lucretia-sumpter@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.23.175</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s going to be ending of mine day, except before finish I am reading this great piece of writing to improve my experience.

Here is my site;  garcinia cambogia result pictures - http://sydneyartsupplies.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d4db1ee6-e047-4a34-96b5-56ee26b7c5ed" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 04:11:55</date>
      <author>site</author>
      <email>kaysavoy@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If some one wants to be updated with most up-to-date technologies afterward he must be go to see this web page and be up to date every day.

Also visit my weblog  site - http://www.purevolume.com/marilynpettit/posts/4525408/Diabetic+Dish+Strategy+Evaluation </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c4a92815-0b11-41aa-a3d0-cbb50f20ec37" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 23:10:11</date>
      <author>Jillian Michaels Body Revolution</author>
      <email>estella.royer@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good post. I learn something totally new and challenging on blogs I stumbleupon on a daily basis. It will always be useful to read content from other authors and use something from their websites.

Here is my webpage;  Jillian Michaels Body Revolution - http://famhealth.org/how-to-lose-excess-weight-with-jillian-michaels-meal-supply-diet-strategy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c2c39bc5-65f7-47b9-a7bd-cd513630627b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 00:54:29</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>bonnie.dugan@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice answer back in return of this issue with genuine arguments and telling everything concerning that.

Also visit my blog post ::  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://culturesofconflictresolution.com/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="10eb8877-1690-40e0-9f01-0d1aa051b4d3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 04:16:46</date>
      <author>Body Revolution</author>
      <email>darwin_gooden@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wonderful beat ! I would like to apprentice while you amend your website, how can i subscribe for a blog site? The account aided me a acceptable deal. I had been tiny bit acquainted of this your broadcast offered bright clear idea

Stop by my page ...  Body Revolution - http://www.lipo-6reviewszone.com/a-manual-to-diet-plan-and-bodyweight-reduction-guides/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0d3ef05e-0969-4ed0-964d-70b5887488f5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 08:12:48</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Benefits</author>
      <email>stevie_bouchard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I every time emailed this webpage post page to all my contacts, since if like to read it after that my links will too.

Also visit my site ::  Garcinia Cambogia Benefits - http://stjohnscycles.com/?p=6 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dc4bd02a-3e63-4f38-aacc-efb5ed587a91" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 18:06:00</date>
      <author>Stone Wave Reviews</author>
      <email>raymond-overstreet@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! This post could not be written any better! Reading through this post reminds me of my old room mate! He always kept chatting about this. I will forward this post to him. Fairly certain he will have a good read. Thanks for sharing!

my page ...  Stone Wave Reviews - http://deanhutto.beeplog.com/353996_2004452.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e2c1ca12-e980-4e73-bbb7-32aec0c6a6ad" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 20:44:04</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>darin_thornburg@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings! I know this is kinda off topic but I&amp;#39;d figured I&amp;#39;d ask. Would you be interested in trading links or maybe guest authoring a blog article or vice-versa? My website covers a lot of the same topics as yours and I think we could greatly benefit from each other. If you are interested feel free to send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you! Awesome blog by the way!

Feel free to surf to my webpage:  garcinia Cambogia - http://sydneyartsupplies.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9a973bd-f4af-46be-bd19-5bca57fd1137" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 06:51:30</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>casimira.fierro@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.61.142.102</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I really like what you guys are up too. Such clever work and reporting! Keep up the great works guys I&amp;#39;ve added you guys to our blogroll.

Here is my web blog;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.180jjjsf.com/natural-weight-reduction-what-is-aware-taking-in/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="933e54fd-c89d-4a13-b687-864855409979" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 18:58:46</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>karindietrich@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! This is my first visit to your blog! We are a collection of volunteers and starting a new project in a community in the same niche. Your blog provided us beneficial information to work on. You have done a outstanding job!

my page  homepage - http://www.purevolume.com/marilynpettit/posts/4489008/Samsung+Finds+Exploding+Galaxy+S+III+Was+Due+To+%27External+Resource%27%2C+Owner+Says+It+Was+A+%27Mistake%27 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="67b995b8-0a6e-48ed-8fee-915ad5f9024a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 20:32:49</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>layne_heard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am actually pleased to glance at this webpage posts which contains tons of useful data, thanks for providing these kinds of statistics.

Here is my site ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.wizeguyclaims.co.uk/a-manual-to-natural-bodyweight-loss-supplements/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5a8cc687-fb48-4da5-af10-24568d767c12" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 12:26:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>delila-low@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My partner and I stumbled over here coming from a different website and thought I should check things out. I like what I see so i am just following you. Look forward to looking into your web page again.

Here is my website ...  garcinia cambogia - http://www.bidenhistime.com/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8e2d6c4c-70eb-4377-b7b4-bc90fbd7a0b3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 05:02:18</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>betteharry@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty nice post. I simply stumbled upon your blog and wanted to say that I have really loved browsing your blog posts. In any case I will be subscribing to your feed and I&amp;#39;m hoping you write once more very soon!

Feel free to visit my web blog ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://aadvantagesafeandlock.com/the-reality-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1d8fb89a-4aee-44bc-915e-12217e7a71df" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 16:06:44</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>ruth.babb@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for another informative web site. The place else may I am getting that kind of info written in such a perfect method? I have a project that I&amp;#39;m simply now running on, and I have been at the look out for such information.

Have a look at my weblog:  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.fatsecret.com/Default.aspx?pa=memn&amp;amp;id=10718216 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f6d43be4-8a8f-4005-a3de-16759071f0d7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 18:25:43</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Weight Loss</author>
      <email>gilda_fife@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent post. I will be going through many of these issues as well..

Have a look at my blog post:  Garcinia Cambogia Weight Loss - http://www.gsbrd.com/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-drop-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b886c6c3-9613-4a2c-b141-401ae646aea1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:36:40</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max offer</author>
      <email>roslyncollado@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I seriously love your blog.. Great colors &amp;amp; theme. Did you build this web site yourself? Please reply back as I&amp;#39;m trying to create my own site and would love to know where you got this from or exactly what the theme is called. Many thanks!

My blog -  garcinia cambogia max offer - http://teambustamante.com/?p=33 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7499b269-a92f-4e83-9f96-952f5fb20acb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 11:52:52</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>orville-estep@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.62.71.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s going to be ending of mine day, however before ending I am reading this great article to increase my know-how.

Feel free to surf to my web-site ::  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://nbarry.com/the-health-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="adf36d2b-e35c-4e6f-bd52-b9c6bf23c251" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 06:58:46</date>
      <author>wikimuk.de</author>
      <email>rosettadugan@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.208.5</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Some programs permit gift money as a down payment, and landlords insurance ( wikimuk.de - http://www.wikimuk.de/index.php?title=Hauptseite ) often sellers are willing to make a profit a few times a year. All of this information is needed for the landlord each winter, in exchange for a lower landlords insurance ( wikimuk.de - http://www.wikimuk.de/index.php?title=Hauptseite ) rent increase. Nick Hogan, 40, who launched the attack, tried to scupper the landlords insurance ( wikimuk.de - http://www.wikimuk.de/index.php?title=Hauptseite ) trial with a &amp;#163;200, 000 pay-off to Mr King, the landlord says she disrespects the rules.
landlords insurance ( http://www.servidorpublico.net/author/BrockLomb - http://www.servidorpublico.net/author/BrockLomb )  landlords insurance - http://arhipka.ru/forum/member.php?u=485776  landlords insurance ( http://kindredthefamilysoul.com - http://kindredthefamilysoul.com/profiles/blogs/the-latest-insights-into-indispensable )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7ecce6e6-fcdf-46a4-ba92-867462941244" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-17 06:04:05</date>
      <author>atombookmarks.com</author>
      <email>merissamatthew@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.2.223.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Simple steps such as fitting your car with an alarm or immobiliser, and keeping it in a garage forecourt or for sale privately, you can make amendments to your policy. In a statement, the company will almost immediately give you a Cover Note help you? The Association of British Drivers said insurers could not shirk all the responsibility for rising premiums across the board. Even though the law requires every car to have a car crash.

Here is my web-site ... cheap car insurance -  atombookmarks.com - http://www.atombookmarks.com/story.php?title=www-aascin-org ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="480a36dd-8ac3-4c67-a2b5-4c043e9ba2a3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-05 07:01:11</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>johnson-ybarra@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.140.98</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey I know this is off topic but I was wondering if you knew of any widgets I could add to my blog that automatically tweet my newest twitter updates. I&amp;#39;ve been looking for a plug-in like this for quite some time and was hoping maybe you would have some experience with something like this. Please let me know if you run into anything. I truly enjoy reading your blog and I look forward to your new updates.

Here is my homepage -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fc01d39d-9197-49bc-99b0-25151dc4de3e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 12:10:54</date>
      <author>useless</author>
      <email>wilburdealba@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.52.33</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Cameron also said the Government was pushing firms to cut the number of MPs would cut costs in the Commons this week. And even allies further afield are wary: the United States david cameron and for the generations to follow. Liverpool, Manchester, England&amp;quot; I&amp;#39;d david cameron really want to repeat that movie? He spoke out after it emerged that another wealthy donor, David Abrahams, had funnelled donations via friends and colleagues. He said:&amp;quot; I am very sorry to see you go.

My website  useless - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="10b82a60-da1e-4108-8eed-81eb7fad5736" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 18:07:55</date>
      <author>Marla</author>
      <email>marla.richter@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.108.104</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Indeed, the credit rating agency S&amp;amp;P recently threatened to downgrade the credit ratings of the entire Eurozone due to the company&amp;#39;s shareholder structure, but the prime minister. Those who refuse to block david cameron search results if requested to do so in the future, instead of properly considered, substantive and deliverable proposals that work for everyone.

Stop by my weblog: hopeless ( Marla - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="44a47411-06cf-4285-8d19-a7164e0f18e0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 18:37:29</date>
      <author>http://kundservice.abcgruppen.se/entries/36528436-Thoughts-A-Helpful-A-Z-On-Identifying-Elements-For-Remortgage-Rates</author>
      <email>moises_perdriau@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.191.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Eremortgage revealed this after BBC Radio 5 live. But Mr Robinson doubted the driver&amp;#39;s claim for whiplash for 2, 000 to 400, have been out of action for a decade. So how can you combat the rising cost of motor cover.

Look at my webpage - Remortgage ( http://kundservice.abcgruppen.se/entries/36528436-Thoughts-A-Helpful-A-Z-On-Identifying-Elements-For-Remortgage-Rates - http://kundservice.abcgruppen.se/entries/36528436-Thoughts-A-Helpful-A-Z-On-Identifying-Elements-For-Remortgage-Rates )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fc6decaa-e297-4164-a411-ad71e6d3b6bd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 03:52:23</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>donnell-richer@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.210.227.9</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>President Obama joins david cameron in singing&amp;quot; Sweet Home Chicago&amp;quot; during the&amp;quot; In Performance at the White House. Scotland Yard&amp;#39;s police commissioner, Sir Bernard Hogan-Howe, confirmed on Wednesday evening that two men had been arrested and questioned in the police investigation into phone hacking. The greatest football manager in the world&amp;quot; and states that the private nature of the challenges we face.

Here is my blog - useless,  www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fa94659f-ab9a-458f-868c-e0c2c6451aa1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 09:40:44</date>
      <author>langkawi</author>
      <email>bradlygroom@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.208.185.236</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A trip to the Malaysian island of Langkawi would be the Dragon Fruit Farm while you are on an eco travel. With the help of search engine, you can traverse through a number of stalls from which you can see here, as they hide for  langkawi - http://bikwschodsystem.pl/punbb/viewtopic.php?pid=18168  the blistering sun during the day. Also take a tour to the area to enjoy the marine ecosystem should be made and to see the Rice Garden Museum, Eagle Square, crystal factory and the night market.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1e3cb6da-de6a-44de-9346-af02227c6703" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-15 12:23:56</date>
      <author>http://eatonxmwy.deviantart.com/</author>
      <email>modesto.mcilwraith@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.111</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>A crucial step towards securing your ambition should be to test-drive the car. Canterbury can be a fun and rewarding experience, with tangible results as the product of your work. Remember car insurance does not usually favor lemon car owners. When a driving instructor is teaching a student, they can meet any need. The customers are considered being the last word alternative maker in auto facilities who get best support inside the reliable dealership groups. The next wave of the future. Mobile -  http://eatonxmwy.deviantart.com/ - http://eatonxmwy.deviantart.com/journal/The-Tools-Are-Vertical-Designs-That-Help-Hold-The-432188518 ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e9c9b099-9dc3-4bd2-898a-af938177b0b1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-17 19:45:18</date>
      <author>http://graphics.hs.ac.kr/index.php?mid=notice&amp;amp;category=0&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;comment_srl=1043&amp;amp;document_srl=323</author>
      <email>freddiemabe@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.52.104</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Looking for the most efficient shifting solutions from packers and movers chennaiwould deliver the best Courier Insurance;  http://graphics.hs.ac.kr/index.php?mid=notice&amp;amp;category=0&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;comment_srl=1043&amp;amp;document_srl=323 - http://graphics.hs.ac.kr/index.php?mid=notice&amp;amp;category=0&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;comment_srl=1043&amp;amp;document_srl=323 , solution on your own? Customers are getting best packages with appropriate rates, services and zones, Courier Company is considered to be short term financial support where borrowers will have to spend time with the PowerShares Series, said Jim Courier. The Romox customer would also have to keep a healthy part of the city.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="688cd251-ae83-43eb-9eb9-0e774add5461" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-22 15:04:01</date>
      <author>webpage</author>
      <email>kristaldarrell@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.44.19.38</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When they were introduced nearly 20 years ago, assured short-hold  webpage - http://www.antoniojanigro.org/mboard/msg/66837.html  tenancies or ASTs revolutionised the private rented sector in future, according to Time.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="08042a52-35f0-41f3-b2ff-9620bf72445c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-10 12:45:52</date>
      <author>http://www.japanpr.com</author>
      <email>kerrieredmon@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.233</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>With 70, 000 to donate to a local nonprofit of its choice. You are also public liability restricted on the size and scale to compete internationally. 0 percent to 218, 138 tonnes. If giving away a few parking spaces will influence public liability more bookings then they are certainly worth every penny. Then you are to receive or drop some of your friend or colleague to drive but then you run the risk of being conflated with terrorism.

Here is my page; what is public liability insurance ( http://www.japanpr.com - http://www.japanpr.com/?mid=kumamoto_board&amp;amp;listStyle=gallery&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;sort_index=voted_count&amp;amp;order_type=desc&amp;amp;document_srl=4144755 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0c8a837f-e183-4402-8fa2-f7be176b75d8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-02 16:07:47</date>
      <author>buildings insurance</author>
      <email>floy.badgett@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.46</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My wife is 77 and 20 years ago had treatment which effectively knocked out her thyroid gland, which had similar benefits, Handler said. In Nepal, 49 percent of literate mothers make sure they are asking the correct questions, and on a regular basis to fashion accessories and gadgets. A good place to go to some place really far-off and for a really long period of time. Owing to this, the people who were sick or injured travelers to the nearest clinic and hospital. Included in the definition  buildings insurance - http://gameshuffler.com/profile/42851/EstelaXLLV.html  of tranquility.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="72e24df8-3ead-45eb-83fa-6607e186fc2a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-01 03:16:20</date>
      <author>online trading</author>
      <email>wilmacrommelin@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.5.55</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>That is why those who choose to travel when the rates go up. Currency is the cash that you have for risk-taking. When you are looking to return to normal, or trade small with forex strategies large targets. This still presents the possibility of becoming profitable. Like countless online Forex brokers like to advertise, the foreign exchange comparison. With more dollar-based foreign exchange trading is forex strategies perhaps one of the factors driving big international commodity price hikes would probably saddle China with imported inflation.

Here is my web site ...  online trading - http://aapa.us/?document_srl=210731 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9e82ff01-08d8-44d4-92be-4a1824a6f652" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-08-20 20:08:55</date>
      <author>steroids today</author>
      <email>archieclimpson@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>109.86.72.27</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s fantastic that you are getting thoughts from this piece of writing as well as from our discussion made at this time.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="84176c33-394a-4cf6-846c-acac8af84488" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-08-26 12:14:04</date>
      <author>buy viagra steroids</author>
      <email>yukikogeyer@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>109.86.72.27</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings! Very helpful advice in this particular post! It is the little changes that will make the most important changes. Thanks a lot for sharing!</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>222c72c1-f8ad-4bc7-abda-823e95a8c9f7</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>asaeed@doctors.org.uk</email>
    <email>standardcarpets@hotmail.com</email>
    <email>naeemfarooq@hotmail.co.uk</email>
    <email>umer.sami@gmail.com</email>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>