<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Mrs Bakhtiar Was Pushed</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 168px; height: 136px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=photo.jpg" alt="" width="168" height="136" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;11&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; September, 2001 was another fateful day in the history of revolution, which gave a new impetus to the emancipation and empowerment of masses. The noted humanist and social activist, Mr Armitage got in touch with the Great Leader, and conveyed to him the love and affection of the American public for the revolution and for its leaders. As a small token of this affection, he offered that the country could be bombed back to the Stone Age. The Great Leader, General Tinpot said (at the risk of sounding ungrateful), that actually the country was already there. He showed him a large collection of stones, which had been thrown at him by the masses, in delirious adulation. Mr. Armitage was convinced that this would be a most beneficial action, as the only gift of Pakistan to the human civilisation were lower Palaeolithic flint tools from the Soan Valley, before Imran Khan invented the reverse swing (with the help of Coca Cola bottle tops, he added: An American contribution).&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;It seemed obvious to the revolutionary council that a reorientation of the national policy was desirable; the question was to what degree. The nice round figure of 180 degrees was thought appropriate. Unfortunately many of the field operatives, who had worked in the Afghan Jihad, had to be retired. This was promptly achieved with a bullet in the back of the head. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;A change of direction in the cultural policy was a bigger challenge. It was decided that the naatia musahairas, mashaikh conferences, and tablighi ijtimas had served their purpose. Instead, it was desirable that fashion shows, rock concerts and sports activities should be promoted. Mr Armitage assured General Tinpot that America and God were firmly on the side of the revolution, and he could speak on the behalf of both. The Great Leader wistfully mentioned that this was evocative of Mr. Brzezenski&amp;rsquo;s statement on the eve of Afghan Jihad, for which a million Afghan martyrs gave their blood, although the cultural emphasis of&amp;nbsp; those times was decidedly different. He agreed that the purpose was the same, i.e. empowerment of masses and spread of democracy.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;A special ministry was created in the revolutionary government, to promote the softer image of Pakistan, under the learned and enlightened leadership of Mrs. Parachute Bakhtiar, also known for her love of endurance sports. It was called the Ministry of Truth. Because of her sweet nature, and empathy, she was also entrusted with looking after the victims of rape. She carried out this duty with true professionalism and diligence. She looked after their travel documents, press statements, exit control lists and housing arrangements, sometimes having to protect them against undesirable media attention and shady foreigners. Her spectacular fall therefore came as a complete surprise. There is a raging debate among the contemporary historians, about the cause of this fall. Some say that she jumped herself, off an aircraft. The emerging consensus, though, seems to be that she was pushed. However her ministry achieved its aim. Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s soft image is now known to be soft as pulp. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-01-25 17:59:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:54:56</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Mrs-Bakhtiar-Was-Pushed</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="87f64cab-7ba5-42da-81ec-f31ddc6f662c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-20 19:25:01</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>luann_neff@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This post will assist the internet visitors for creating new weblog or even a weblog from start to end.

Look into my web blog ::  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.outdoor-barstools.org/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7fbc308d-f561-4e83-bf98-8518d9fda1a2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-20 23:39:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>neil_haggard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.131.206</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>For newest information you have to visit world wide web and on world-wide-web I found this website as a finest web page for most up-to-date updates.

Have a look at my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7b966986-b2f5-444f-8ac4-a1e62badf3a5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 00:46:12</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>renlennon@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.58.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I must thank you for the efforts you&amp;#39;ve put in writing this site. I&amp;#39;m hoping to view the same high-grade content from you in the future as well. In fact, your creative writing abilities has inspired me to get my own, personal blog now ;)

my web page ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f9f78a06-af9c-4526-9a21-04c43f54c1d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 14:56:55</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews amazon</author>
      <email>bryanchatman@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.128.11</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi to every body, it&amp;#39;s my first pay a quick visit of this website; this weblog consists of remarkable and really good stuff in support of readers.

my blog ...  garcinia cambogia reviews amazon - http://td-snow.com/the-truth-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1da105a6-5713-4d12-9912-c89597549ab8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 18:22:44</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>everettself@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya i am for the first time here. I came across this board and I find It truly useful &amp;amp; it helped me out a lot. I hope to give something back and help others like you helped me.

Review my web-site:  garcinia Cambogia extract - http://www.eads-na-security.com/2013/07/which-weight-loss-supplements-can-i-use-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="34a2d698-189f-4377-b029-611f115f7f6b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 08:13:54</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>kurtis_montemayor@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Can I simply just say what a relief to uncover someone that truly knows what they&amp;#39;re talking about on the net. You certainly realize how to bring an issue to light and make it important. A lot more people have to check this out and understand this side of your story. I can&amp;#39;t believe you are not more popular given that you definitely possess the gift.

my web-site;  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.new-youth.com/best-places-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9e017513-244b-429d-9663-4b7f0fc94082" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 02:33:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>luciana.dowell@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there terrific website! Does running a blog like this require a massive amount work? I have absolutely no understanding of coding however I was hoping to start my own blog soon. Anyway, if you have any ideas or tips for new blog owners please share. I know this is off topic but I simply wanted to ask. Kudos!

Also visit my page -  garcinia cambogia hca - http://soratrasancargo.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-fit/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6e6671f7-d844-477b-a0c8-721df818eacc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 04:02:29</date>
      <author>instructions for lichi superfruit and garcinia cambogia cleanse diet</author>
      <email>hayleyreeder@wildmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up this is kinda of off topic but I was wondering if blogs use WYSIWYG editors or if you have to manually code with HTML. I&amp;#39;m starting a blog soon but have no coding know-how so I wanted to get advice from someone with experience. Any help would be greatly appreciated!

Here is my page;  instructions for lichi superfruit and garcinia cambogia cleanse diet - http://vdesignstudio.ca/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8954e110-7fe9-47ad-b010-fb41d400f0a7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 04:04:40</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>carl.blanchard@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for sharing your thoughts. I truly appreciate your efforts and I am waiting for your further write ups thank you once again.

my homepage;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://tzhs163.com/?p=57 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b0d79d3d-6aa7-4f65-84f5-ebe3c6f096d1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 13:24:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>gabriele-carey@fastmail.cn</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m amazed, I must say. Rarely do I come across a blog that&amp;#39;s both equally educative and amusing, and let me tell you, you have hit the nail on the head. The issue is something which too few people are speaking intelligently about. I am very happy I came across this in my search for something concerning this.

Feel free to surf to my website:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://watchstorelive.com/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="32ddf060-9559-4d0e-80e1-a65a5e55b632" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 18:19:25</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia before and Afterresults</author>
      <email>patriciaeastman@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Normally I do not read post on blogs, however I would like to say that this write-up very pressured me to try and do so! Your writing style has been amazed me. Thank you, quite nice article.

My web site -  garcinia cambogia before and Afterresults - http://promotionscoach.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ddd9e525-5f8d-4218-b5fb-3426e6c4c715" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 20:32:12</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>zacherymahaffey@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have read so many posts regarding the blogger lovers but this piece of writing is in fact a pleasant piece of writing, keep it up.

My site  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.betterbuildingchallenge.net/all-natural-excess-weight-management-vs-conventional-excess-weight-loss-support/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="024c35d5-e78d-43d5-bf7d-3cc0bea89be7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-18 06:07:14</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia dr oz video</author>
      <email>marcelobabb@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Asking questions are really fastidious thing if you are not understanding something entirely, however this paragraph presents fastidious understanding even.

Feel free to surf to my web blog ...  garcinia cambogia dr oz video - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ad029851-61f5-46b2-8c48-c7c92a6eb5df" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 10:33:17</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>franklynhendrickson@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings from Florida! I&amp;#39;m bored to tears at work so I decided to check out your website on my iphone during lunch break. I enjoy the knowledge you present here and can&amp;#39;t wait to take a look when I get home. I&amp;#39;m surprised at how fast your blog loaded on my mobile .. I&amp;#39;m not even using WIFI, just 3G .. Anyhow, very good blog!

my page  garcinia cambogia - http://www.hauucsb.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="838d6b32-5985-47ed-ae80-79bc3f9167a6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:05:38</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>leonardrome@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks a bunch for sharing this with all of us you actually recognise what you are speaking approximately! Bookmarked. Kindly also consult with my web site =). We can have a link exchange arrangement between us

Look at my web site;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.buildingfamilies411.com/?p=31 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0c9cb8da-f1a8-48e9-b3ae-d34553a38d74" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 13:10:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>jesuschavis@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.220.246</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks for the marvelous posting! I really enjoyed reading it, you will be a great author. I will always bookmark your blog and will come back later in life. I want to encourage  continue your great posts, have a nice holiday weekend!

my web-site:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://nzsnowsports.com/?p=76 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d0ba3f5b-c4df-4d61-85f7-cddd940d1e25" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 14:48:37</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>robinlarsen@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.112</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>For hottest news you have to pay a visit the web and on the web I found this website as a most excellent site for most recent updates.

Visit my weblog  garcinia cambogia hca - http://matildas.net/normal-fat-decline-will-perform-for-you/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="64c9bef5-eaa1-400f-98cc-495119d0eca1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 08:36:00</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia 1500mg</author>
      <email>kelly.tyree@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Quality content is the key to invite the visitors to visit the web site, that&amp;#39;s what this site is providing.

Also visit my site:  pure garcinia cambogia 1500mg - http://brandjewelleryshop.co.uk/the-wellness-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="66c826f1-9916-4766-8cdd-753bb9c8f2a2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 07:42:43</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>jewell.worthington@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome! Its actually awesome article, I have got much clear idea on the topic of from this piece of writing.

Here is my homepage:  garcinia cambogia - http://nanohex.eu/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b0f27045-cdb9-4083-9e5b-91b04d007296" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 10:50:38</date>
      <author>Pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>isidromclemore@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.138</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My family members every time say that I am killing my time here at net, but I know I am getting experience everyday by reading thes nice content.

My blog -  Pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://yourdailydiet.info/fitness/what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="444f3f5b-af83-4a82-953a-ddf706aa5b3a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 04:29:08</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>rosalindflynn@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.7</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Simply desire to say your article is as surprising. The clarity in your post is simply cool and i can assume you&amp;#39;re an expert on this subject. Fine with your permission let me to grab your feed to keep updated with forthcoming post. Thanks a million and please continue the enjoyable work.

my webpage  pure garcinia cambogia - http://allthingsbonsai.net/diet-patch-that-works.html/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="47185d12-4559-44e6-bcd6-c4257d9a21ff" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-05 08:23:39</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews</author>
      <email>annabellevanover@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.204</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy would you mind letting me know which web host you&amp;#39;re utilizing? I&amp;#39;ve loaded your blog in 3 different web browsers and I must say this blog loads a lot faster then most. Can you recommend a good internet hosting provider at a honest price? Kudos, I appreciate it!

Have a look at my website ...  garcinia cambogia reviews - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>uzmas2k@yahoo.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>