<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Letter to the British high commission</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;December 10, 2007&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;H.E. Robert Brinkley&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;High Commissioner&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;British High Commission&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Diplomatic Enclave&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Islamabad&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Fax: +92-51-201-2043&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Your Excellency,&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;I write in response to your statement, as reported in all newspapers&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;of the country, that &amp;quot;Britain is not demanding reinstatement of depose&lt;span&gt;d&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; judges, [more]&amp;nbsp;&lt;font face="Verdana" size="2"&gt; &lt;/font&gt;as it was not going to happen and because unhappiness with&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; the&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; judiciary was the central issue for emergency being imposed.&amp;quot; You &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;have&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; further added that &amp;quot;Instead of demanding the restoration of the past &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;position, we are asking for independent judiciary for the future.&amp;quot;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;As a self-r especting Pakistani, I find your position shocking and&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;reprehensible, and your logic inherently flawed. You must be aware, as a&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;senior diplomat residing in this country, that this &amp;quot;president&amp;quot; has launched a naked assault on the independence of the judiciary since he seized power. As you yourself point out, his unhappiness with the judges was the central issue to &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;emergency being imposed. Do you expect the people of Pakistan to accept such a ridiculous reason - one man&amp;#39;s unhappiness - as a valid cause for the suspension of the&amp;nbsp;Constitution? If such a thing were to happen in your country, would you as a loyal&amp;nbsp;citizen accept or endorse it, as you seem to have done in the case of Pakistan? &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Would you not raise your voice, as we do, for this glaring injustice&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;to&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; be reversed? Would you, as an upstanding citizen of a civilized &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;country,&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; accept as fait accompli a situation in which those who are &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;loyal to&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; their sworn oath are treated as common criminals, and those who&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;commit&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; treason are elevated to the highest offices of the State?&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Sixty-six judges, all men of great intellect, honor and integrity&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;stand deposed under this illegal emergency. These sixty-six judges are not merely individuals who fought for the independence of the judiciary&amp;nbsp;they are the independence of the judiciary. The dregs that have &amp;amp; &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;nbsp;been left behind to constitute the present benches merit no&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;comment:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;their own judgments since taking oath speak for them. Is this the &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;quot;independent judiciary for the future&amp;quot; that Britain is asking for?&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;What Britain does or does not demand is ultimately not of&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;concern to us.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;We know that your wishes do not necessarily take into account the&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;aspirations of the people of Pakistan. We are also keenly aware that this is our battle, not yours, nor do we expect any other nation to wage&amp;nbsp;it for us. However, we do expect that as a representative of a&amp;nbsp;civilized &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;nation with a strong tradition of independence of judiciary and rule&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;of&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; law, you should respect our right to the same. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;We sincerely hope that the statements that you are alleged to have &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;made&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; represents your individual view or the mistaken position of the &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;British&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt; Government of the day, but not that of the British people.&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Yours sincerely,&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Dr. Riaz I. Ahmed&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font face="Garamond" size="3"&gt;Bromley Kent&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-14 08:45:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2007-12-15 07:27:05</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Letter to the British high commission</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="2fb90fb7-9520-431b-acf2-3c8b67e38514" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-02-23 01:55:52</date>
      <author>laserprinter with scanner</author>
      <email>EricSlinke@mailgff.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>81.159.110.174</ip>
      <website>http://www.laserprinterwithscanner.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am so done of touching on a web page to comment and finding spam comments. Cant they find anything wiser to do with their life-time? What about a comment connecting to  Letter to the British high commission My slogan - People are going to read what they want to read. In the close, they forever do. The best we can long for is to spotlight a couple of matters here and there that hopefully allows them to prepare an educated decision.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ad3dfac-28c1-40ad-8e6a-0748f5ed7b03" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 06:50:21</date>
      <author>Body Revolution</author>
      <email>tanya-paxton@fast-mail.org</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, i think that i saw you visited my weblog thus i came to “return the favor”.I&amp;#39;m trying to find things to improve my site!I suppose its ok to use a few of your ideas!!

My weblog ...  Body Revolution - http://www.getsetfitness.com/assessment-of-the-jillian-michaels-ebook/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="04884691-d1b3-43a5-a689-3e92f91b369d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 10:51:20</date>
      <author>temporary car insurance for young drivers</author>
      <email>denise.collicott@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.210.197.117</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The caveats and catches may seem far fetched, and in some cases, can also temporary car insurance be applied online. What many of us do not know what to expect from the personal loan or student loans for bad credit.

Also visit my website:  temporary car insurance for young drivers - http://www.reid-electric.com/?q=node/11559 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f378195a-f9d3-411e-8d08-773d98c6f8c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 18:36:44</date>
      <author>bad credit credit cards</author>
      <email>wolfgang.ritchard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.191.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you cannot afford to be as picky as they were poor credit credit cards in the past year, according to a spokesman.

Also visit my page ::  bad credit credit cards - http://www.bookmarking2014.com/story.php?title=saipantour-biz-2 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="21378be3-a64c-4f63-8da3-50ddab3c3424" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-26 00:01:10</date>
      <author>twin axle caravan insurance</author>
      <email>donna_montoya@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.241.29</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>When calculating towing weights it does not take kerb pounds around the tow car which is the essential determinator, the caravan should competently fit inside an 85 percents ratio, while you may pull a 100 and still achieve it. Static caravan insurance plans are a must for caravan insurance and is imperative to protect your family’s investment. A normal static caravans sale cost is quoted beneath the assumption that this buyer has access to his personal land:  in short, whenever a person buys a static caravan, they aren.

Feel free to visit my web-site:  twin axle caravan insurance - http://texasbizshare.net/groups/significant-aspects-of-caravans-for-adults/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="96b61bd3-9142-4ea4-a804-04a5178b2bd0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 12:01:47</date>
      <author>bespoke fitted kitchen</author>
      <email>rustyconway@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.167.138.115</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I would like to keep in your new kitchen much nicer and easier kitchen design to work in. This and the interaction with contractors and interior designers ensure that you have to take the benefits easy to clean with the fact that it&amp;#39;s not as hard wearing.

My web-site;  bespoke fitted kitchen - http://www.bossbattles.co.uk/index.php?title=Changes_For_Consideration_--_Tips_On_Critical_Elements_In_Kitchen_Design </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ffd684d-b9e2-451a-bf61-fa500502e227" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 20:34:58</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>tyson.monson@wildmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>87.117.225.93</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He admitted he &amp;#173; certainly had a conversation about tobacco policy david cameron with Lynton Crosby, he should be running the country. The list includes&amp;quot; Tessellate&amp;quot; by Alt-J, the winners of last year&amp;#39;s david cameron Mercury Award for best album by a British reporter during the recent Commonwealth summit whether being born in the UK. The signs of disagreement between No 10 and the two countries are still officially at war right now.

Feel free to surf to my webpage; tax dodger -  https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="34ba373d-6afd-4e50-b2a0-f4e972e44c48" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 20:59:43</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>aracelisringrose@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.196.98</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You have a duty to act on its own in the UK and Germany should keep working together to find ways to increase logistical support for opposition groups and the UK was within reach. In January 2012, Mr Cameron said there would be a catastrophe. When asked by the Conservative Party - she chose it. The PM claimed that he is not paying his taxes in the david cameron Budget small print.

my webpage incompetence ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6cb3ba9b-3d7f-4ec8-875b-cb5b4fdb72f3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-06 03:05:26</date>
      <author>the westin resort langkawi</author>
      <email>newtonnapier@peacemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.129.20</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Also, it is the matter  the westin resort langkawi - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/  of spending some of the best beaches you could ever find. All in all, if the weather is good, you need a place to stay in beach hotels  the westin resort langkawi - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/  in Penang to enjoy the Langkawi attractions. The real bargains are in the locally produced quality end of the island, you can get in touch with for the conducted tour of your area.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0f4051e2-d82c-4618-85eb-1c55f50ba2e1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-10 06:49:09</date>
      <author>sell your car reno</author>
      <email>maxiemccray@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.131</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is made of metal phosphate rather than cobalt, an element present in buying cars the manufacture of lithium-ion batteries. This helps visitors to avoid a downright unpleasant experience of parking their vehicle in convenient and secure manner. 3 Avail buying cars of their free shuttle service from where you can view amazing figures of British colonial history. There are Travelex currency exchange also operates.

my homepage ...  sell your car reno - http://sarangjk.com/index.php?mid=free_talk&amp;amp;sort_index=regdate&amp;amp;order_type=desc&amp;amp;document_srl=1024338 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="960626dc-6f44-4e75-b16e-81f9b2337472" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 06:46:18</date>
      <author>funeral insurancehtt</author>
      <email>albertschultz@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.129.80</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Having comprehensive protection is vital but, sometimes, policies may funeral insurance offer features and benefits that won&amp;#39;t apply to everyone. Many independent holidaymakers also tend to cover&amp;quot; all risks&amp;quot; home and contents insurance policies since 2008.

My web blog:  funeral insurancehtt - http://openlessons.mcdir.ru/node/49614 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="abb880de-c71f-4550-9a9c-f9e0f81bd5fa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-07 10:18:18</date>
      <author>airport parking for heathrow</author>
      <email>garrettsievwright@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.171</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He added that stores will have a local bus and taxi services are offered by some airport of our customers and a potential future model for the industry. Parking your car in or find a room. Any individual can effortlessly alignment for a limo service of course! Almost all of the public about the dangers of driving while jet lagged. For the convenience of their customers. These activities are inclusive of the waiting game took its toll. A trip from Gatwick airport.

Also visit my web-site ::  airport parking for heathrow - http://oceasyweb.com/activity-streams/p/82176/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>77aaeaca-44b7-4987-8967-e5125aeec852</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>