<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Gold and the Steel</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 280px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=boyh_nyt.jpg" alt="" width="280" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;By &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steelman; &lt;/strong&gt;Dear Brother, let me put a mark on your forehead, with the ashes of the NAB, to ward off the evil eye. Fortune has favoured you. You have seen the coronation of Bilawal, won the elections, seen off the challenge by the pretender Amin Fahim and Judge Dogar is hoovering up the remaining cases. Every reason to be pleased Brother. [more]&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goldman: &lt;/strong&gt;You have not done badly either, Brother. You have eventually returned from the exile. Clocked up enough air miles, in the process, to travel de luxe on several airlines. You have annihilated the Q League and mopped the floor with the Chaudhries. You are still alive and your syntax has improved.&amp;nbsp; No mean achievement Brother, I have to say. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steelman: &lt;/strong&gt;I am sorry to bring it up Brother, not that I want to be prying, but what are we going to do about Judge Chaudhry? &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goldman: &lt;/strong&gt;He came to offer condolences for the soul of BB Sahiba. I dived behind the sofa, because Naek Sahib has told me to keep a low profile. He said it was not necessary. He had a steely glint in the eye Brother. I was unable to tell whether it was meant for me or Sherry Rehman, but it makes me very uneasy indeed. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Naek Sahib says to keep the BMW in the garage, not to keep any bank accounts and to keep all my savings in a sock. That is what I have been trying to do. It makes an awful big bulge Brother. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steelman:&lt;/strong&gt; I would not worry too much about that. He may have the steely glint, but you will have the IG Islamabad, that will make all the difference at the end of the day. I think we should be more concerned about Tinman. He still has his finger on the Big Button. If he doses off and presses it even by mistake, we will all be history Brother. It would be much better to bring in Judge Chaudhry and let him square off with Tinman&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goldman:&lt;/strong&gt; I am pleased to inform you that I have seen to that issue. The wires to the Button are cut. I had confirmation from the GHQ, and from International Community. Our International Friends have fixed the Button, so that if it is pressed, there will be an awful racket, but no actual damage. Give it some time Brother, Tinman will wither on the vine. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tinman:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Chants in front of the Big Button with incense burning)&lt;/em&gt; Fiftyeight twobium, addendum octagonium, negro pontonium, anne pattersonium, kayanium golium, om shanti, shanti, shanti. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;See also: &lt;a href="/post/2008/03/Chaudhry-Negroponte.aspx"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #cc6714; text-decoration: none; text-underline: none"&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman" size="3"&gt;Chaudhry Negroponte&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span style="font-size: 12pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman'"&gt;&lt;a href="/post/2008/03/Quaid-e-Tehrik-Pizza-Shop.aspx"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #cc6714; text-decoration: none; text-underline: none"&gt;Quaid-e-Tehrik Pizza Shop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-04-04 18:14:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:57:45</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>4</rating>
  <slug>The-Gold-and-the-Steel</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="c3fa9bd8-ed2f-4532-a9d8-f445f87d6d10" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-11 06:05:27</date>
      <author>helmets</author>
      <email>AndySelby@mailhcc.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>81.159.108.63</ip>
      <website>http://www.helmetsmotorcycle.net/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>First, solid article in  The Gold and the Steel, just drifting through umteen sites, appears to be a really capable writing style you are utilising. A post a day keeps the remarks flowing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a30f7b52-0cf4-4387-be6d-9922eb3df2e5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-04-01 20:58:26</date>
      <author>heidi</author>
      <email>lxtdwxpwj@163.com</email>
      <country>cn</country>
      <ip>36.249.165.12</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>With the fall and winter off-road season upon us, those who work during the daylight hours will have to turn to riding their local singletrack at night to get in adequate training time.
Here are some lighting tips that will allow you to get the most out of your time spent on the trails at night.
Primary and Backup Lighting on the Trail
Your primary [b][url=http://www.chinacarbonbicycle.com/5-color-light-for-car-bike-motorbicycle-led-wheel-light.html] light[/url] (usually mounted on the bars) needs to be powerful enough to light up the trail in front of you and give you the ability to ride almost as fast as during daylight.
The most popular backup [b][url=http://www.chinacarbonbicycle.com/bike-bicycle-car-motorcycle-led-flash-spoke-wheel-light.html] light[/url] seems to be the helmet light. If using both lights together, the terrain in front of the bike should be illuminated properly by the bar [b][url=http://www.chinacarbonbicycle.com/aluminum-alloy-bike-motorcycle-handlerbar-led-light3.html] lights[/url] in order to respond to any obstacles, while the helmet light gives light wherever you&amp;#39;re looking.
The two-light system really complements each for varying riding conditions such as a helmet light for tight singletrack and a bar light for fire roads.
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="df35c066-f4eb-453e-aa1b-8ed83fa81852" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-04-01 21:00:58</date>
      <author>heidi</author>
      <email>lxtdwxpwj@163.com</email>
      <country>cn</country>
      <ip>36.249.165.12</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>By keeping your handlebar-mounted headlight just loose enough, you can rotate it forward or back to concentrate the beam the right distance. The helmethttp://www.chinacarbonbicycle.com/5-color-light-for-car-bike-motorbicycle-led-wheel-light.html] flashlightworks well with the handlebar light if the beams are stacked one on top of each other (like two snowballs on a snowman).</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5e2ef2e9-cd7b-4241-99f9-abfc3621e740" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-19 06:20:41</date>
      <author>Alfredo</author>
      <email>alfredoschott@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>31.13.144.52</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Top internet web site Brier

My weblog - vegan Trader Joe&amp;#39;s ( Alfredo - http://forum.gl-netz.de/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;amp;u=176841 )</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>