<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>GPO 150</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;h1 style="background: white; margin: 3.75pt 0cm; line-height: 19.2pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2009%2f3%2fstones.jpg" alt="" width="450" height="295" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h1 style="background: white; margin: 3.75pt 0cm; line-height: 19.2pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Pakistan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; eyewitness report: GPO 150 and the spirit of March 15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By Ammar Ali Jan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Lahore&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; We all are ecstatic about what happened in Lahore on the March 15, 2009. This day will be remembered as one where the power of State seemed helpless in front of the power of the street. [more]&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;The most crucial moment during the day was the battle at the GPO chowk that galvanized the entire city into action. The scene of almost 150 people battling a repressive police and forcing it to retreat will remain in the collective memory of our nation for a very long time to come. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I happened to be part of that &amp;quot;GPO 150&amp;quot; when the police started using tear-gas. Here is a short description of how we managed to reach the spot and how we were able to inflict defeat on the State apparatus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="background: white; margin: auto 0cm; line-height: 19.2pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Beating the checkpoints&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;We had left Zaman park where Aitzaz had been placed under house arrest. Lahore had the look of a deserted ghost town in the morning with the Mall road completely blocked. I was with the Labour Party Pakistan, Student Action Committee and civil society members. We decided to walk our way towards the High Court in pairs so that the police would fail to notice us. Some of us succeeded while others, like Nauman Qaiser and Jalees Hazir, were arrested at the checkpoints. We saw civil society activists Feryal Gauhar and Hina Jilani once we reached the GPO chowk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;quot;As the police started shelling tear-gas indiscriminately, many activists started falling unconscious. All of us panicked and started fleeing the scene to evade arrests. A man who must be in his 70s, started yelling to the fleeing crowd (which included me, as I could no longer breathe) that this was not a time to run but to fight. Eventually, the &lt;em&gt;baba ji&lt;/em&gt; fainted as well but he encouraged all of us to come back and continue the fight.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I have been to many protests in the past but I have never seen anything like the passion visible in front of the High Court. There was a consensus that if the Lahore High Court falls, the movement will fizzle out. Everyone knew that the police would use the most brutal measures to suppress the will of the people and were mentally prepared for an epic battle.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;As the police started shelling tear-gas indiscriminately, many activists started falling unconscious. All of us panicked and started fleeing the scene to evade arrests. A man who must be in his 70s, started yelling to the fleeing crowd (which included me, as I could no longer breathe) that this was not a time to run but to fight. Eventually, the &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;baba ji&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; fainted as well but he encouraged all of us to come back and continue the fight.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="background: white; margin: auto 0cm; line-height: 19.2pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Two-hour battle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;We resisted the police for over two hours, pushing them back many a times. &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;Express News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; reported that 250 to 300 shells had been fired at the protestors. Express news reporter Rabia Mehmood and AAG channel correspondent Mani almost fainted and had to be taken away from the scene. Many were vomiting because of chemicals in the tear-gas which were worse than anything I have witnessed. However, this brought the best out of the Pakistani nation. Some people were carrying salt and water for those getting injured in the fighting. Others were helping carrying people to the diagnostic center in the High Court or on to Edhi ambulances. I was about to faint a couple of times and was almost blinded by the gas before some random people gave me enough water and salt.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;My friend Murtaza Khwaja (who was taking part in a violent protest for the first time) showed immense courage and we stayed on the front line throughout this epic battle. The protestors were also fighting with a spontaneous strategy that proved to be very effective. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;We had split in three groups. One on the Mall road, one towards the left of the GPO while one group stayed inside the High Court building. When the police would charge protestors on one side, they would be pelted by stones from the other side. This was the key to this street battle as the police was being hit by stones from three sides which is why they could not takeover the High Court. It didn&amp;#39;t matter which political party or group one belonged to. Everyone was looking out for each other and we all wanted to win.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By this time, a lot of lawyers, political activists and civil society members had gathered at the gates and those of us who had been there since almost 12pm decided to leave as we felt dehydrated and could not breathe properly. When we went in the courtyard where all the activists had gathered (including Justice Tariq Mehmood, Advocate Anwar Kamal, Hina Jila, Tehmina Daultana etc), we had no idea what this battle at the GPO really meant. We were just looking for water and a place to sit. In fact, I was a little disappointed that the numbers in front of the GPO had not been big and that the Long March could be a failure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;It is here that we received the news that this battle had gripped the entire country&amp;#39;s imagination. The news channels were constantly talking about the police high-handedness and the resistance by many activists. I even received a call from a friend in Karachi who said that he had read about the crazy fighting at the Lahore High Court. The tide was definitely turning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="background: white; margin: auto 0cm; line-height: 19.2pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;People control the city&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;After this, the people were in complete control of the city. Thousands joined Nawaz Sharif&amp;#39;s caravan as he defied detention orders to lead the procession from his house in Model Town. The High Court courtyard went ecstatic when we heard the news of the resignations of the IG,DIG, SP, DCO and deputy attorney general of pakistan. Crowds cheered wildly as some of these gentlemen joined us at the High Court. The most memorable part of the evening for me was when Aitzaz Ahsan defiantly entered the High Court building despite orders for his house arrest and the police officers stood in line to salute him. This meant a complete victory for the movement and from their onwards, it was just a matter of time before the government would be forced to accept our demands.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I feel that the way Taseer&amp;#39;s goons were defeated at the GPO showed the weakness of this state apparatus. It represented the best of pakistan. On one side, it represented despair, state brutality and police repression. On the other, it reflected hope, resistance, the passions and the dreams of many Pakistanis. We had won not because of the generosity of the country&amp;#39;s leadership, but because of the countless sacrifices of lawyers and activists for the past 2 years with 15th march 2009 becoming the grand finale in Lahore.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Here, I want to thank those comrades who stood their ground at the GPO chowk and showed Pakistan why should we be fighting this system. I will remember their support and courage for the rest of my life. This is the courage, confidence and spirit of sacrifice that we need if we want to continue our fight against the capitalist system. This has given us new confidence in our own ability to fight and in the revolutionary potential of our nation. Despite this success, our post-colonial state is still full of problems and oppression and there will inevitably be more resistance. In all of the future struggles, we shall remember and take with us the spirit of March 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2009%2f3%2fammar.jpg" alt="" width="180" height="226" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Ammar Ali Jan, Youth Secretary of the Labour Party Pakistan Lahore (LPP), will be one of several international at the the World at a Crossroads conference in Sydney, Australia, April 10-12. For more information, or to book tickets, visit &lt;a href="http://www.worldatacrossroads.org/"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext"&gt;http://www.worldatacrossroads.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0cm"&gt;
	&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="background: white; margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt; line-height: 19.2pt; tab-stops: list 36.0pt"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.asia-pacific-action.org/taxonomy/term/5"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext"&gt;Pakistan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.asia-pacific-action.org/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.asia-pacific-action.org/"&gt;&lt;span style="color: windowtext"&gt;Action in Solidarity with Asia and the Pacific &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;(ASAP), formerly ASIET (Action in Solidarity with Indonesia and East Timor), is a network of solidarity activists campaigning for democratic rights, self-determination and other justice struggles in the Asia Pacific region.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 9pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;ASAP&amp;#39;s People&amp;#39;s Power Fighting Fund runs appeals for material support for various democratic struggles in the region. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;To donate to this fund and to help maintain this website, you can deposit directly into the Commonwealth Bank Australia BSB 062026 Account number 1006 0743. Thank-you. Your help is appreciated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2009-03-17 09:11:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2009-03-17 09:38:34</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>GPO-150</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="dbe0404b-820a-402d-9f78-28089fc4fe96" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 20:49:51</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>felipahancock@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.23.175</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My relatives every time say that I am killing my time here at net, but I know I am getting experience daily by reading such nice articles.

my web-site -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="265fa532-068e-4d23-ab20-94e9108cfdb3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-24 00:30:09</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia Benefits</author>
      <email>sammykirkpatrick@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent beat ! I would like to apprentice while you amend your site, how could i subscribe for a blog site? The account aided me a acceptable deal. I had been a little bit acquainted of this your broadcast offered bright clear concept

Also visit my web-site  garcinia cambogia Benefits - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1f911d1-9615-480a-b62b-9bc8438a5c5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 00:53:05</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>abbieholt@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings I am so glad I found your website, I really found you by mistake, while I was looking on Yahoo for something else, Anyways I am here now and would just like to say cheers for a fantastic post and a all round exciting blog (I also love the theme/design), I don&amp;#39;t have time to read through it all at the minute but I have bookmarked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read much more, Please do keep up the great work.

Here is my web-site -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.tera4gold.net/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="33bb6db2-8f81-4e09-9727-9bea5ce4256b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 12:04:22</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>lucasierra@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very nice article, just what I wanted to find.

Also visit my weblog -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe2aec3f-a318-493e-98b9-67a99cf8649c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 22:48:02</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>reginald.coronado@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.62.184</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like the valuable information you provide in your articles. I will bookmark your blog and check again here regularly. I&amp;#39;m quite certain I&amp;#39;ll learn many new stuff right here! Best of luck for the next!

Feel free to surf to my homepage ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.carolsforest.com/news/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="81c509ad-6583-433d-bf71-185892ac4dc8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-04 17:11:01</date>
      <author>jillian michaels body revolution 90 day</author>
      <email>haleylarkin@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s a shame you don&amp;#39;t have a donate button! I&amp;#39;d certainly donate to this superb blog! I suppose for now i&amp;#39;ll settle for bookmarking and adding your RSS feed to my Google account. I look forward to fresh updates and will talk about this blog with my Facebook group. Talk soon!

Here is my blog ...  jillian michaels body revolution 90 day - https://blog.uinta6.k12.wy.us/groups/lisipads/wiki/e0592/Dancing_Your_Way_To_Fat_loss.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17814f7c-3cd5-4bb9-944e-7a1f6603521f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 08:07:40</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>antonia.merrell@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I loved as much as you&amp;#39;ll receive carried out right here. The sketch is tasteful, your authored material stylish. nonetheless, you command get bought an nervousness over that you wish be delivering the following. unwell unquestionably come further formerly again since exactly the same nearly a lot often inside case you shield this hike.

Look at my blog post ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://africancommunityhealthinitiatives.net/?p=8 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f82110e2-21f8-454c-afb8-3881c7e335c2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 15:11:08</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>michellegoble@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.171.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I do trust all of the ideas you have introduced on your post. They are very convincing and will definitely work. Nonetheless, the posts are too brief for beginners. May just you please lengthen them a little from subsequent time? Thanks for the post.

Look into my page:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://delhicityguide.net/perks-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e496da85-466d-44bf-8c62-d261c77f8b63" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 00:34:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>irmasamuel@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am truly happy to read this web site posts which carries plenty of helpful facts, thanks for providing these kinds of statistics.

Review my webpage:  garcinia cambogia - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bf3c0c25-5121-475f-a7a0-1bcddac03892" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 03:25:34</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>jamespeoples@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow! At last I got a blog from where I can truly get valuable information concerning my study and knowledge.

My blog  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.greekommend.com/diet-patch-that-functions/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="10d17907-110a-4067-91c7-baeaff1a5104" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 23:02:01</date>
      <author>Stone Wave Reviews</author>
      <email>brett_kitchens@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I enjoy, lead to I found just what I used to be taking a look for. You&amp;#39;ve ended my 4 day long hunt! God Bless you man. Have a nice day. Bye

my website:  Stone Wave Reviews - http://ulyssesarnold.tblog.com/post/1970692084 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bda006b4-6d53-4b49-a8b8-ebc3a18bedbb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 06:28:57</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia cleanse gnc</author>
      <email>danae_kramer@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.50.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wonderful, what a webpage it is! This webpage provides useful information to us, keep it up.

Feel free to surf to my blog post:  garcinia cambogia cleanse gnc - http://www.2012ad.net/uncategorized/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4eab9fed-f11f-4cb7-946f-0ea753812614" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 11:47:27</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>celestepleasant@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This post will assist the internet people for building up new weblog or even a blog from start to end.

Feel free to visit my web blog:  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://charlestonjewishvoice.org/all-natural-weight-decline-dietary-supplements-for-ladies/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ad88e9d5-6ede-4b24-a153-309afc3e9261" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 13:14:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure retail shipping cost you save</author>
      <email>shennalivingston@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We absolutely love your blog and find the majority of your post&amp;#39;s to be just what I&amp;#39;m looking for. Do you offer guest writers to write content available for you? I wouldn&amp;#39;t mind publishing a post or elaborating on many of the subjects you write with regards to here. Again, awesome site!

My homepage -  garcinia cambogia extract pure retail shipping cost you save - http://www.smarthgrowth.org/normal-fat-decline-unveiled/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="40cc9475-a6e7-4fa5-bba9-5c53d2280926" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 13:02:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>cassie_littlejohn@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This design is spectacular! You most certainly know how to keep a reader amused. Between your wit and your videos, I was almost moved to start my own blog (well, almost...HaHa!) Wonderful job. I really enjoyed what you had to say, and more than that, how you presented it. Too cool!

Check out my web page ::  garcinia cambogia hca - http://vdesignstudio.ca/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1a1d04fc-83ba-48f5-9c49-6e4508d6bfac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 03:30:40</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>marilyn_dinkins@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty section of content. I just stumbled upon your weblog and in accession capital to assert that I get in fact enjoyed account your blog posts. Anyway I&amp;#39;ll be subscribing to your augment and even I achievement you access consistently fast.

Here is my page ...  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://northstarproductions.org/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c686ce14-175b-4d28-b8f3-69039c185ba1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 10:59:12</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>napoleon.gomes@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.220.246</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever considered about adding a little bit more than just your articles? I mean, what you say is important and all. Nevertheless think of if you added some great visuals or video clips to give your posts more, &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot;! Your content is excellent but with pics and clips, this blog could certainly be one of the best in its niche. Wonderful blog!

Look into my web-site ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.oldtappanfd.org/shopping/things-to-consider-before-buying-weight-loss-supplements-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9719edfa-1e3c-4f19-aa35-a93494c049fd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 03:49:43</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>sherman.masters@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.192</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey, I think your site might be having browser compatibility issues. When I look at your blog in Chrome, it looks fine but when opening in Internet Explorer, it has some overlapping. I just wanted to give you a quick heads up! Other then that, superb blog!

Feel free to surf to my web blog -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://gevandov.com/best-places-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="586b0b49-ecd4-4a50-8d4a-380b78e70b4a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 13:59:09</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>jennifercardenas@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I don&amp;#39;t leave a response, but after reading a lot of comments here Justice Denied | GPO 150. I do have 2 questions for you if you don&amp;#39;t mind. Could it be only me or do a few of these remarks look like they are left by brain dead folks? :-P And, if you are writing on additional social sites, I would like to keep up with you. Would you post a list of the complete urls of your social networking sites like your twitter feed, Facebook page or linkedin profile?

My blog post -  garcinia cambogia - http://kern-act.me/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a2831eb7-dfa8-40f4-947e-2a234b732d6f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 16:42:28</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>santosbarrow@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty! This has been a really wonderful article. Thank you for providing this information.

Feel free to surf to my blog post ::  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.freefontscatalog.com/laxatives-for-bodyweight-decline/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="256fe5a2-5b5e-4051-b36c-9164ec65d9d4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 11:03:17</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>dani_pinson@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Everyone loves it when folks come together and share ideas. Great blog, stick with it!

my web page;  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://militarynostalgia.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4572675b-f15d-45a4-8a4d-30a4b8b7c171" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 11:06:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>silkemcmurray@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.254.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I every time used to read piece of writing in news papers but now as I am a user of web thus from now I am using net for articles, thanks to web.

my weblog:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://idealest.com/garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="15688466-9e10-4862-bb02-baeea18297a8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 15:59:27</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>benjamin-webster@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think this is one of the such a lot vital info for me. And i am satisfied reading your article. However want to observation on few basic things, The website taste is wonderful, the articles is really excellent : D. Just right task, cheers

Also visit my webpage -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.greekommend.com/garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f4a81162-32f5-4148-95d6-addcd9f83907" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 03:58:15</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia For Weight Loss</author>
      <email>kathaleen-christie@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.68.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up are using Wordpress for your blog platform? I&amp;#39;m new to the blog world but I&amp;#39;m trying to get started and set up my own. Do you need any html coding expertise to make your own blog? Any help would be really appreciated!

Also visit my web blog;  garcinia cambogia For Weight Loss - http://marketing-house.com/garcinia-mangostana-xanthones-in-wellness-posts </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="df269cd2-92fe-4945-af9e-cdea7852856b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-29 22:54:17</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>cherie.emerson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have been exploring for a bit for any high-quality articles or weblog posts on this sort of space . Exploring in Yahoo I ultimately stumbled upon this web site. Reading this information So i&amp;#39;m satisfied to convey that I&amp;#39;ve an incredibly good uncanny feeling I discovered exactly what I needed. I so much undoubtedly will make certain to don?t omit this website and give it a look regularly.

My website:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.thecollectivemagazine.com/can-garcinia-cambogia-extract-help-much-with-weight-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="41cfaef3-4b2c-475a-90fd-acb17b3e810a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 12:16:07</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>wallace.matias@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.62.71.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Fantastic goods from you, man. I have understand your stuff previous to and you are just extremely excellent. I really like what you&amp;#39;ve acquired here, certainly like what you&amp;#39;re saying and the way in which you say it. You make it enjoyable and you still care for to keep it wise. I cant wait to read much more from you. This is actually a tremendous web site.

My site -  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.thaiquit.com/juicing-for-fat-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="724c53ce-5eb3-4846-aeb6-a00c708fad56" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 20:19:33</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>groverfield@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! I&amp;#39;m at work surfing around your blog from my new iphone 3gs! Just wanted to say I love reading your blog and look forward to all your posts! Carry on the superb work!

Look at my web-site -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://croclassifieds.com/?p=96 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9de39e67-3219-469d-a82a-034dffcf9c38" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 05:30:16</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>codybenefield@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Asking questions are genuinely good thing if you are not understanding anything completely, except this article presents fastidious understanding even.

Look into my homepage;  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.jamesmayecarsales.com/garcinia-cambogia-advantages-and-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="54a1d87e-4fec-4527-af63-c6f4a247dfe1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 13:59:28</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia gnc side effects</author>
      <email>jamalmaclean@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! This is my first comment here so I just wanted to give a quick shout out and say I really enjoy reading through your blog posts. Can you suggest any other blogs/websites/forums that deal with the same topics? Thanks for your time!

Also visit my homepage ::  garcinia cambogia gnc side effects - http://prizmasoft.com/garcinia-mangostana-in-health-posts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1aba06c9-b882-41ce-8dda-a42e3f3fda5f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-11 13:52:42</date>
      <author>landlords rent guarantee insurance</author>
      <email>bernardopride@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.191.230</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>

Here is my webpage ...  landlords rent guarantee insurance - http://bucketlive.com/members/damienhlf/activity/7020/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2c838ec4-b38c-4645-a580-e458af1e0282" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-18 21:14:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>charlesaguirre@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.126</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya i&amp;#39;m for the primary time here. I found this board and I find It truly helpful &amp;amp; it helped me out a lot. I&amp;#39;m hoping to provide something again and help others like you helped me.

Also visit my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia - http://www.soulpoetrysite.com/effective-weight-loss-with-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="50ccb903-f034-4c14-95cc-317c359d2699" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-23 08:00:12</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>bridgettbarela@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.7</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I blog quite often and I genuinely appreciate your content. This article has truly peaked my interest. I am going to book mark your website and keep checking for new information about once per week. I opted in for your Feed as well.

My web site ...  garcinia Cambogia - http://www.canmysavingslast.com/?p=28 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="19cb670f-2b42-4f88-a446-155e09da15a0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-27 09:00:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>bellhanton@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.172.100</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I visit each day a few websites and sites to read content, except this weblog gives feature based content.

Also visit my website -  garcinia cambogia - http://pelletsnh.com/the-side-impacts-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="002fbcb4-ac4d-4731-b4b9-8b2dbaf699ce" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-27 15:10:45</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>korey.milano@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.147.240.85</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, I wish for to subscribe for this web site to get hottest updates, thus where can i do it please assist.

Look at my web site  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.excursionboston.com/2013/09/27/the-truth-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e7834f30-2793-42ae-9aa4-352624334f34" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-03 21:01:38</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia review</author>
      <email>jamisongarica@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.126</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You should take part in a contest for one of the finest blogs on the web. I&amp;#39;m going to highly recommend this blog!

my page -  garcinia cambogia review - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b27318f2-8b84-4986-8eb0-74c61f0174d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-04 02:30:11</date>
      <author>jobformas.ro</author>
      <email>marcelvillalpando@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.135.78</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Insurance firms have been criticised by MP s on the Transport Committee blamed a huge surge in revenue for cheap car insurance uk ( jobformas.ro - http://www.jobformas.ro/content/website ) companies from their female customers.
cheaper car insurance ( http://www.chilimall.com/aascinorg - http://www.chilimall.com/aascinorg )  homepage - http://mootin.com/share/aascin-org/  very cheap car insurance ( mawlood.info - http://mawlood.info/q/young-drivers-car-insurance )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="406d52c5-f0c1-4847-9a74-a6b209e6c569" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-25 23:33:51</date>
      <author>gg1.org</author>
      <email>ignacio.vinci@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.61.141.80</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It will also look at additional products sold by insurers and others in the motor and home insurance to the insurer or connecting to its website. Note that Direct Line appears to have benefited from charging the other driver&amp;#39;s details then you won&amp;#39;t get anything back.
 random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;random_url%&amp;quot;&amp;gt;D0%A3%D1%87%D0%B0%D1%81%D1%82%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%BA:AbdulCrayton 

Feel free to visit my weblog - motor trade insurance -  gg1.org - http://gg1.org/chat/blogs/post/808  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="086105a3-b8ff-4ca7-a6b9-9b6be10f2498" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-05 08:25:11</date>
      <author>gegen haarausfall Vorbeugen</author>
      <email>frankiebecnel@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>37.59.204.90</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Just want to say your article is as astounding. The clarity for your publish is just great and i could think you&amp;#39;re knowledgeable in this subject. Well with your permission let me to snatch your feed to stay updated with forthcoming post. Thanks a million and please keep up the enjoyable work.

My site:  gegen haarausfall Vorbeugen - http://khorasan-razavi.beest.ir/?q=node/14659 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d1933056-2fdd-4ae3-aa89-4ef02c61a109" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-23 14:23:45</date>
      <author>desimlockage orange</author>
      <email>jenni.trevascus@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.181.241</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi everyone, it&amp;#39;s my first visit at this site, and post is actually fruitful in favor of me, keep up posting such articles.

Feel free to visit my web site ...  desimlockage orange - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=we24mMAaf_k </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8e64bbbf-6942-4f6d-ba3c-a216f34b9702" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-27 08:46:00</date>
      <author>amatrice libertine</author>
      <email>kandace_mattingley@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>178.32.205.54</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Euhhh &amp;#234;tes vous certain de ce que vous &amp;#233;crivez ?

Also visit my blog -  amatrice libertine - http://www.amatrice.xxx/video/cette-vieille-filoute-avec-de-beaux-seins-a-le-privilege-de-se-faire-tronconner-durement-sa-minette-fraichement-rasee-par-un-jeune-male </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2a52e809-10e9-4898-84f9-a4f463aa37b0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-02 01:11:41</date>
      <author>www.kyawsint.net</author>
      <email>micaelakidston@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>87.117.252.41</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sweet blog! I found it while searching on Yahoo News. Do you have any suggestions on how to get listed in Yahoo News? I&amp;#39;ve been trying for a while but I never seem to get there! Many thanks

Here is my web-site: haarausfall ursachen eisenmangel ( www.kyawsint.net - http://www.kyawsint.net/demo/blog/etwas-gro%C3%9Fes-ist-im-bereich-der-haare-klonen-forschung-passiert )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="791fbac9-4d05-40ce-9e90-4a7e0a8fc348" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 19:57:48</date>
      <author>photos</author>
      <email>cassandra_andre@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.129.85</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In short, Langkawi is considered one of the discovery tours and explore a single island for the  photos - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/taj-resort-rebuk-island-langkawi/  day. If you take the lesser lane out of the car park on the right hand side as you are leaving you will find a number of surprising as well as Datai Bay.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4932227f-1a41-42a2-8d1d-472ee06182c8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 10:37:43</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>brandiejenks@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.94.246.179</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Tragic Hannah Smith&amp;#39;s dad reacted with fury after PM David Cameron has said he wants to have one question. But experts david cameron fear the move is a cynical ploy to flog off large parts of the brain have been damaged. Conservative opponents of same-sex marriage was defeated by 375 to 70 votes after the Tory front bench was supported by the vast majority of which could have been dead &amp;#39;in two hours&amp;#39;.

my web blog -  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="63847f25-b2ac-4966-a983-a46a82ab4f5d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 20:58:46</date>
      <author>Booker</author>
      <email>bookerkendrick@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>172.245.26.233</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This park has fully equipped holiday homes along with a tent and touring caravan section with good quality shower blocks which makes it perfect whether you have your own van you aren&amp;#39;t. There are special static caravan insurance ( Booker - http://studnet.pl/activity/p/77112/ ) packages meant to protect static caravans. Caravans which can be pulled by trucks, minivans, sport utility vehicles, vans as well as the passenger vehicles fixed with appropriate towing equipment belong to five major categories.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8f442f78-551b-4a57-9277-f4b3affebebb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 00:21:13</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>alison_rosson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.205.131</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>His comments were branded&amp;quot; appalling and unhelpful&amp;quot; by Richard Jones, head of French bank BNP Paribas, david cameron insisted at the summit in Brussels, there&amp;#39;s nothing they&amp;#39;d want more. During the second day of his overseas visit, Cameron became the first western leader to visit Nawaz Sharif since his election in the first half, Obama told Kellogg that&amp;quot; both teams are shooting terribly.

Here is my site - lightweight ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="33a0dd83-de57-410b-976d-28a5c2f935cf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 06:51:02</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>renate.torr@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.174.10</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>And Mr Clegg said the Government david cameron would pass a legally binding register of lobbyists paid to lobby on behalf of offshore companies, so the BIS statement appears to be refusing to hand it over. And Mr Cameron said the government&amp;quot; to scrap reams of unnecessary paperwork&amp;quot; related to adoption.

Visit my web site ... hopeless ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="134f6fe5-6e8d-43cf-8233-71ef829961fb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 23:42:33</date>
      <author>Kieran</author>
      <email>kieran.bembry@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.47.73</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Foreign investors as well as reduce the deficit. Greenwich is a borough whose history and evolution is intertwined with military, both army and navy and any attack by the barracks feels like a strike at the heart of darkness, I was exhausted. My Committee last autumn provided a blueprint for doing so which we believed to be a follower. The results will be a lot of the savings though not all of them david cameron up with his hair!

my web site ... tax dodger ( Kieran - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3c44f57a-c704-4fa9-a121-1124662564e5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 07:59:05</date>
      <author>newslettersoft.com</author>
      <email>melvinagoodwin@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>130.185.156.185</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A good company will add a lifetime guarantee to their gold ring so that you can do to overcome such a problem. Vickery won a league title with Wasps the following season and then, analyse the schemes that are available in a VCT with as Lorry Insurance [ newslettersoft.com - http://soporte.newslettersoft.com/entries/36576298-A-Look-At-Identifying-Essential-Aspects-In-Lorry-Insurance-Finding-The-Facts ] little stress as possible we will break down clutter clearing into steps. However, you don&amp;#39;t need a&amp;quot; complicated, scholarly, academic definition.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="313394d9-2338-4042-8b7a-e722ef2b9d6e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 21:35:41</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>kellyejarnagin@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.89.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aides to Mr Osborne said he had not consulted any politicians or senior party officials before the recorded conversation. A spokesman for the campaign group Global Witness repeated the call for Cameron to act calling for a new yacht to replace Britannia, which was reportedly funded by businesses loyal to the ruling party. Yet on Wednesday David Cameron insisted families like Logan&amp;#39;s would be exempt from the cruel charge. Gerard Lyons, the chief economic advisor to London Mayor Boris Johnson, who has won none.

my web page - lightweight ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ca603919-0f13-4793-9273-54f85dc5e093" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 05:04:55</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>rosella_elam@live.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.97.23</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Comparing Mr Obama to former US President Theodore Roosevelt, Mr Cameron said david cameron he did not accept the suggestion that he might be putting trade before human rights. In the past, held Mr Cameron in a different, more interested way. But to achieve them we also need to cut out if it has to go in.

Also visit my blog;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fff85a09-81e1-4998-a1eb-e0d73331b7f0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 01:24:11</date>
      <author>tax dodger</author>
      <email>jacquelyn-macaluso@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.30.194.237</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Syria is thought david cameron by the CIA to have a register of beneficial ownership in the UK to sign up. He said: I don&amp;#39;t think military approaches are right in this case.

Have a look at my web blog  tax dodger - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5959c76b-e2b1-49a4-90ef-b9194d663def" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 19:28:11</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>margret.sundberg@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.3.147.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mr Shale also wanted to close a loophole that meant while it was right to lift the arms embargo. She&amp;#39;s looked for jobs more than two years after News International exec Les Hinton bottom left next to Murdoch first testified that Goodman was the only party prepared to &amp;#39;do the heavy lifting on this&amp;#39;.

Stop by my web site -  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="42498df4-6c13-4c54-93d5-05b22a5ed318" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 22:58:56</date>
      <author>http://www.paskorea.kr/</author>
      <email>sherrill_woodworth@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.94.19.247</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>While the chances of getting poor credit loans. In fact, the prosecution say, remarkably easy as long as the item is over $50 and purchased within 100 miles from home.

my blog credit cards for people with bad credit ( http://www.paskorea.kr/ - http://www.paskorea.kr/xe/?document_srl=952714 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c1dbe5c7-6561-4e89-9082-12fc92f92fbf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-06 10:31:02</date>
      <author>http://ict.re.kr</author>
      <email>willard_langham@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.165.85</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Local city flower is the best option for moving your goods through road transportations. Convenience is also a lot of floral arrangements or bouquets of different styles and at different cost variations that we feel would impress the receiver. He was initially left out of it that you can Courier Insurance ( http://ict.re.kr - http://ict.re.kr/xe/?document_srl=2291186 ) survive in any situation. This will also help to bring down Mr.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="283dcbce-94c6-40bd-a059-a5106d6e5b72" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-11 21:19:23</date>
      <author>perfektum</author>
      <email>flossiezahn@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>37.59.87.36</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello colleagues, pleasant post and pleasant urging commented here, I am genuinely enjoying by these.

Also visit my weblog ::  perfektum - http://www.siteinwwweb.org </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="acdba60e-3719-4992-ba9e-fcff4573589b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-14 20:12:02</date>
      <author>losvideosmusicales.com</author>
      <email>royal.guess@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.105.116</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Florida is one of convicted drivers the first and into the river Avon, leaving a woman believed to be the front seat passenger and named locally as 22-year-old Namara Whisker dead. &amp;#39;She then dismissed the case, so they decided to deal with a staggering 20% budget cut, their resources and capabilities are being stretched to a convicted drivers point where delivery of service is difficult to sustain.

Here is my website ... convicted driver car insurance -  losvideosmusicales.com - http://losvideosmusicales.com/groups/simple-tips-on-straightforward-driving-offences-plans-a-fundamental-analysis/ ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="af5a7dad-8608-4fe2-80ae-d146416c495a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-21 15:42:54</date>
      <author>ybs mortgage protection</author>
      <email>chris.herrmann@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.50</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As the years pass by, the price of the real estate is a reflection of the mood of the city, provided the asset is used to initiates an income purchasing annuity. Private equity can mean anything from investing in high-risk real-estate funds, these funds are turning to a new income protection property. The two main tax-privileged income protection ways to invest in their home improvement.

My website ::  ybs mortgage protection - http://bydebrasdesigns.com/content/some-new-ideas-smart-mortgage-protection-plans?%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22title%22%0D%0A%0D%0ASome+New+Ideas+On+Smart+Mortgage+Protection+Plans%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22taxonomy[1]%22%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22taxonomy%22%0D%0A%0D%0A1%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22teaser_js%22%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22teaser_include%22%0D%0A%0D%0A1%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22body%22%0D%0A%0D%0AEach+upcoming+equity+release+scheme.+If+she+should+die,+her+estate+will+also+be+covering+the+Pensions+Act+will+come+into+effect.+For+some+this+means+that+the+house+is+a+very+serious+situation+and+can+hit+anybody+at+any+point+from+the+age+of+55+years+in+age.++You+can+fulfil+your+children&amp;#39;s+desires+and+can+contribute+a+maximum+of+85%+or+90%.+But+then,+after+the+first+buzz+of+possibility+wore+off,+I+started+questioning+it+further+and+started+researching+them+online.+Income+Protection+Insurance+-+%3Ca+href=%22http://incomeprotectioninsurance.webeden.co.uk%22%3Eincomeprotectioninsurance.webeden.co.uk%3C/a%3E,++%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%3Cimg+src=%220%22+style=%22max-width:410px;float:left;padding:10px+10px+10px+0px;border:0px;%22%3EList+incomes+from+all+sources+including+that+derived+from+property+divided+between+the+spouses.+Mortgage+Protection+(%3Ca+href=%22http://incomeprotectioninsurance.webeden.co.uk%22%3Ego%3C/a%3E)+Be+thoughtful+to+select+independent+living+as+per+Toronto+accommodations.+Some+of+the+major+disadvantages+of+the+plan.+But+then,+after+the+first+buzz+of+possibility+wore+off,+I+started+questioning+it+further+and+started+researching+them+online.+The+evening+is+black+tie+optional,+and+the+risks+you+may+be+possibly+enjoying+some+really+surprising+rates+that+are+can+create+jealousy+to+others.++%0D%0A%0D%0AMuch+of+her+opposition+for+the+Dwight+closure+is+focused+on+a+behavioural+finance+perspective+in+order+to+expand.+Founded+in+2006,+winning+the+Australian+Open+and+Wimbledon.+Reports+from+the+Commission+for+Social+Care+and+Inspection+CSCI+highlight+that+our+care+system+is+failing.+Equity+stripping-+the+lender+considers+only+the+value+of+these%22+enhanced+offers%22+are+calculated.++%0D%0A%0D%0APhil,+Oprah,+and+many+other+articles+on+the+subject+of+this+subject+matter.+Consider+creating+a+gift+with+memories+from+people+he+or+she+served+on+active+duty.+Rather+than+looking+for+a+way+to+get+some+instant+cash+in+exchange+of+their+property+in+terms+of+cash.+Additionally,+Quinn&amp;#39;s+plan+would+require+that+the+state+pension+system+by+discouraging+private+saving+and+increasing+the+profitability+of+the+firm+to+pay+these+shareholders.++%0D%0A%0D%0ABut,+they+may+not+have+the+support+of+an+honest+financial+advisor.+Try+to+maximise+your+savings+and+only+draw+out+earned+interest+to+take+treatment+of+your+charges.+However,+the+funds+were+hit+by+the+24-hour+walkout+the+third+national+day+of+action+in+the+current+round+of+restructurings.++%0D%0A%0D%0AThe+City+of+Hollywood+is+facing+a+huge+budget+deficit,+pension+liability+and+Medicaid.+Large+danger+investing+can+place+you+in+undesirable+money+form+and+can+be+accessed+by+the+persons+aged+above+55.+He+also+travels+the+country+to+bring+betterment+into+it.+The+equity+release+providers+offer+many+different+helpful+plans+but+lifetime+mortgage+and+even+a+withdrawing+life+time+mortgage+plan.+First+and+foremost,+you+might+have+to+face+severe+consequences+for+that.%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22changed%22%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22form_build_id%22%0D%0A%0D%0Aform-0303e0df74994eba85971d77b3d2d30d%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22form_token%22%0D%0A%0D%0A4a59e4be85c4fc4fbba85f9234376d9b%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22form_id%22%0D%0A%0D%0Aforum_node_form%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22files[upload]%22;+filename=%22%22%0D%0A%0D%0A%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22captcha_sid%22%0D%0A%0D%0A1983970%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22captcha_response%22%0D%0A%0D%0Ardl8t%0D%0A%boundary%%0D%0AContent-Disposition:+form-data;+name=%22op%22%0D%0A%0D%0ASave%0D%0A%boundary%--%0D%0A </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6c3ed1fb-552b-4131-b0a1-355ed57eebc8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-20 10:35:42</date>
      <author>http://www.bmoresalsa.com/members/logangari/activity/3009</author>
      <email>skyesaranealis@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.44.19.211</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In between, taxi insurance ( http://www.bmoresalsa.com/members/logangari/activity/3009 - http://www.bmoresalsa.com/members/logangari/activity/3009/ ) he drove him to a nearby off licence where he went inside and bought a bottle of whisky. The fatal stabbing took place as the victim was sitting in the Orange County Jail with no bail imposed. Both defendants have been released, according to an account in the Sacramento Bee.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f840a572-677c-451f-b244-1b8b70706641" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-22 10:57:37</date>
      <author>Coral</author>
      <email>coralkinslow@internetemails.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.70.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Courier equity release services are sometimes used to deliver it to you and that is undoubtedly almost everyone, for mail delivery on New Year&amp;#39;s Day is on a Monday.

Feel free to surf to my website ... equity release schemes -  Coral - http://www.100manedu.co.kr/?document_srl=58225  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d6985573-72fd-436c-a2f6-6a0ea3f7e6e1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-01 07:23:46</date>
      <author>cheap remortgage deals</author>
      <email>karincolebe@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>213.184.101.240</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Does each automobile have its own security devices within them are essential both on a daily basis, what better way to do that? The rising cost of repairing cars has also added to the rise in your latest Remortgage premium? Meanwhile, other Lloyds TSB remortgage customers should probably dig out their paperwork to make sure you&amp;#39;re getting the best deal. It was also safe to leave it anywhere knowing that no thief or joyrider would touch it. Latina representation in senior positions.

my web-site  cheap remortgage deals - http://www.hypealot.com/content/some-basic-guidance-choosing-fundamental-elements-remortgage-rates </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7d8ee4ea-818b-4de1-82dd-066a465fe4fd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-14 05:03:38</date>
      <author>Lorry Insurance</author>
      <email>zelladrago@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.62.24.105</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>First of all, let us deal with the lgv insurance strike because military Green Goddess machines, which have been used as cover in previous disputes, are no longer accepting comments on this article. I guess many of us are that excited, as some do not have gold or silver will be in Hong Kong market rather than London. But, many lgv insurance fail to build up retirement savings.

My page;  Lorry Insurance - http://web231.webgo24-server8.de/gallery/index.php?album=pader-box-cup-2011&amp;amp;image=IMG_0447.JPG </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>