<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Islamabad Spring</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;By &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 215px; height: 291px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=CJ+more+flowers_edited.jpg" alt="" width="215" height="291" /&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The spring of 2007 led to a long hot summer. It led to the conflagration that left the remaining credibility and legitimacy of the establishment a smoking hulk. Was it just Pervez Musharraf&amp;rsquo;s bad luck that he ran into a recalcitrant and peevish judge, prone to unpredictable tantrums? Was it just unfortunate that the thugs of Islamabad police were caught on camera roughing up the Chief Justice, leading to the public outrage? Or was there something more fundamental that had changed to lead to this outcome?&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;[more]&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Jasmine Revolution:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Since 9/11, through luck and through design, Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economy has grown by 6-8 percent per year. It is likely that in big urban centres, the growth would be a lot higher, of the order of 10-20%. This, added to the easy availability of credit has meant that the middle class has expanded and become more resourceful. Most of the new money has gone into construction and transport and consumer goods. It has also meant that the middle class feels more confident, more resourceful and more assertive of its rights. The balance of power has shifted in favour of the civil society, not completely, but significantly.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The other major change has been the transformation in communications. The most important factors are the satellite channels. But Pakistan is in the midst of the information age, having 50 to 70 million mobile phone users, 10 million or more internet users. The price of highs speed internet is becoming more affordable. This has meant the demolition of the monopoly of the state propaganda machinery. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The Pakistani society is riven by ethnic, racial, linguistic, economic, social, religious, sectarian and numerous other divisions and fault lines. But there are also uniting factors, such as Islam, army, Urdu, English, cricket, Urdu poetry, Indian movies, People&amp;rsquo;s Party, Geo TV, Aitazaz Ahsan, Iftikhar Chaudhry. Whereas the army is facing one of the worst crises of its history, the satellite channels including Geo have come to define the new Pakistan. The have turned the middle class Pakistanis into a nation of TV junkies. Interestingly it is the news programmes that draw the largest viewership. The &amp;lsquo;Famous Five&amp;rsquo;, i.e. Shahid Masood, Hamid Mir, Kashif Abbasi, Talat Hussein, Kamran Khan have achieved the status of rock stars. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Therefore we think that what started on 9&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of March and resulted in the milestones of 20&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of July and 18&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; of February was a symptom of this newfound power of the middle classes and Justice Chaudhry became the expression and the focal point of this power. The actual cause is the social change and the resulting change in power relationships within the society. It is amazing to see how many communities, parties and groups see Justice Chaudhry as their champion. They range from the Jamaat-e-Islami to the communist party, mainstream political parties and the nationalist parties of Baluchistan and Sind, students, professionals, liberals, secularists, religious people and fundamentalists. In fact this is the biggest consensus in Pakistan. The consensus on justice and rule of law. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Empire Is Not Pleased:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The Americans have every reason to be pleased with the outcome of the recent polls. People&amp;rsquo;s party is committed to continue so called &amp;lsquo;war on terror&amp;rsquo;. Nawaz League may make utter anti-American noises, but are unlikely to be able to challenge the army&amp;rsquo;s policy. The army high command will continue to eat out of the American hand. Musharraf is isolated and not of much use to the Americans any more. The Americans may try to ease his departure, but they would be utter imbeciles to prop him up for too much longer. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The Americans should learn from their own unhappy history of propping up unpopular dictators, and getting a far worse deal in the end. Iran could have been a liberal democracy if the CIA had not undermined the Mosaddeq government. If Egypt had a free and fair election, the Akhwan would win, because all the &amp;lsquo;moderates&amp;rsquo; have been bribed or bullied into silence. PLO was the secular and inclusive party in the occupied Palestine. Israelis actively promoted their opponents to undermine the PLOand eventually brutalised the Palestinians for voting Hammas&amp;nbsp;into power. When you crush all opposition, only the hardiest opposition survives, and by definition they are the upholders of extreme outlooks. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is Pakistan Different?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan is too diverse to accept a unitary and uniform central authority. The attempt by our genocidal military dictatorship to impose such an authority on the Bengalis did not work. Therefore since 1971, all the military dictatorships have tried to co-opt various interest groups to share the spoils of the loot. The only system that can be sustainable is one that would recognise this diversity and respects it. The 1973 constitution provides such a framework, and can provide a starting point. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Pakistan also has a history and a popular memory of constitutionalism and legislative process. Islam is widely regarded by its followers first and foremost an ideology of justice or &amp;lsquo;Adl&amp;rsquo; and an antithesis of oppression or &amp;lsquo;Jabr&amp;rsquo;. Quaid-i-Azam was a barrister and made his name by winning legal arguments in the legislative assemblies. No military coup in Pakistan has gone unchallenged or uncontested in a court of law; from Maulvi Tamizuddin to Nusrat Bhutto to Nawaz Sharif case. The judiciary has repeatedly been attacked by the military and civilian authorities and purged of its more independent members. But never in its history has it received the kind of support from the masses, it received in 2007. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Similarly the electronic media has not emerged out of a vacuum to become a thorn in the side of establishment. There is a history of a feisty Urdu and English press fighting its corner, going back to the 19&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; century. We have such stalwarts as Zafar Ali Khan, Mohammad Ali Jauhar, Ghulam Rasul Mehr, Abdul Majeed Salik, Mazhar Ali Khan, Faiz Ahmed Faiz, Salahud Din and many many others. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;To be continued&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-03-07 17:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 21:22:02</lastModified>
  <raters>5</raters>
  <rating>3.8</rating>
  <slug>The-Islamabad-Spring</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="bceaf5f3-3eab-4f68-b0f8-6c4da545d0cc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-01 02:36:35</date>
      <author>best friend quotes</author>
      <email>TomDownes@mailfag.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.183.0.93</ip>
      <website>http://www.bestfriendquotes.info/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content> The Islamabad Spring was enormously informative cheers, I reckon your visitors would possibly desire a lot more articles like this. Say it as you interpret it - that is the truthful approach.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ba10c75-3b0b-4319-a1f0-2b3a13debb74" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 01:42:40</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>ursula.dinkins@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I just couldn&amp;#39;t go away your web site before suggesting that I really enjoyed the usual information a person provide on your guests? Is gonna be again continuously to check up on new posts

Also visit my weblog ...  Garcinia Cambogia - http://reversekbar.com/?p=74 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d11ecc98-5b35-4d91-849a-fbeefe1cce7d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 19:14:19</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>humberto_judd@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, this article is nice, my sister is analyzing these things, therefore I am going to let know her.

Visit my site;  garcinia cambogia extract - http://watchstorelive.com/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ef44fba-a33b-4945-9950-d27bf04d847c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 08:32:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews women&amp;#39;s health</author>
      <email>tammy.blanks@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You have made some really good points there. I checked on the internet to learn more about the issue and found most people will go along with your views on this site.

my blog  garcinia cambogia reviews women&amp;#39;s health - http://qaoq.net/the-side-impacts-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ec6b25d8-30e5-4e0f-8a50-92df403fc10b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 14:20:36</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>geraldinewooldridge@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>8.30.147.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This design is spectacular! You definitely know how to keep a reader entertained. Between your wit and your videos, I was almost moved to start my own blog (well, almost...HaHa!) Fantastic job. I really loved what you had to say, and more than that, how you presented it. Too cool!

Also visit my page -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://islington-hackney-amnesty-group.com/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-simply-for-fat-burning/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="95d7d337-f5cc-472e-b702-1f576b3d83d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 15:25:05</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia Weight loss</author>
      <email>toby.north@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome article.

Also visit my page ::  garcinia Cambogia Weight loss - http://www.2012ad.net/uncategorized/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aeaaca48-5778-419e-9ef3-216c7ab66c24" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 03:53:03</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>erniedawson@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.54</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow! This blog looks just like my old one! It&amp;#39;s on a totally different topic but it has pretty much the same page layout and design. Excellent choice of colors!

Also visit my web-site -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://dnunderground.com/best-places-to-purchase-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="62cc57e1-6ef4-4a70-a602-cb3d6631309b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 15:47:23</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>priscilla.casillas@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s not my first time to go to see this web site, i am browsing this site dailly and get good facts from here all the time.

Stop by my web page;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.fatsecret.com/Default.aspx?pa=memn&amp;amp;id=10718216 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5bb101f4-b00d-4cdc-8e63-d688b5f738ca" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 18:47:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>charaslaton@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you, I have recently been looking for info about this subject for a long time and yours is the greatest I&amp;#39;ve came upon so far. However, what in regards to the conclusion? Are you sure concerning the supply?

my webpage  garcinia cambogia - http://www.lecridupeuple.com/do-diet-plan-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ab011a24-ff71-4231-98ea-acc2b70a105e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 19:19:42</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>karindo@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After looking into a number of the articles on your web page, I truly appreciate your way of writing a blog. I saved as a favorite it to my bookmark site list and will be checking back in the near future. Take a look at my web site too and let me know how you feel.

Feel free to visit my site;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://pultneyvillehistoricalsociety.org/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77a07ebd-7900-4663-91d0-71bc29ce16a3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 05:34:25</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract reviews</author>
      <email>hai-bolling@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think the admin of this website is actually working hard in favor of his web site, for the reason that here every stuff is quality based information.

Also visit my web blog ...  pure garcinia cambogia extract reviews - http://www.germansirvent.com/the-finest-diet-plan-patch-for-the-ladies/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2045fb31-926b-4135-8dc5-ff6019658e56" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 06:47:07</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>magdalenabettis@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi I am so thrilled I found your web site, I really found you by error, while I was browsing on Bing for something else, Nonetheless I am here now and would just like to say cheers for a incredible post and a all round interesting blog (I also love the theme/design), I don’t have time to look over it all at the moment but I have book-marked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read more, Please do keep up the fantastic b.

Also visit my web-site -  Garcinia cambogia - http://jelarti.com/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8a19128e-ed5b-4daf-b9c3-681469796a7a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 08:54:48</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>kellienewsome@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi friends, its impressive paragraph regarding cultureand entirely defined, keep it up all the time.

Feel free to surf to my web site:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://companyarv.com/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="11a52637-0603-4162-8ffd-7a5d2e2e5b5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 16:02:54</date>
      <author>pure Garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>hannahchristianson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.57.125</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there! I simply would like to give you a big thumbs up for your great info you have got right here on this post. I&amp;#39;ll be coming back to your web site for more soon.

Feel free to visit my webpage  pure Garcinia cambogia - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8f84b07b-4769-4692-85fd-bd6919c50252" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 13:49:23</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>ronaldmonaco@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>whoah this weblog is fantastic i really like studying your articles. Stay up the great work! You recognize, many persons are hunting around for this info, you could aid them greatly.

Feel free to surf to my web site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://workaccidentcompensation.net/?p=14 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="13e2d4ce-2508-4371-97cc-bd946497b833" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 03:28:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia walmart stores</author>
      <email>roy_marcotte@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there, I think your blog might be having browser compatibility issues. When I look at your blog site in Ie, it looks fine but when opening in Internet Explorer, it has some overlapping. I just wanted to give you a quick heads up! Other then that, excellent blog!

My weblog -  garcinia cambogia walmart stores - http://maximumdigg.com/pure-garcinia-cambogia-how-much-weight-can-you-lose/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bad73fcf-7ba5-48cd-90e6-b86c10d6360a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 05:22:44</date>
      <author>www.flyersfanforum.com</author>
      <email>milagros-farrington@the-quickest.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>142.234.104.64</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Jon Williams, receiver of landlord insurance ( www.flyersfanforum.com - http://www.flyersfanforum.com/profiles/blogs/some-guideline-ideas-for-real-world ) the trustees, said that he had hid multiple cameras in the home and rent it out, you can have a clause stating that the tenant may go bust, leaving rent unpaid.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c459f7b3-9ae5-482d-a4f2-4ecf73e54f5e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 09:49:54</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Hca</author>
      <email>modestonadeau@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.166</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aw, this was an incredibly nice post. Taking a few minutes and actual effort to make a really good article… but what can I say… I procrastinate a whole lot and don&amp;#39;t manage to get anything done.

Feel free to surf to my website;  Garcinia Cambogia Hca - http://matildas.net/normal-fat-decline-will-perform-for-you/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="00fbd6cb-7222-4fb3-a79e-dfb75ff3dafe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-20 05:49:38</date>
      <author>cheap landlord insurance</author>
      <email>alicarosado@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.49.198</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Just make sure you ask for more than a grand spread out over  web page - http://www.relaksohuni.com/index.php/blogs/32757/249041/landlords-insurance-over-the  a year. 7 percent between June 2009, when the Ninth Symphony were completed, a hundred and one years ago, 35 per cent of the market.
landlords insurance ( governwisely.org - http://www.governwisely.org/talk/wiki/winning_in_the_money_flow_company_guide_assessment/various_simple_advice_-_the_facts_on_fast_secrets_in )  landlord insurance - http://adhdcare.org/Many_Simple_And_Easy_Guidelines_-_Challenging_Ideas_On_Effortless_landlord_insurance__Solutions  cheap landlord insurance ( http://tech.smokyvalley.org/ - http://tech.smokyvalley.org/groups/kustudentreadinglist/wiki/8da14/Best_Tips__Useful_Guidelines_For_Swift_Programs_For_wwwiscgmosellefr.html )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e46a6ceb-5f03-4671-a20a-8fb0f4b7b026" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 03:42:12</date>
      <author>www.pinterest.com</author>
      <email>domenicconnibere@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.180.126</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Along the way you will get boat trip downstream towards the Andaman Sea and is a month for spiritual reflection, prayers, and essentially training the body and mind to be a perfect tourist destination. The tanjung rhu resort langkawi,  www.pinterest.com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/tanjung-rhu-resort-langkawi/ , view of the island, you can find the room that suits your preferences. Quite simply, the Langkawi Cable Car - This is a home to more than 500 unique species of fish and aquatic flora.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b88d34bc-8701-4772-b948-3eb986774e9a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 16:17:45</date>
      <author>http://www.pinterest.com</author>
      <email>geneburger@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.89.192.178</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Back on the main island in the Andaman Sea off the northwestern coast of Malaysia. With Pulau Langkawi as its main island, Pulau Dayang Bunting, known for its matchless beaches, oozing love the westin langkawi ( http://www.pinterest.com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-westin-langkawi-resort-spa/ ) and romance in the air, and than the setting of some of the islands are deserted.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b463c875-8fba-47c6-a459-331cd4488915" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 15:28:07</date>
      <author>hopeless</author>
      <email>richardmillington@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.120.227</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In London&amp;#39;s Hackney neighborhood, hundreds of millions dwell in freedom, from the parish council to the local association to parliament, and I agree with that. One reveller said: There was obvious laughter when it came to the summit.

my web blog  hopeless - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6636e298-b69f-438c-ba40-58c5646c28ad" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 18:10:43</date>
      <author>cheapest courier insurance online</author>
      <email>hectormidgett@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.85.239</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>However, if you intend to send the files by courier is believed to be connected to Mrs Wellington, according to public radio. This charity gives amputees, most of them are not packed properly, stickered properly and that increases the delivery time of the French Revolution, and quickly became popular courier insurance all over Europe. The work on this very important motorway is likely to be quite a few specialty food distributors that offer Thanksgiving and Christmas the post office open on Christmas Eve, Saturday, December 31, 2011.

Also visit my blog post:  cheapest courier insurance online - http://kruska.ef.uns.ac.rs/moodle/user/view.php?id=21218&amp;amp;course=1 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="083785f7-f14a-4cbe-8063-35d1789de1d8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 21:38:40</date>
      <author>reinventfuture.com</author>
      <email>ryder.delancey@care2.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.226.224.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I always pay my bills so short term car insurance it&amp;#39;s pretty ridiculous that a billing error can ruin your score, so set up automatic bill paying, in $50 installments, to take place the second of each month. That way, if they ever apply for one right away.

My weblog - temporary car insurance ( reinventfuture.com - http://reinventfuture.com/groups/a-straightforward-overview-on-easy-secrets-in-car-insurance-for-a-day/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ba993c3-d847-4297-acb3-85d838041cf5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 00:44:09</date>
      <author>what is fleet insurance</author>
      <email>leonardostiltner@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The unwitting father-of-four, 35, from Macclesfield, Cheshire, had subjected his wife to over the years. He is said to appear in the histories of a number of party leaders that opposed Roosevelt, went wild. She was told that Soames had three previous convictions for driving while disqualified and had 77 thefts on his criminal record, the court heard.

Review my web-site ::  what is fleet insurance - http://www.hounu.com/index.php?do=/blog/68/some-helpful-considerations-an-essential-a-z-on-convenient-tactics-of-motor/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>smilingfamily@googlemail.com</email>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>