<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Asylum Taken Over </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f7%2fThe+Asylum+Taken+Over+.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Dar Sahib came knocking on the door, a kashkol (1.5m x 1.5m) in hand, begging for a 1 per cent increase. I have told him to go away. The court will not be moved by the considerations of economics or economic literacy or control of inflation. It only wants justice for the sprawling and miserable humanity, including Arsalan Beta. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;He had the temerity to go to the parliament and get it approved retrospectively. The court takes a dim view of these underhand methods to defy the norms of justice, unless of course if it is a coup, conducted in the best interests of the nation and to avoid corruption. In those circumstances, retrospective approval may be granted, but the coup maker will have to apply to this court on the basis of a properly constituted PCO, through proper channel, and the court will arrive at its own independent conclusion, following the legal tradition set by Hazrat Umar.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;It is clear as to all students of law that not all PCOs are alike. Some qualify for approval and acceptance by the highest legal authorities and the beneficiaries will go on to become stars in the firmament of national endeavour. Others will be struck down ruthlessly and the petty minions of the conspiring masters will be sent home with a resounding kick on the backside by the august court inspired by the highest regard for the constitution and democracy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;It should also be clear that not all generals are alike. A distinction has to be made in the national interest between those who are in service and thus occupy a special status in the consciousness of the nation and those who are retired and can no longer hold a gun to your head.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;The former do not have to appear in person to account for their nation building activities in Khuzdar, but can send their batman with their footwear for the court to clean and return in good order. The latter will face the full force of the law, till they can exit to Jeddah on a special aircraft, flown in by Prince Muqrin.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Gone are the days when any adventurer could walk in and have his way with the national institutions. We will not allow jumped up politicians to cite obscure laws approved by the colonial British in 1931 to implement financial witchcraft, for the mere reason that they have been elected through an election. They will have to work for the pleasure of the court. We are the guardians of public interest and answerable to ourselves and to the roulette machine in Monte Carlo. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Not like Dar Sahib, who is only answerable to mandarins in Geneva who ask for the reduction of deficit to four per cent, imposition of VAT, reducing subsidies and ending financial loss in public sector corporations. He thinks he is running a government. He is hugely mistaken. We are running the government, the judiciary the legislature and everything that moves except, of course the GHQ who are allowed to run themselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Down, down with the IMF.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-07-27 02:44:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-07-27 02:45:21</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>The-Asylum-Taken-Over-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="7b039a49-82c2-4cb5-9f88-ed104d2e811b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-08-12 05:15:17</date>
      <author>flash player apk</author>
      <email>gregschuster@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.241.213.251</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Expanding business apps onto other platforms can not enable discover to such the large market in contrast to android marketplace. The site takes the career beyond the on the road world.

Also visit my weblog -  flash player apk - http://flashplayerapk.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8435fe0c-e37c-48ac-a8fb-095736dd4fc4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-22 22:00:35</date>
      <author>home insurance comparison shopping</author>
      <email>lula.collett@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.104.169</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Travel insurance comparison in Dubai is a good method to procure the right kind of cover for your travel. It&amp;#39;s best to know who you are dealing with before you agree to any services. It is important for homeowners to be aware of who determines the calculations of depreciation and what method, exactly, is used in determining that rate of depreciation.

My page ::  home insurance comparison shopping - http://74people.ru/DeniceBur </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4fef4605-4ef7-4b72-b951-18b732c5f9ab" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 23:00:23</date>
      <author>home security systems</author>
      <email>karin-dolan@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.241.213.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you think you think failure can only carry to the other good guy you are really wrong. The most important &amp;quot;other guy&amp;quot; can thinking the actual same thing and of him you can be found that &amp;quot;other folk.&amp;quot; You have on the way to protect yourself, your family, your room and business!!
Typically the &amp;quot;infra&amp;quot; part of the name &amp;quot;infrared&amp;quot;, the truth is comes from all the Latin word &amp;quot;infra&amp;quot;, which translates directly into the English word &amp;quot;below&amp;quot;. The good reason that it is use to describe heat radiation, is because inflammed is the color of visible light one longest wavelength.
Are actually many types of safes to find from, but with the objective of safeguarding information or small valuables, determining the size you need must be the most important factor when choosing personal safe. Reduced lock boxes can be ideal for a person who does not website personal information every home, but searching to lock it down a few products and solutions. These cartons can be based and easily out of sight away.
Families get two added installation pieces, one much more tortuous than the other, and both very effective in his or purpose. Incredibly first consider a security alarm tool that running costs less than a major few dollars: that warning sign. ADT gives its customers a window warning as well as a patio or yard sign warning, alerting any nearby potential thieves that the real estate asset is protected according to ADT security, one particular trusted name inside of business. This fact is a good deterrent, but as if audible alarms, is usually no replacement meant for live monitoring.
The individual could do this task on your exclusive and make your own surveillance camera system buying models here and certainly, there. A couple of thoughts just about this. Preliminary of all, our components may not be compatible so you have the fact to worry dealing with.  home security systems honeywell - http://wda2012.vetagro-sup.fr/?q=content/security-systems-residential-home-safe-wireless-security-system-system . And secondly, usually when your family bundle components every single you&amp;#39;re able if you want to get a increased deal from a person particular place.
Make use of a  http://www.securitysystemschicagoinc.com/ - http://www.securitysystemschicagoinc.com/  technique to protect real estate property and family is in fact a smart work. By spending a good solid few dollars, any extra layer out of protection is nestled around property. Installation usually results in a residential owner&amp;#39;s insurance discount, saving money.
Often the famous expression &amp;#39;go ahead and make my day&amp;#39; created by legendary Clint Eastwood formed the cause of so called &amp;#39;make my day laws&amp;#39; and subsequent Citadel Doctrine Law. They are marvelous laws but may vary so much among states that it could be problematic.
Police arrest officials tell us that if a property owner has a footage of a break-in that the chances of catching the crook improve by approximately 50%. That&amp;#39;s huge!</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>