<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Who is Afraid of Ansar Abbasi</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f4%2fExtraordinary+head.jpg" alt="" width="700" height="400" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;em style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Our new generation is being corrupted from the inside. Fifth columnists have infiltrated the Punjab Text Book Board which is being run by the enemies of the ideology of Pakistan. The tree of ideology which was so carefully nurtured by the Shaheed Mustache ul Haq with the help of Tara Masih and brought to ultimate fruition by Syed Drone ul Ummat, Maulana Munawar Hasan, has been hollowed out by no less a person than the Chief Servitor of the masses, the prodigal son of Abbaji, the prodigal husband of three illustrious wives, the builder of the levitating bus, Mian Shehbaz Sharif. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;If only I had not lived to see that day. To replace Allama Iqbal with Firaq Gorakhpuri is an act of treason which should be tried under article 6. One can not imagine a worse crime except giving young children polio drops to make them infertile and prevent mujahids like me being born in future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Nam Dev Mali was no martyr. Any attempt by Maulvi Abdul Haq to present him as one is misguided and doomed to failure. Maulvi Abdul Haq was an Indian agent working under the cover of Anjuman e Taraqqi e Urdu to undermine Islamic cultre and horticulture. If you want to write about martyrs, why not write about Baitullah Mehsud Shaheed or Ilyas Kashmiri Shaheed or Rashid Rauf Shaheed. They were the true guardians of the ideology of Pakistan and fell prey to the infidel Hellfire missile fired by Abu Jehal, Leon bin Panetta. But no, the Text Book Board has no time of the true heroes of Islam.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;We should all unite against this travesty and marching in goose step, reciting the war poetry of TTP, should take a procession to Misri Shah where we should set alight the houses of infidels, put a bullet in the heads of polio workers and save the ideology of Pakistan from annihilation at the hands of Asma Jahangir.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;I am of the opinion that the entire project was ill conceived and doomed from the start. We should not be wasting the precious peninsular riyals on Urdu text books at all. All the school education should be in Arabic so that we can stay on the straight and narrow path. It is a sign of degradation that the PTV is broadcasting news in Balti and Shana. Gone are the days when Abbaji used to watch Al-Anba and not the local languages of jahiliyya.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;The Islamic ideology is on the retreat. If we continue on this ill conceived pathway, there may come a time when not even the returning officers will be able to save it from extinction. My heart is weeping. I am sure that Shaheed Mustache ul Haq is gnashing his lower jaw in anger as he watches infamy descend on the capital of the Republic. As I sit crying at his mausoleum, I have thought of a cunning plan. I will stick a knife in the ribs of every passerby and ask him to recite Dua e Qanoot. That will save Islam. Inshallah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Yours Truly&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Bekar Abbasi&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-04-14 04:01:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-04-14 04:12:27</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Who-is-Afraid-of-Ansar-Abbasi</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="c198211a-df18-4540-ad67-8b015ad90427" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-06-01 07:31:31</date>
      <author>Nike Free Run</author>
      <email>lavondelaney@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.194.25</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever thought about adding a little bit more than just your articles? I mean, what you say is fundamental and everything. However think of if you added some great graphics or video clips to give your posts more, &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot;! Your content is excellent but with images and videos, this site could definitely be one of the very best in its niche. Good blog!

Also visit my web-site:  Nike Free Run - http://ngosummit.com/nike-free-run.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="924ae766-ff3c-49ef-bf19-9c22e8c7bd84" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-06-15 08:35:55</date>
      <author>pompe &amp;#224; chaleur air air</author>
      <email>lizzie_eskridge@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.47.95</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>parlons bien pergola salle &amp;#224; manger le camion pompe chaleur pompe &amp;#224; chaleur air eau  aerothermie - http://www.pompeachaleurdevis.com/  pac air air pompe &amp;#224; chaleur aerothermie vid&amp;#233;o chaleur faire appel incendie travaux   chauffage pompe &amp;#224; chaleur piscine pompes &amp;#224; chaleur l&amp;#39;&amp;#233;t&amp;#233;  ils  pompe &amp;#224; chaleur prix pompe a chaleur geothermie pompes &amp;#224; chaleur fen&amp;#234;tre la plage</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ac0197d9-3561-4dc1-bb08-fd682f9de175" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-24 05:14:56</date>
      <author>Nickolas</author>
      <email>nickolasdelargie@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>91.210.100.185</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>naturally like your web-site however you need to test the spelling on several of your posts. Several of them are rife with spelling problems and I to find it very bothersome to inform the truth then again I&amp;#39;ll surely come again again.

Also visit my webpage; spielautomaten kaufen novoline,  Nickolas - http://www.relaksohuni.com/index.php/blogs/27402/180806/skat-vom-spieltisch-bis-zu-den ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="07fdb4a8-3628-4005-98bb-0dcded6804a4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-14 22:22:09</date>
      <author>Elwood</author>
      <email>elwooddelacruz@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.31.90.69</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Let&amp;#39;s face it, improving health is a priority for most of us enjoy traveling and taking the family to meet up. Taking care of hot tub 50 amp the water from different points of the tub. Light Exercise While exercising with back pain is not something most people are eager to hot tub 50 amp try, there are many more hot springs around. That is why purchasing a hot tub or in dry land. We create those hot tubs which are becoming more and more extras like a waterfall and neck / collar jets.

Here is my weblog: click the following page ( Elwood - http://lobbyproductions.com/galeria/details.php?image_id=1755&amp;amp;sessionid=9f7c5e155552d6f3ea6b457c29a9abc0 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c528c25a-5c02-4a0d-9e80-ba84c149b997" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-18 06:57:11</date>
      <author>sektsteuer</author>
      <email>nestor_mcloud@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>195.78.109.35</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Bei der Milchwirtschaft kommt ein weiteres spezifisches Problem hinzu: In dem Lauf jener Hugo Cocktail Hugo Sekt kette wird n&amp;#228;mlich Milch unterschiedlicher Herkunft stets wieder vermischt. Als im Jahr 1400 von jenen Landesherren Hugo Hugo Sekt Sekt z&amp;#246;lle und Abgaben eingetrieben wurden, l&amp;#246;ste dies bei den Hugo Sekt bauern gro&amp;#223;e Ver&amp;#228;rgerung aus, da jene f&amp;#252;r welche Erzeugung hart arbeiten mussten. Zu lang mit Innovationen in der IT zu lange warten, heisst automatisch verpasste Chancen f&amp;#252;r Kosten- und Fehlerreduktion.

Also visit my web blog  sektsteuer - http://www.scottandcatherine.org/home/brandon-heath-has-announced-a-new-studio-project </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cb41a2f5-179c-44b1-80ca-894ff8ed8fc8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-26 11:35:10</date>
      <author>of ra book</author>
      <email>astridhalley@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>91.210.103.173</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Woah! I&amp;#39;m really enjoying the template/theme of this blog. It&amp;#39;s simple, yet effective. A lot of times it&amp;#39;s hard to get that &amp;quot;perfect balance&amp;quot; between user friendliness and visual appeal. I must say you have done a amazing job with this. Also, the blog loads very fast for me on Chrome. Superb Blog!

My web site  of ra book - http://articles-publisher.com/Wie-Person-Betruegerische-On-Line-Casinos-Im-Im-Netz-Aufspuert.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="22b03ac8-15f4-4e38-add8-0fd2a66af601" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-28 18:28:53</date>
      <author>book of ra kaufen</author>
      <email>reynaldo.sherer@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>195.78.109.27</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings! This is my first visit to your blog! We are a collection of volunteers and starting a new initiative in a community in the same niche. Your blog provided us beneficial information to work on. You have done a extraordinary job!

my website  book of ra kaufen - http://christiangle.com/groups/on-line-casino-jackpots/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="feb7705b-97c1-4f1a-9f9f-8f1e7fbdafa3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-07 02:45:43</date>
      <author>sekt mit erdbeeren</author>
      <email>alycia_humphery@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>62.122.72.54</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Auf die G&amp;#228;rung und jener Hanglage kommt es bei dem Hugo Sekt gut Hugo Cocktail Mosel an. Auch noch immer gilt an diesem ort jener Erfahrungssatz des BGH, wonach ein verst&amp;#228;ndiger Durchschnittsverbraucher in dem Allgemeinen nicht annehmen wird auch, Hugo Sekt da&amp;#223; ein als Nahrungserg&amp;#228;nzungsmittel (Hugo Sekt ) angebotenes Produkt tats&amp;#228;chlich jenes Hugo Sekt  ist, sobald es in jener empfohlenen Dosierung keine pharmakologische Wirkung hatte. Angefangen hat fuer Costers del Si&amp;#243; alles im Jahre 1992, als Hugo Cocktail jener umtriebige Juan de Porcioles und seine Frau Mar&amp;#237;a Buix&amp;#243; jenes Gut in jener N&amp;#228;he jener Stadt Lleida kauften.

Here is my homepage ...  sekt mit erdbeeren - http://coming06.exblog.jp/597293/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="76ebbaa8-53f3-43c5-8839-fbbed0f472c3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-11-30 04:56:40</date>
      <author>sekt cocktail</author>
      <email>paulettebockman@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.254.141.138</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Mit die G&amp;#228;rung und selbst jener Hanglage kommt es bei dem Hugo Sekt gut Hugo Cocktail Mosel an. Jenes verlagseigenes Tier-Forum bietet Anlaufstelle, Austausch die Anregung fuer schreibende die in dem &amp;#187;richtigen Leben&amp;#171; aktive sowie interessierte Tiersch&amp;#252;tzer. Den Nachhaltigkeitspakt von HAKA, der Hugo Cocktail cateringgroup stellen Oberndorfer bringt Gesch&amp;#228;ftsf&amp;#252;hrer Gerhard Hackl auf Prosecco den Punkt: „Was gibts Prosecco Ehrlicheres als sowie in einer ober&amp;#246;sterreichischen K&amp;#252;che das ober&amp;#246;sterreichische IBOSCHHugo Sekt  vom ehrlichen ober&amp;#246;sterreichischen Caterer cateringgroup zubereitet wird.

My site  sekt cocktail - http://www.trisomie21-haute-garonne.org/site/index.php?option=com_lyftenbloggie&amp;amp;view=entry&amp;amp;year=2010&amp;amp;month=04&amp;amp;day=30&amp;amp;id=19%3asommet-des-sessad-de-france-reflexions-et-avenir-&amp;amp;Itemid=91 </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>