<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The Gates of Lahore</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+14.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="400" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Written and researched by Mudassar Bashir&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Translated by Prof Tariq Maqbool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gates of the Walled City of Lahore&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You could not step twice into the same river; for other waters are ever flowing on to you. (Heraclites)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Man is a social animal&amp;rdquo; and can not live alone. Human history shows a constant evolution of different lifestyles as adaptation to the environment is a continual, cultural and learned process. At first, humans started dwelling in caves and forests and they were merely hunter- gatherers. As populations grew, there was an increased demand of food and greater dependence on plants. This led to the independent development of agriculture at different points of human history in different lands particularly near the banks of rivers and streams. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Earlier, the humans settled into small villages and then these villages grew into towns and big cities. Most of these towns and cities were fortified with walls and ditches to defend them from potential aggressors. Walls may only be crossed by appropriate city gates. Initially, these fortifications were simple constructions of wood and earth, which were later replaced by mixed constructions of stones piled on top of each other without mortar. From very early history to modern times, walls have been a near necessity for every city. Uruk in ancient Sumer (Mesopotamia) is world&amp;rsquo;s oldest known walled city. Some settlements in the Indus Valley Civilization were also fortified. By about 3500 B.C., hundreds of small farming villages dotted the Indus floodplain. Many of these settlements had fortifications and planned streets. The stone and mud brick houses of Kot Diji were clustered behind massive stone flood dykes and defensive walls, for neighboring communities quarreled constantly about the control of prime agricultural land. Mundigak (c. 2500 B.C.) in present day south-east Afghanistan has defensive walls and square bastions of sun dried bricks. These walls had gates to control the traffic moving in and out of the cities. Lahore like other ancient cities was fortified by a wall with thirteen gates to control the traffic flow. The gates and wall was first constructed in Mughal King Akbar&amp;rsquo;s times and the fortification was thirty feet high. Later, Maharaja Ranjit Singh reconstructed the fortification but decreased its height to fifteen feet. The city wall was accompanied by the ditches to reinforce the defense system. The ditches were topped up with the mud and gardens were planted around the city in the British period. These gardens were the center of cultural activities such as horse racing, wrestling, classical and folk music playing, kite flying etc. Minarets of the Shahi Mosque, Maharaja Ranjit Singh&amp;rsquo;s Smadhi, the brilliance and magnificence of the Royal Fort and the peaceful flow of the river Ravi along its walls made it a very charming and picturesque place to visit. Our main object is to discuss the gates of Lahore, so we start our discussion with the Delhi Gate and going along the Circular Road, end it on the Akbari Gate. The history, origin, identification and other related topics will be discussed and explored in details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1-Delhi Gate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;The Delhi Gate was once the main entrance to the walled city of Lahore and people mostly coming from the east used to enter the city through this gate. It is named as Delhi gate because of its opening on the highway from Delhi to Lahore. The gate was first built during the Mughal era. On its left, there is famous food grain market &amp;ldquo;Akbari Mandi&amp;rdquo; named after Mughal emperor Akbar. According to an Italian tourist who visited this market in the Mughal era, camels and elephants were commonly used as beasts of burden. It shows it was so big and vast but now it is just the opposite.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 5px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;The Delhi Gate is one of those gates which were reconstructed during British period. The remains of the old gate still exist in depleted and destitute condition known as &amp;ldquo;Chitta Darwaza&amp;rdquo; (white gate). The other buildings attached with the old gate were demolished as well in the British period. Not far from the gate, is famous Mosque Wazir Khan. This mosque was built in the Mughal era and is famous for its engravings on the walls and roof. A few steps from the mosque is the mausoleum of Sayyed Sakhi Suf, a venerable sufi saint. Beside it; there is also the tomb of Imam Gamoon, another sufi saint.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;The upper storey of the gate was used by the government officers and policemen. There used to be a gigantic wooden gate mentioned in many history books which was used to open and close the gate. Although the gate suffered a lot during 1947 riots, it has been renovated and is still a flourishing place. After 1947, the building of the gate and the royal bath adjacent to it were used as a school building. It was also used as a party hall for marriage and religious ceremonies. But now the royal bath is under the custody of the department of archaeology however, the building of the gate is still used as a girls&amp;rsquo; school. Interior of the gate is dome shaped but the roof is plain and even. The entrance is bordered by windows and doors of the neighbouring houses. On top of the windows, there are nests of pigeons, a characteristic feature of the old city&amp;rsquo;s life. Lower and ground floors are occupied by the janitors and attendants. Some rooms are under the custody of the health department. At the entrance, on both sides of the gate, there are shops and movable wheel barrow shops. They sell food stuff such as vegetables, fruits, ghee, oil and other items of daily use such as detergent powder, soap and shoes etc., Bangles, artificial jewelry, anklets, bracelets, earrings, lockets, necklaces and other metal ornaments are sold on the wheel barrow shops. From Delhi Gate to Chitta Darwaza, there are so many shops selling a variety of things. Under the Chitta Darwaza, there are people selling rosaries and caps on the bicycles. The bullock carts, the donkey carts, horse coaches, the wheel barrows and the labourers etc that the twenty first century is still centuries away from this place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;2- Zaki Gate alias Yakki Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is named after a celebrated saint Pir Zaki. As the sound of letter &amp;ldquo;z&amp;rdquo; (zee) is interchangeable with the letter &amp;ldquo;Y&amp;rdquo; (Ya) with the passage of time it becomes Yakki Gate instead of Zaki Gate. The gate has been demolished during British period due to its depleted and exhausted condition but the grave of Pir Zaki along with some other graves still exist there. There is no historical background about these graves and their origin but only legendary stories. The legend goes on like this that Pir Zaki and his followers or disciples died fighting against the Mongol invaders. It further adds that even after Pir Zaki was beheaded, his headless body kept on fighting for a few metres or so. Therefore, the head and body were buried in different graves. His burial chamber is a few steps from the city and in front of it there is a famous mosque &amp;ldquo;Madina Mosque&amp;rdquo;. A few step s away, there is a government hospital and a police station.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3-Khizri Gate or Sheranwala Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;There are two traditions about the origin of this gate&amp;rsquo;s name. According to the one, it is named after Khawaja Khizar (A.S) whose name is associated with waters, rivers, seas, boats and navigation. As the river Ravi used to flow very close to this gate by the side of the walled city and the tomb of Pir Balawal Shah and the Bara Dari of Sher Singh was not far from it where the river was navigated by boats and small ships, so it was named Khizri gate. There is a Khizri Muhallah (neighborhood) just after crossing this gate which supports this old tradition. Another tradition about the origin of its name as Sheranwala gate is that In the times of Maharaja Ranjit Singh, two lions in the cage were placed beside the gate and the guards had to take care of them as well as the gate. It was then that it was named as Sheranwala gate due to its association with the lions. When the British took over, they removed the lions the carved images of the lions on both sides of the upper floor remained and are reminiscent of Ranjit Singh&amp;rsquo;s times.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is on the road leading from Lahore Railway Station to Pakistan Monument (Yadgar‐i‐Pakistan). After crossing Ek Moria Bridge, on the left side, there is a government hospital along the waterway and the newly rehabilitated wall of the old city. Along the wall, there is a garden which used to be a ditch filled with mud during British period. Not far from the hospital, there is a mosque called Sheranwala mosque or Jamia Masjid Ghausia. On the left of the mosque, there is the tomb of Molana AbdulQayum. The road coming down from the gate is very steep and is known as Sheranwala Ghatti and same is the case with the gates lying next to it. This gives support to the assumption that these gates were built so high because of the vicinity of the river Ravi.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;A new gate was built in 1990&amp;rsquo;s and a few steps away from it, stands the old gate. There are old wooden pieces attached to it and the small rooms in the interior are used as warehouse by the shopkeepers. There is an old school beside the gate which was established in 1889. Many celebrities graduated from this school and one of them is the famous classical singer Ustad Aziz‐ud‐Din. A little far from the school is the mosque associated with Molana Ahmad Ali Lahori. A few steps from this mosque, there are reminiscent of the old gate with the craved lions on its upper storey. There is a wooden tablet down under on which the words, &amp;ldquo;Katri Babu&amp;rdquo; are engraved. The remains of this Katri or Haveli are still there with its depleted doors, windows, balconies showing the nice woodwork and telling many untold stories of this transient world. Under the gate, there is a small tea shop and the smoke rising from its stove has badly affected the ceiling of the gate. There is a small market or bazaar and the neighbourhood is called Khizri Muhallah reminding the old name of this gate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4-Kashmiri Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;The "Kashmiri Gate" is so named because it faces the direction of Kashmir. It is one of the gates reconstructed by the British and its old style was not transformed. Like Sheranwala Gate it is linked with the reconstructed wall of Lahore&amp;rsquo;s old city. A steep path constructed with Nanak Shahi bricks leads to the main road passing by. This steep path is known as Kashmiri Ghatti (pass). There are remains of the old wall reconstructed in Ranjit Singh&amp;rsquo;s times accompanied by some depleted buildings with their dilapidated doors and balconies standing as a proof to the indifferent attitude of authorities toward this historical heritage. Kashmiri Gate still has wooden door valves and arches. Like other gates, the interior of this gate has many shops. There are tea and juice stalls after crossing the gate. Left side of the road is used as parking by the traders of nearby markets. Then there is a girls school established in an old haveli which is under construction now-a &amp;ndash;days. Nobody has any information about this haveli but in some history books it is mentioned as &amp;ldquo;Haveli Rani Gul Begum&amp;rsquo;. It is named after one of the wives of Maharaja Ranjit Singh who used to live in this place after her marriage with Maharaja.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5-Masti Gate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;There are two traditions about the origin of this gate&amp;rsquo;s name. One traditions says that it is named after a royal guard Masti Baloch who performed his duties with great dedication and commitment. According to another tradition which is more plausible, its original name is Masiti Gate (Masit is for mosque in Punjabi) which was distorted into Masti Gate as a few yards from the gate stands &amp;ldquo;Begum Shahi Mosque&amp;rdquo; of Mughal era. It was destroyed during British period due to its deteriorated condition and a comparatively small doorway was built. But now there exists neither the gate nor the doorway. There is a two feet wide and five feet high pillar on the extreme left of the road unnoticeable among the shops; the sole remain of this gate. A steep path known as Masti Ghatti (slope) goes down to link it with the main road. After crossing the gate, the street leads to the Chune Mandi where there is a historic Sikh temple named after their fourth Guru Ramdas. Along the steep path, there is mushroom growth of the market places eclipsing the whole beauty of the wall and the gardens around it. There are vendors, hawkers, traffickers selling edible items moving around here and there. Just opposite the gate, the neighbourhood is known as Badami Bagh but there is no trace of any garden except the iron market sprawling all around there. On the left side of the Masti Ghatti(slope) ,there is the building of Masti Gate police station.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;6-Roshnai Gate alias Hazoori Bagh Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is known as Roshnai Gate because of its association with the lights. The western side of the Lahore Fort was housed by the courtiers and the elite class and they set alight their havelis and houses with lamps and lanterns by the royal decree soon after the sunset. As it was more illuminated compared to other gates, so it was known as Roshnai Gate. It is along the western wall of the fort. It was used as a main entrance to the fort by the courtiers and other dignitaries till the times of Ranjit Singh.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Hazoori Bagh that lies between the fort and the Royal (Badshahi) Mosque is in proximity to this gate. People started calling it Hazoori Bagh Gate after the independence of Pakistan. It looks like part of the fort as revealed by the style of its construction. This gate can be approached either by the high road opposite to the Iqbal Park (Yadgar-i-Pakistan) that leads to the Royal Mosque. The second approach is from the road besides the Lady Wellingdon Hospital going side by side with the wall of the Royal Mosque leading to a garden where the Roshnai Gate stands reminding us its past glory. There used to be a cannon beside this gate till 1990&amp;rsquo;s but it is no more there and nobody has any idea about its whereabouts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7-Taxali Gate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Unfortunately, it is one of those gates which have been completely lost and exist only in name. This gate was called Taxali because there used to be a mint (Taxal in the local language) in the Mughal era. That mint has also met the same fate and nothing is left there but the old Taxali mosque still survives. On the left of the road leading from Pakistan Monument to Data Darbar, there is a slope path. This slope bifurcates into two paths, one leading to Roshnai Gate and other leading to Taxali Gate. The building of the Taxali Gate had been completely lost since long but the old bazaar along it still survives. In the beginning, there is ever close Ustad Daman&amp;rsquo;s Academy which used to be the sitting place of well known Punjabi poet &amp;ldquo;Ustad Daman&amp;rdquo;. Interestingly, in the times of Akbar, the great Mughal King, one of the greats of Punjabi poetry, &amp;ldquo;Shah Hussein&amp;rdquo; used to live in the same one room house. A little away, there are a lot of tea stalls, tea shops and Pan shops. Beside them, there is a big shoe market. These shops sell traditional embroidered and fancy shoes and sandals. This bazaar is the part of the notorious, &amp;ldquo;Heera Mandi&amp;rdquo;. The buildings above the shops are housed by the dancing girls who are sex workers running their business under the cover of singing and dancing. A little further from the bazaar, there is &amp;ldquo;Novelty Cinema&amp;rdquo; and not far from it, there used to be the building of &amp;ldquo;Aziz Theatre&amp;rdquo; but theatre has no place at such a place now. There are many food stalls and restaurants there as well. A little away from these restaurants, there is a market where musical instruments are sold and repaired. Close by is the building of Tibbi police station. There used to be two bazaars even after the partition known as &amp;ldquo;Do Rupiah&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Punj Rupiah&amp;rdquo; bazaars but they are completely lost and survive only in history books. Not far is the building for the healthcare of women of this area. May be it provides them medical care but who cares about their spiritual and mental health which has long been buried alongside this gate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;8-Bhatti Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is named after the people inhabiting this area earlier in the history. They belong to the caste &amp;ldquo;Bhatt&amp;rdquo; so the gate was known as Bhatti Gate. At present, none of the Bhatt people live there. To the southwest of this gate, there is the mausoleum of &amp;ldquo;Hazrat Ali Hajveri alias Ganj Bakhsh&amp;rdquo; and this is one of the reminiscent of &amp;ldquo;Ghazanavid Period&amp;rdquo;. A road from this gate leads straight to Badshahi Mosque and alongside it, there are many Havelis which have are not in their real shape and housed by many families who have no idea about their historic background.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;In front of the Bhatti Gate, the road is very crowded as there is bus stop, wagon stop, and motorcycle rickshaw stop spreading noise, smoke all around making it hard to see the clear sky even in the broad daylight. This pollution has taken away all the beauty and glory of the place and has metamorphosed it into one of the ugliest spots in the city. There are shops along the bus stop where people can buy and sell birds of different kinds.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Bhatti Gate was reconstructed by the British and its old building stands near the open drain. The Bhatti Gate police station building is next to the old building of the gate. The gate still has wooden arches which have lost all their beauty after being painted green very badly. A few steps from the gate, there is a decaying house. This house has a historical significance as the great poet, &amp;ldquo;Allama Muhammad Iqbal&amp;rdquo; lived in this house for more than one year but nobody has shown any interest to preserve it. A little further away, there is Justice Latif&amp;rsquo;s Muhallah (locality). Justice Abdul Latif who wrote the famous book &amp;ldquo;History of Lahore&amp;rdquo; used to live at that place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;There are many food stalls and other items for sale in the shops surrounding the gate. The road leads to &amp;ldquo;Bazaar Hakimaan&amp;rdquo; where there is no more any Hakim (physician) as the place used to be teemeing with physicians of high caliber in the past. Their prescriptions were buried along the other arts and sciences of the past and nobody has any idea about the research they did and the medicines they used to treat all kinds of diseases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;9-Mori Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 10px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;It is the smallest among all the gates of Lahore. According to one tradition, this gate was built by Malik Ayaz when he conquered Lahore in Mahmud of Gazna&amp;rsquo;s times. But another tradition which is more reliable tells us that it was used as sewerage when the Sikhs ruled Lahore. All kinds of waste and garbage were thrown out of the city through the sewerage passing through this gate. The sewerage was connected to all other sewers in the city. As the word &amp;ldquo;mori&amp;rsquo; in Punjabi means sewer so this gate was known as &amp;ldquo;Mori Gate&amp;rdquo;. British didn&amp;rsquo;t take any step to reconstruct it and it was left in a decaying state and with the passage of time, this gate was completely lost in history. The sewerage still exist and there are always heaps of garbage and trash outside this gate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10-Lahori Gate or Lohari Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;It is considered to be one of the earliest&amp;nbsp; gates in Lahore. In the early part of 11th century, the city was badly affected by the wars between Mahmud of Ghazna and Raja Jai Pal. At one time, it was even uninhabited. When Malik Ayaz was appointed viceroy of North India, he made Lahore, the seat of government. It is at that time, that the people started inhabiting the city particularly this part of the city and this gate was known as Lahori Gate since then. It was rebuilt in British period with small bricks in the same old style. The rooms were built in the upper storey for officials. It has same wooden arches found in other old gates of Lahore. Coming from Mori Gate, on the left, near the entrance to this gate, there is Muslim Masjid (mosque) named after renowned muslim scholar Molana Muhammad Bakhsh Muslim. Across the road, there is famous Anarkali Bazaar. There are shops under the mosque. On the corner of the bazaar, leading to the gate, there is a flower shop selling different kind of fresh flowers like red roses, jasmine etc, A few steps away, there is the building of Lahori Gate with a slab showing the details of reconstruction of this gate in Hindi and English languages. There are old and heavy arches and they give the door a look of some old entrance to a fort. Like other gates of Lahore, there are many food stalls, tea shops and other eating places. After passing through the gate, there are shops of bone setters and herbalists practicing their centuries old art. Next to them, there are some shops selling items associated with old culture and living style like Hookah, mats, tobacco and jute to weave fibres for the cots and there are shops selling clay pots and utensils reminding the old culture of this part of the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11-SHAH ALAM GATE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate does not exist anymore as it was completely destroyed in the riots of 1947. It was the second gate named after a Moghul king; it was named after King Bahadur Shah Alam Shah I who succeeded to the throne after the death of his father King Aurang Zeb. He shifted his capital from Delhi to Lahore to crush the Sikh rebellion. He died in Lahore and this gate was named after him. It was reconstructed during British period with utmost care to keep its old look and glory intact. This gate was situated between Lohari gate and Mochi gate on the southern side of the city. Going from Lohari gate to Mochi gate, there is a square called Shahalmi Chowk, the lone proof of its existence there once. There was also a Hindu temple known as &amp;ldquo;Shahalmi Mandir.&amp;rdquo; The real name of the temple was Ratan Chand temple and inside it there was a magnificent pond. This temple along with the pond was also destroyed and there are no remains of the gate or the temple there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;After independence, the remains of the gate were destroyed completely and a double roadway was constructed linking the mazy and labyrinthine streets and marketplaces such as Azam Cloth market to other parts of the city. This led to further destruction of the old city and its culture as it prompted the construction of tall buildings and shopping malls and plazas in place of havelis and old houses. As T.S. ELIOT says,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;What we call the beginning is often the end&amp;rdquo; (Little Gidding V)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 24px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;12-Moti Gate or Mochi Gate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is next to Shah Alam Gate. Its old name is Moti Gate which is distorted into Mochi Gate. In the times of great Mughal King Akbar, the person who kept watch over this gate, his name was Moti Ram. He performed his duties diligently and devotedly and this gate was named after him. This gate was completely pulled down during the British period and was never built again. The British established a garden beside the road which has been the scene of many historical meetings and processions held by different political parties and other groups. In the beginning, there is the building of Mochi Gate surrounded by the shops selling fireworks and other dangerous explosives. Many accidents have taken place there due to these explosive materials but the authorities never took any serious steps to guarantee the safety of life in the surrounding area. A few steps away, there is a &amp;ldquo;Khoya Bazaar&amp;rdquo; on the left and the mosque of &amp;ldquo;Mullah Muhammad Saleh Kamboh&amp;rdquo;. Next to the mosques, there are shops of kites and kite flying materials. There are also shops of kebabs and sweets. Beside these shops, there is &amp;ldquo;Muhallah Sadakaraan&amp;rdquo; where one of the great classical singers of the subcontinent&amp;rdquo;Ustad Chote Ghulam Ali Khan&amp;rdquo; used to live. It is unfortunate that most of the people have no idea about him and his art and it is a forgotten chapter of history like the magnificence and glory of this city.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline; letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13-AKBARI GATE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; min-height: 22px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;This gate is named after the Mughal King Jalal-ud-Din Akbar. This gate and the food grain market inside both are named after Akbar. During British Raj, it was reconstructed and the glory was restored . Unfortunately , after the independence, it was demolished and only the inn attached to it was left. The walls of the inn were attached with those of the gate but there is no sign of the gate now. This gate is between Delhi gate and Mochi gate lying on the eastern wall of the old Lahore city. Coming from old Crown Bus Stand to Akbari Police station, it used to stand on the left side of the road. The present police station is housed in the old building of the inn attached to the gate. There is a road leading to the Akbari food grain market. A little further, on the left , a road leads to the Delhi Gate. It is one of the busiest marketplaces in Lahore. There are shops of all kinds of food grains like wheat, rice, lentils, jams, marmalade, and herbs of all kinds. Different modes of transportation are operational here, the old ones with the new ones. There are horse, mule, and donkey driven carts along&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: verdana, geneva; font-size: large;"&gt;Please see below, views of Lohari Gate:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+1.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+2.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+3.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+4.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+5.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+6.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+7.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+8.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+9.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+10.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+11.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+12.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+13.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+14.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+15.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+16.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f6%2fGates+17.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-04-21 12:29:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-06-01 13:49:45</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>4</rating>
  <slug>-Gates-of-the-Walled-City-of-Lahore-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="051c4f3d-efe7-4e20-aec1-ffcdf00d299b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-05-11 01:35:19</date>
      <author>hallen</author>
      <email>zoyismith@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>cn</country>
      <ip>125.77.179.131</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Proper protection for a new smartphone is a must. After all, you have spent $500-$600 to buy a new device that can fit in your pocket but has functions of a powerful PC. Sure, you do not want to scratch it. Perhaps, you have seen lots of leather case for Iphone 4s lots with phones having cracked screens and numerous scuffs. If you do not want to sell your cell phone on http://www.ebulkdirect.com/cover-case-handy-tasche-for-blackberry-z10-p-660.html at a ridiculous price (nobody wants to buy used smartphones at high prices) you should already be looking for a good protective case. leather card case are not just accessories that contribute to your style. The main reason why people buy cover cases it to protect their devices from wear, scuffs and scratches. Gone are the days when you put your old Nokia to any jeans pocket without being worried of possible scuff marks and other damages. Even minor scratches on the screen can make a smartphone barely usable, since these devices are used to watch videos and for Internet surfing. http://www.ebulkdirect.com/   Edges of the phones body are also vulnerable spots. So, a case will give a maximum protection without spoiling the phone&amp;#39;s look. Luckily, today&amp;#39;s markets offer a variety of options in terms of design and materials. Here are a few tips and considerations for buyers looking for good quality, durable and reasonably priced cell phone cases. Leather versus silicone cases and rubberized plastic. Yes, leather looks and feels great. A leather case will perfectly fit a new iPhone 5 or Samsung Galaxy S III. This is a great choice for business people http://www.ebulkdirect.com/tpu-silicone-case-tasche-for-huawei-ascend-g300-u8818-p-532.html, managers and consultants. Silicone and rubberized plastic are great and durable materials. Besides, all possible colors are available. It is difficult to recommend particular materials. Some people can&amp;#39;t stand silicone and enjoy holding a genuine leather ipad cases , while others purchase 7 multicolored silicone cases and use a different case every day.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3f8d450a-ae5c-4d3f-8f4c-a6523028ab9b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-05-29 18:17:52</date>
      <author>raihan</author>
      <email>mystyle@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>117.18.231.42</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>thanks for unique post. hope it will be running. from this i learn manythings</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe5cd7f7-23b3-45ac-8d5a-9b3f7ece782f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-06-06 18:35:33</date>
      <author>Raihan</author>
      <email>mystyle825@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>117.18.231.41</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>good comment. this post  i read again and again.
&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.alherabd.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;laen many more&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8e1d8776-ae4c-4cd1-bfb7-26775619458f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-07-26 04:53:47</date>
      <author>bobby genovese</author>
      <email>isiah.brownell@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.27.246.123</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, that&amp;#39;s what I was exploring for, what a information! present here at this weblog, thanks admin of this website.

Review my page:  bobby genovese - http://www.finanznachrichten.de/nachrichten-2013-07/27499961-bobby-genovese-named-best-online-entrepreneur-008.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="61229caf-5bcd-4c69-9145-168b4d88dea4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 11:31:06</date>
      <author>mitto 2</author>
      <email>arethatyner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.100.93</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you for the good writeup. It in fact was a amusement account it. Look advanced to more added agreeable from you! By the way, how could we communicate?

Also visit my web-site:  mitto 2 - http://bft-mitto.livejournal.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f35d37ac-dd70-4435-9a2f-c0633fc31a4d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 17:51:59</date>
      <author>Best CV Templates</author>
      <email>mystyle825@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>117.18.231.39</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>what a good post .really this is not good but true.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6b37155b-dd08-4e21-bc0f-bffcaf156134" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 10:23:03</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>ismaelsommers@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there! This is kind of off topic but I need some advice from an established blog. Is it hard to set up your own blog? I&amp;#39;m not very techincal but I can figure things out pretty quick. I&amp;#39;m thinking about creating my own but I&amp;#39;m not sure where to begin. Do you have any points or suggestions?  Thanks

My website;  homepage - http://theplumbingdoctor.net//home </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="661a6da0-554f-4316-a28d-2f2dfd4c7228" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 22:00:49</date>
      <author>free samples</author>
      <email>paulette.connolly@hailmail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.241.213.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Some ask at credit card answers and such appropriate information. One of the many best elements belonging to the proper marketing crossstitching for a restaurant, at least on the web is to start making a customer list that you can start e-mailing.

Feel free to visit my webpage -  free samples - http://freesamplesreal.co.uk/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6deedac9-a056-451a-b7f5-861a6fa276bd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-14 23:30:35</date>
      <author>nyc real estate litigation lawyer</author>
      <email>raphaelcowart@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.27.246.123</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I could not resist commenting. Perfectly written!

Feel free to visit my blog post  nyc real estate litigation lawyer - http://nashvillecarpetcleaners.us/nycrealestatelitigationlawyer </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c7626dcb-67af-495c-9835-f3ede5e2d0cf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 10:53:46</date>
      <author>tattoo kit</author>
      <email>theresastump@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Here is my blog post:  tattoo kit - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8b78bb06-9673-460f-8cd9-e333f0b4f6c7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 15:45:11</date>
      <author>free samples</author>
      <email>barbra_vinson@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.241.213.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Selection products is an outstanding way to try something while not having having to have it. My most traditional idea to do which is to direct contact the manufacturer behind the product openly.

Also visit my web-site ::  free samples - http://freesamplesreal.co.uk/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3529f0f3-1c06-47d0-ad92-7ff7c3d38e41" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 03:02:04</date>
      <author>tattoo kit</author>
      <email>kazukochristiansen@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Feel free to visit my homepage  tattoo kit - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="81561d26-9563-4a0d-bda4-048fb297dcdc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-23 17:48:45</date>
      <author>Ghd MK4 Kiss Styler</author>
      <email>gordonnorris@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.165.254.150</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>With havin so much written content do you ever run into any problems of plagorism or copyright infringement? My blog has a lot of unique content I&amp;#39;ve either created myself or outsourced but it appears a lot of it is popping it up all over the web without my permission. Do you know any solutions to help prevent content from being ripped off? I&amp;#39;d certainly appreciate it.

my blog ...  Ghd MK4 Kiss Styler - http://www.jmax.co.uk/low-price-ghd-mk4-kiss-styler.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="34141f26-4954-4885-b7f1-500a399ad66a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-24 01:58:39</date>
      <author>Ghd Peacock Blue</author>
      <email>reginaloveless@veryfast.biz</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.59.18</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Amazing! Its truly remarkable post, I have got much clear idea regarding from this article.

Here is my blog ...  Ghd Peacock Blue - http://www.nrsas.co.uk/cheap-ghd-peacock-blue-original.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d19177bc-0149-4489-8cbe-3a0c24969e51" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 13:37:40</date>
      <author>tattoo kit</author>
      <email>florenceforeman@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.174.194.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>this site is ugly

Also visit my web blog;  tattoo kit - http://www.tattoodiy.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f7f757f4-8ff5-440a-8ae9-1c8eff97c617" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 18:50:01</date>
      <author>nyc construction law firm</author>
      <email>mohammadholloman@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.221</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Asking questions are truly pleasant thing if you are not understanding something fully, however this piece of writing provides nice understanding even.

My webpage  nyc construction law firm - http://nashvillecarpetcleaners.us/nycconstructionlawfirm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="42f87126-d783-4263-a193-add639789cfe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-05 01:07:59</date>
      <author>Nike Air Max UK</author>
      <email>betsyyanez@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.165.255.35</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>After I originally commented I appear to have clicked on the -Notify me when new comments are added- checkbox and from now on whenever a comment is added I get four emails with the same comment. Perhaps there is a way you can remove me from that service? Thanks a lot!

Look at my weblog ...  Nike Air Max UK - http://www.hb6.co.uk/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="09165ec9-8038-4179-ba45-327faf0c0989" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-09 17:38:48</date>
      <author>buy backlinks</author>
      <email>eloise-edward@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.241.213.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Now that you received some ideas how to market around low budget generally are for certain millions of  ways. Incorporate them, accept inability but stay focused! You would be playing a exercise and don&amp;#39;t wan to lose!
Participating on social multimedia sites is a related strategy but should be done correctly.  buy backlinks - http://stockbacklinks.com/  are best not included inside your feeds or Website profile boxes. A link can be added in almost bio boxes to achieve a backlink. By syndicating your writing you most likely will earn backlinks upon updates to internet feeds through this RSS aggregators.
To example, the many kinds of search engines learn that people feedback on blogs as well forums for all purpose of and produce links, which means that you cannot provide too much extra weight to these. Will have, as even more thus today with unquestionably the social fat. But the remark must contribute articles and other content associated with that topic in challenge. They work for those remarks that the majority of state &amp;quot;congratulations, this post very good&amp;quot;, and leave those link. You should add content material material with the truly comment.
Site link Limit:When you are exchanging links confirm the external backlinks on that pages. If the number is together to 60 most people can take link, but if it exceeds this total number your link will have much value. Another matter is when someone are posting review articles on blog coupled with you see wihtout a doubt 100&amp;#39;s of comments on the post, then there is not much aspect in taking tie from such a good solid page. If the other links are spam your own personal website can also be considered junk posts. This comment on good blogs which widely check comments before posting and put emphasis on quality. You can recognize such blogs for the reason that they will carry limited i.e. up to 9 or 8 good comments on their posts.
Over are the era of link spamming. Google&amp;#39;s algorithm has changed considerable in will establish 5 years. Google continually aims to deliver incredibly best search results on the end user acquiring this, Google&amp;#39;s screens are always ever-changing to provide seo qualified sites that relates to the search topic. For example, if i typed in the most important keyword &amp;quot;dog grooming&amp;quot; into Google, I&amp;#39;d expect to locate a site about &amp;quot;dog grooming&amp;quot;. Just?
You should also use &amp;#39;Visit our team to find more about crazy dogs&amp;#39; with regard to anchor text. To find the websites backlinking to running and what written is being use to link to ones own website, you may use this free resource backlinkcheck. If you find a site is actually linking to your website, but is not using a suitable anchor text, down the road . contact the weblog owner if easy to modify it. This will with any luck boost your article rank score.
You might want to remember that target is to perform your business a irreproachable way. Research everything as well as assume anything. Question the viability of every thing that you encounter. There are many sharks that operate on the world wide web. They will use each and every ploy to get your money and defraud you.  backlinks tracker - http://jetso.2hea.com/node/325 . You need to be careful and make use of common sense. If you perhaps may be careful and righteous, you will take the path confidently and success is actually going to yours.
One obvious way to build links to your website is to exchange website links with other world-wide-web sites. As much as anything is, this might be described as a traditional form towards web site promotion. Exchanging links is however moment in time consuming, since you ought to spend time where to locate sites to exchange links with, and also you must then developed the links while monitor them on an ongoing basis. Another disadvantage every single exchanging links, is simply of course you just are not primarily links coming according to your site, shoppers also linking to, and sending potential customers to, other net websites.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="398d8fba-254f-488c-8182-423f07bb9cf2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-09 21:15:05</date>
      <author>nyc construction law firm</author>
      <email>cruz-avery@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.140</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Write more, thats all I have to say. Literally, it seems as though you relied on the video to make your point. You definitely know what youre talking about, why waste your intelligence on just posting videos to your site when you could be giving us something informative to read?

Also visit my blog ...  nyc construction law firm - http://nashvillecarpetcleaners.us/nycconstructionlawfirm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0c86b619-7569-4451-90ab-2c1685eff06b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-10 23:50:24</date>
      <author>Ray Ban 2140</author>
      <email>maryloustorm@mailftp.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.165.255.35</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure why but this blog is loading extremely slow for me. Is anyone else having this problem or is it a issue on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later on and see if the problem still exists.

Take a look at my web site ::  Ray Ban 2140 - http://www.ziana.org/ray-ban-2140.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e5369864-aae3-40e7-a5db-4299e399c52e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-12 17:24:09</date>
      <author>Cheap Christian Louboutin Pumps</author>
      <email>tatiana-vo@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>37.187.88.143</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I rarely drop comments, however i did some searching and wound up here Justice Denied | The Gates of Lahore. And I do have a few questions for you if you usually do not mind. Is it only me or does it seem like a few of the comments look like they are coming from brain dead folks? :-P And, if you are posting on other social sites, I&amp;#39;d like to follow everything new you have to post. Could you make a list of every one of all your public pages like your linkedin profile, Facebook page or twitter feed?

Also visit my site ...  Cheap Christian Louboutin Pumps - http://www.erton.org/christian-louboutin-pumps.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="47d4b7f4-83e5-43ce-bfd8-f4143c7bc70c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-13 03:04:06</date>
      <author>nyc business lawyer</author>
      <email>armando.bevins@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.51.117</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s genuinely very complex in this busy life to listen news on Television, so I only use the web for that reason, and obtain the most recent news.

my site  nyc business lawyer - http://nashvillecarpetcleaners.us/nycbusinesslawyer </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="afa7e27e-8faa-450a-83d4-55693b98d1ed" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 02:52:45</date>
      <author>Escort Agencies In Trumbull</author>
      <email>domenic.rizzo@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.151.183</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wonderful goods from you, man. I&amp;#39;ve understand your stuff previous to and you are just extremely excellent. I actually like what you have acquired here, certainly like what you&amp;#39;re stating and the way in which you say it. You make it entertaining and you still take care of to keep it wise. I can&amp;#39;t wait to read far more from you. This is actually a tremendous website.

Here is my blog;  Escort Agencies In Trumbull - http://www.purevolume.com/wilburnheldyislwe/posts/4636077/Patchogue+HighlandsNew+York+escorts+%7C+Call+%28800%29+437-6579 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f3ac210e-9118-452a-a83e-6afea5aa2adc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-23 22:01:11</date>
      <author>Sanjed Ahned Zakir</author>
      <email>zakir@eapparelsource.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>180.149.7.202</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>great thesis </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f4800562-3273-4917-a376-5b025a8c8dfa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-27 23:15:44</date>
      <author>Ermelinda</author>
      <email>ermelinda.lynch@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.104.237</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>There are several types of hot tub covers are the hot tubs spring tx plastic ones which might leak at times. Usually this happens just outside of the warranty! Like wise this cost cutting or simply trying to make a Hot Tub in Spain there is a broad portfolio of tubs to choose from, which can harm hot tubs. Even if the water is clean and sterile, the tubs will not be able to assimilate information relating to the different designs, styles and materials used.

my page; click through the next article ( Ermelinda - http://Wiki.ustea.org/index.php/Useful_Concepts_-_Basic_Advice_On_Smart_Hot_Tub_For_Sale_Tactics )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4841a211-616d-47df-848a-2de44894d3fe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-03-01 17:14:17</date>
      <author>medicamentos</author>
      <email>lancepenman@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.105.56.5</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>We stumbled over here by a different web address and thought I might check things out. I like what I see so now i&amp;#39;m following you. Look forward to looking over your web page for a second time.  Also visit my web site  medicamentos - http://g-s.us/como-controlar-ansiedad58721 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c8002d1b-ec9b-47c6-9199-a0b204decfd3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-04-12 05:22:05</date>
      <author>Trucos</author>
      <email>silvestredelrio@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>158.222.2.108</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>﻿ Esperaba este titulo con considerables ansias y sin embargo constituye provechoso, despues de todo es realmente cansino  Comprueba y puedes visita mi web siteOo  Trucos - http://www.paperjourney.com/__media__/js/netsoltrademark.php?d=trucoteca.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="85b80b06-27ec-46b2-ae80-a2b3b13f4c99" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-17 22:13:10</date>
      <author>landscaping conroe tx</author>
      <email>moseslemos@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.241.106.80</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You actually make it appear really easy with your presentation but I find this topic to be actually one thing that I believe I would never understand. It kind of feels too complicated and very extensive for me. I am having a look forward in your next post, I will attempt to get the grasp of it!  Also visit my web page -  landscaping conroe tx - https://www.txlanddesign.com/wp-content/themes/Divi/epanel/shortcodes/css/shortcodes.css?ver=3.0.45 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8204e66b-7fef-4cd8-bc05-0defdeb0168b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-27 18:00:05</date>
      <author>Trucos y guias</author>
      <email>josepomer@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.3.25.211</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>﻿Que pasada!! Unos muy bien dichos puntos de vista! Sinceramente seria muy bueno que tu subieras mas articulos ademas  casi todos los escritos  de la site es muy util.  Mira lo siguiente y navega por mi website-  Trucos y guias - http://asmez.halley.it/c064056/mc/mc_gridev_messi.php?x=0f8376207cee1e3771177176ce7105ee&amp;amp;servizio=&amp;amp;bck=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.trucoteca.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0b7bb42f-daf1-4118-9fc4-f7b727dc8eb9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-27 22:29:47</date>
      <author>instantly buy bitcoin</author>
      <email>helene.whitelaw@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.241.106.80</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Please let me know if you&amp;#39;re looking for a writer for your blog. You have some really good articles and I think I would be a good asset. If you ever want to take some of the load off, I&amp;#39;d really like to write some material for your blog in exchange for a link back to mine. Please shoot me an email if interested. Thanks!  Check out my web blog  instantly buy bitcoin - http://www.instantlybuybitcoin.com/how-to-buy-bitcoins/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="39693127-f7e1-442e-b429-e4eb0644b8b2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-31 13:45:34</date>
      <author>enlace</author>
      <email>agustinhumphrey@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.175.33.13</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>﻿ No yo pienso que el titulo sea tan alucinante como dicen, si no que es entretenido  Comprueba y puedes navega por mi webXD  enlace - http://justjewelers.com/__media__/js/netsoltrademark.php?d=trucoteca.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="167bda27-a585-4c5a-86c6-ff04a725b061" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-12 17:23:17</date>
      <author>free std testing syracuse new york</author>
      <email>santobuntine@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>191.101.72.174</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Bear in mind, many STDs have no signs or symptoms.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1894bfc-7552-4f5b-b73f-ec8678d52c0e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-20 16:15:37</date>
      <author>free std testing herpes</author>
      <email>dorisbarry@mymacmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>104.160.18.161</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In fact, common testing is very advisable.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="794c84ba-e72a-48a9-b5d9-d07836f49768" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-25 04:08:14</date>
      <author>std testing tennessee</author>
      <email>clarissanewdegate@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>109.230.203.178</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Our 10-Take a look at Panel will check for all major STDs.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d7e2a4ed-4eb4-4e7e-850e-e120aca35d05" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-05 20:10:43</date>
      <author>std testing round rock</author>
      <email>lesliedge@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>104.160.18.140</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Please call to substantiate when testing is offered.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="49b02953-c46f-4be0-b7fb-555d9963e42a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-28 01:44:29</date>
      <author>bookkeeping</author>
      <email>mariaduterrau@zoho.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>104.160.18.162</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Say goodbye to tedious books and ledgers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="45fdb61a-dfd8-44df-a886-99dd124446d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-11-13 00:14:46</date>
      <author>Michael</author>
      <email>jetta.bedard@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.215.221.98</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Really quite a lot of helpful information!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7f7ca0f6-871d-4e68-8894-29d5b1ee9ac5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-15 03:52:29</date>
      <author>Local STD Clinic</author>
      <email>lakeshaglaser@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.158.133.159</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In case you are sexually lively, you might be in danger.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="194a95b8-a787-41ad-a6d9-b1b7e13bc981" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-19 03:28:43</date>
      <author>std testing near me same day</author>
      <email>martinamoreland@reallyfast.biz</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.158.121.135</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Sexually transmitted ailments (STDs) are very common.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3de0c8b1-5307-406c-a48e-e9d8e0535c1d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2018-03-23 09:50:39</date>
      <author>STD Testing Near Me San Diego</author>
      <email>geraldo.spivey@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.158.134.139</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Searching for HIV testing sites apart from the Borum?</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>zoyismith@hotmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>