<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>editor</author>
  <title>Girl Thrown to Dogs</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2008%2f10%2fgpc_work_midsize_82.jpg" alt="" width="241" height="298" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Justice Denied&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Tuesday, October 28, 2008&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Baby thrown into canal; Zardari takes prompt action, seeks report&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
By Rauf Klasra&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
ISLAMABAD: There is more to the bone-chilling account of the 17-year-old Taslim Solangi of Khairpur who was thrown to dogs &amp;mdash; she was 8-month pregnant and was forced to give birth to her baby prematurely. [more]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The baby was immediately thrown into the nearby Ubhal Wah canal after her killer father-in-law passed a judgement that the child was illegitimate and did not deserve to be allowed to live. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile, a new report said hit men have also been dispatched to Karachi to kill the absconding mother of Taslim who had fled the village. Top level inside sources have now confirmed to The News on good authority that at the time of her murder Taslim was to give birth to her first child in two-week time.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But, once the decision to eliminate her was taken by her father-in-law Zamir Solangi, she was taken to a local midwife Mrs Badshaan alias Baashi for forced delivery of the child. Soon after the delivery, the baby was thrown into the nearby canal and later the mother was put to death.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In Islamabad, President Asif Ali Zardari reacted sharply to the report of killing of Taslim and has asked lady MNA Nafeesa Shah to investigate the shocking event and submit him a report. President&amp;rsquo;s spokesman Farhatullah Babar told The News that the president was greatly disturbed over the incident and had immediately asked Nafeesa Shah to investigate the matter.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Mr Babar said the lady MNA, who was scheduled to leave for Turkey along with Prime Minister Yousuf Raza Gilani, has cancelled her trip and decided to go to her village and probe the incident.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile, source said, an influential assistant commissioner serving in the Sindh government, who heads the Solangi tribe, is said to have played a key role in facilitating the murder of the 17-year old girl. Mrs Zakran, the mother of the victim, is hiding in Karachi as Zamir Solangi has now dispatched hit men to kill her. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A source said: &amp;ldquo;You are talking about some one who was murdered in March, but no one is talking about the mother of the victim whose life is in serious danger after she decided to take on the killers of her daughter.&amp;icirc;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The murderer is still at large, telling every body that he has sent hired assassins to eliminate the mother of his daughter-in-law. The police have instead arrested the husband of the girl, who volunteered to confess that he has killed his wife. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Gul Sher had married a woman of the adjoining Kanhar tribe from whom he had two sons and as many daughters. Taslim was the elder daughter, who was married to the son of her real uncle Zamir Solangi. One day, the mother of Taslim borrowed jewellery from her neighbours and fled the village along with her children. It is not known why she left her house, leaving her husband behind in the village. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
She settled in Karachi with her children. After some time, she got her daughter Taslim married to a young man of Kanhar tribe of the same area. This marriage had taken place in Karachi. Having no idea that the young man belonged to the adjoining village of her own village, she married off her daughter to him. The Kanhar tribes have many houses adjacent to Hajana Shah, Pir jo Goth (the area of Pir of Pagara). One day, the young man took his wife Taslim to his village, as he did not know the history of her mother-in-law. By chance, some women from Hajna Shah came to visit the very house of the Kanhar tribe and learnt that Taslim had remarried to another man. They went back and informed their elders the whole story. This became a matter of enmity between the Solangi and Kanhar tribes. However, the chief of Solangi tribe and a serving assistant commissioner Sain Dad brokered a deal between the two tribes. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The assistant commissioner decided that the Kanhar tribe would pay a fine of Rs 400,000 to the Sloangi family for remarrying the girl. Likewise, Sain Dad also made the Kanhar tribe to hand over Taslim to an old man Khajan of Hajana Shah village as &amp;euml;Amaanatي till a final decision. The girl was handed over to one Mulla Ajao who later handed her over to Mr Khajan who kept her in his home.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But one morning Zamir Solangi came to Khajan with holy Quran in his hands to assure him that if he handed over his daughter-in-law, he would not harm her. He vowed on Quran that he would not kill her and would keep her at his house. Zamir also gave a word on Quran to her frightened niece and daughter-in-law Taslim that he would not kill her. Khajan agreed and handed over the girl to Zamir Solangi.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
After taking the girl to his home, the first thing he did was to take the pregnant Taslim to a midwife Baashi to arrange the delivery of the child whose actual date of delivery was still fifteen days away. The moment the child was born, he was thrown in the Ujhal Wah canal.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Zamir Solangi forced his son Ibrahim Solangi to declare that his wife was a &amp;euml;Kaaliي. He asked his son it was better that he confessed to police that he had killed his wife for being &amp;euml;Kaaliي, as it would be easy at the later stage to get him out of jail after some compromise, as happens in the cases of honour killing. Ibrahim went to the police station and confessed to have killed his wife in the name of honour. Thus the real killer managed to escape arrest. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile, the Ahmedpur police station officials did not show any interest in further investigating the whole issue after the husband of girl surrendered before the police. Talking to The News, DSP Khairpur Liaqat Abbasi said it was a simple case of honour killing, as the husband had confessed to the crime and was in jail. He claimed that there was some dispute over the payment of money, which had actually led to big hue and cry.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile, MNA Nafisa Shah, who belongs to Khairpur, has condemned the incident of Taslim Solangi&amp;rsquo;s murder, which she termed as cruel, inhuman and barbaric. She also condemned the role of the Jirga. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There have been numerous cases where the MNA, a former Nazim, has taken personal risks and saved lives of many women. There have been other cases when she learnt of deaths months after the incidents and ordered enquiries and the culprits were brought to justice. This has been duly acknowledged nationally and internationally, as she received a number of citations on peace and human rights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-10-31 08:37:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-04-01 15:33:29</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Girl-Thrown-to-Dogs</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="37fce528-87c6-4748-8ac0-e2d02937516f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-02-22 03:16:42</date>
      <author>Kim</author>
      <email>iris.geboortekaartjetekst@gmail.com</email>
      <country>nl</country>
      <ip>82.161.136.15</ip>
      <website>http://www.geboortekaartje-tekst.nl/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>What a terrible story!
God bless her</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c1db141e-6322-4e9f-86e5-4d246488753b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-01 06:33:29</date>
      <author>Michael</author>
      <email>stephan@create2send.com</email>
      <country>nl</country>
      <ip>82.161.92.55</ip>
      <website>http://www.geboortekaartje-maken.nl/category/zelf-ontwerpen/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>What a disgusting story!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bbfb04cf-2025-4d62-a294-415c5935b9a8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 00:42:53</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>brandyketchum@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.58.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, awesome blog layout! How long have you been blogging for? you made blogging look easy. The overall look of your website is wonderful, as well as the content!

my web blog;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.comfortstudioblog.com/all-natural-ingredient-appetite-suppressants/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c9debedd-7874-47be-8e18-d14b74c7a318" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-04 21:28:03</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>candralockwood@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hmm it seems like your blog ate my first comment (it was super long) so I guess I&amp;#39;ll just sum it up what I submitted and say, I&amp;#39;m thoroughly enjoying your blog. I as well am an aspiring blog writer but I&amp;#39;m still new to everything. Do you have any suggestions for first-time blog writers? I&amp;#39;d definitely appreciate it.

my web page;  Garcinia Cambogia Extract - http://www.2012ad.net/uncategorized/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c36d5af2-12a6-482b-9dea-78c3cc920b0d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 07:07:30</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>raphael-hays@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.50.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Good answer back in return of this issue with genuine arguments and telling everything regarding that.

Here is my web site;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.greekommend.com/diet-patch-that-functions/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="98abf272-5e97-43be-aaf0-7519e1572b83" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 10:07:29</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>wilma.wagoner@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I all the time emailed this website post page to all my friends, because if like to read it after that my friends will too.

Here is my homepage -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://hostandcare.com/DennyBold </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e38e911b-b931-4315-9af5-323dfeb1420a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 08:54:38</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>chetcorey@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This web site truly has all of the information I needed about this subject and didn&amp;#39;t know who to ask.

Feel free to visit my web blog ::  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.buildingfamilies411.com/?p=31 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="12431384-db35-4a9c-ad87-d18ba25c0f35" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 13:54:11</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>antonolivares@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Quality content is the important to interest the viewers to pay a quick visit the web page, that&amp;#39;s what this web page is providing.

Here is my blog post  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.peressident.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8038b4dd-7e69-4685-ab63-e6a07216a7b0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 19:25:26</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>ferminsellars@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Do you mind if I quote a couple of your articles as long as I provide credit and sources back to your site? My blog is in the very same niche as yours and my visitors would truly benefit from a lot of the information you provide here. Please let me know if this ok with you. Thank you!

my webpage -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://qaoq.net/the-side-impacts-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a8b000bc-e0fd-472c-9203-e1d923c334cd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 19:32:19</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>antonietta-withrow@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya this is somewhat of off topic but I was wondering if blogs use WYSIWYG editors or if you have to manually code with HTML. I&amp;#39;m starting a blog soon but have no coding skills so I wanted to get advice from someone with experience. Any help would be greatly appreciated!

My blog post  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.hauucsb.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8a18a556-7ec3-4e6f-a166-57b46fe9b54a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 08:43:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>mariepalacios@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice blog here! Also your web site loads up very fast! What host are you using? Can I get your affiliate link to your host? I wish my website loaded up as quickly as yours lol

Also visit my weblog ::  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.fatsecret.com/Default.aspx?pa=memn&amp;amp;id=10718216 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f5fe4759-b811-4979-b45f-3e14128282fb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 19:07:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>leticiaholden@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s hard to come by well-informed people about this topic, however, you sound like you know what you&amp;#39;re talking about! Thanks

Review my site;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://kuzdosport.info/garcinia-cambogia-extract-information/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d301d786-8d8e-402d-bdec-babfbb4c9000" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 09:32:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>noebartley@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.56.94</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Please let me know if you&amp;#39;re looking for a article author for your site. You have some really good articles and I believe I would be a good asset. If you ever want to take some of the load off, I&amp;#39;d really like to write some articles for your blog in exchange for a link back to mine. Please shoot me an email if interested. Many thanks!

Here is my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.aj-onu.org/garcinia-cambogia-extract-info/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f2780cc0-81df-459a-b990-298e98d5bcc0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 12:21:34</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>terrance-beckwith@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.112</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! Someone in my Facebook group shared this site with us so I came to check it out. I&amp;#39;m definitely loving the information. I&amp;#39;m book-marking and will be tweeting this to my followers! Exceptional blog and fantastic design and style.

Here is my page -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.arnbarn.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-assist-you-slim-down/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="492cb945-310a-4af0-ba38-91d4e9b15a20" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 02:53:26</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>manie_fortune@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.39.165</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I used to be suggested this blog via my cousin. I am not positive whether or not this put up is written by means of him as nobody else realize such specific about my problem. You are incredible! Thanks!

My webpage;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.tz315.net/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7a35d978-d561-4b8e-a48a-fec68b0a52f0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 03:23:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>ariellewhitcomb@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent post! We will be linking to this particularly great post on our site. Keep up the great writing.

Feel free to visit my weblog  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://kern-act.me/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fe3c2c21-2150-44c2-8e52-d4b09de3f5e9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 08:43:44</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>julianne.dowling@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty section of content. I just stumbled upon your weblog and in accession capital to assert that I acquire in fact enjoyed account your blog posts. Anyway I&amp;#39;ll be subscribing to your feeds and even I achievement you access consistently rapidly.

Take a look at my website:  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.infogadget.info/most-efficient-bodyweight-loss-drugs/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a2348c4f-b794-4ba7-a89a-a0af9d57774b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-07 00:02:27</date>
      <author>where can you buy garcinia cambogia walmart</author>
      <email>williamscoulter@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.88.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s amazing in support of me to have a site, which is useful in favor of my experience. thanks admin

My web page:  where can you buy garcinia cambogia walmart - http://dixongrove.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b33aacfd-4588-49e4-915e-bacb69e14c7e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-14 16:57:17</date>
      <author>http://www.ostrov-federacia.ru</author>
      <email>marilynnburgos@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.143.135.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Incidentally, if you meet with an accident while driving, and had gone up by 40% in the year to &amp;#163;1, 421. There is hard statistical evidence that young men are more likely to be involved in a collision with an uninsured or under-insured motorist coverage would pick up the tab. Simon Douglas, director of insurance at the Association of British Insurers ABI, 12% of drivers are aged 17 to 24 - but they are responsible for almost 30% of accidents.

my page - cheap motor trade insurance -  http://www.ostrov-federacia.ru - http://www.ostrov-federacia.ru/node/14688  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="327accc0-c3da-4cb8-9884-a19cd1b48eac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 09:19:40</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>bailey-roberts@the-fastest.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.166</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, constantly i used to check webpage posts here early in the daylight, as i love to gain knowledge of more and more.

Here is my homepage -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://proxydrop.org/?p=31 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="780170f5-09ad-4075-9815-c013ec9ab7e3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-16 07:21:39</date>
      <author>cheapest car insurance for young drivers</author>
      <email>latanyalambert@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.189.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This includes a basic rate of 16  cheapest car insurance for young drivers - http://www.futurschampions.com/groups/guidelines-for-prudent-secrets-in-young-drivers-car-insurance/  hours pay for every officer, irrespective of the number of accidents. Interestingly Ford, who have seen the average price go up by almost a quarter, or 326 a year.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="02268a74-a628-4709-b1a8-34c4f280a160" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-18 22:26:25</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>ianlaflamme@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.7</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Do you have any video of that? I&amp;#39;d care to find out more details.

my web site -  Garcinia cambogia Extract - http://www.go1688.info/should-you-or-should-you-not-purchase-garcinia-cambogia-select/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1e95b01d-1573-4aca-b3cc-6f8b3a20c941" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-08 10:15:27</date>
      <author>http://network.josephsnetwork.com/members/otiliaber/activity/2188</author>
      <email>tristaabt@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.25.5</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>These showed that in September of 2011 three deposits totaling $785, 000 had been made as well  http://network.josephsnetwork.com/members/otiliaber/activity/2188 - http://network.josephsnetwork.com/members/otiliaber/activity/2188/  as avoid the worst of the traffic. After three nights, or at least the first night trying out all our camping gear, in  http://network.josephsnetwork.com/members/otiliaber/activity/2188 - http://network.josephsnetwork.com/members/otiliaber/activity/2188/  the driveway of a cosy cottage, even in the car park of a local business. Afterwards, he defended himself for his comment and said:&amp;quot; It was a fine enough scenario that we decided to put our infamy behind us and head off in search of a beach.
cheap motorhome insurance ( usplus2.com - http://usplus2.com/members/abbymeeha/groups/my-groups/ ) campervan insurance,  http://2to.info/members/linakeene/activity/58912/ - http://2to.info/members/linakeene/activity/58912/ ,  webpage - http://casitademausi.bootstudio.net/noticias/concerns-raise-detailed-breakdown-smart-httpmotorhomeinsuranceblogcouk-methods 
cheap motorhome insurance -  www.panda-mb.ru - http://www.panda-mb.ru/content/guidance-wise-httpmotorhomeinsuranceblogcouk-strategies-useful-overview , motorhome insurance ( gsppi.berkeley.edu - http://gsppi.berkeley.edu/author/LesleyOtt ) cheap motorhome insurance ( http://www.wiligear.com/?q=forum/topic/170967 - http://www.wiligear.com/?q=forum/topic/170967 )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9d22369e-c85d-42aa-8dbc-c31a6f772d63" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 08:11:53</date>
      <author>truman-algeria.com</author>
      <email>ingeborg.pickard@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.154.114.39</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you are connected with a financial planner, who should be able to clarify this for health insurance you. Single premium is technically a limited payment period or a change in the death benefit tax-free. If there is a loss of the borrower and his physical condition. For most families, this means getting term life insurance with no medical exam, is always preferred by people.

Here is my homepage - private health insurance ( truman-algeria.com - http://truman-algeria.com/forum-truman/member.php?5968-MagnoliaM )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8c597eea-a4f0-4a9c-9e87-40508f7279e2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-07 18:06:54</date>
      <author>jnmv</author>
      <email>hazelberkman@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.168.26.250</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you desire to grow your know-how just keep visiting this web page and be updated with the latest gossip posted here.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1743dbb8-1840-428d-8fb4-a5e05c693807" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-03 01:04:59</date>
      <author>Аренда квартир в Аликанте</author>
      <email>heathbroomfield@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>151.237.178.192</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greetings I am so delighted I found your website, I really found you by accident, while I was researching on Askjeeve for something else, Anyhow I am here now and would just like to say thanks a lot for a incredible post and a all round interesting blog (I also love the theme/design), I don&amp;#39;t have time to read through it all at the moment but I have bookmarked it and also added in your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read much more, Please do keep up the superb work.  Here is my homepage;  Аренда квартир в Аликанте - http://www.daydayshop.com/comment/html/index.php?page=1&amp;amp;id=61149 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f79ac45c-784c-4795-b25f-a6cef76efd01" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-04 17:49:51</date>
      <author>best coupon website in vietnam</author>
      <email>santo_westover@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>151.237.176.50</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#161;&amp;#166;s really a nice and useful piece of information. I&amp;#161;&amp;#166;m satisfied that you just shared this useful information with us. Please keep us informed like this. Thank you for sharing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c1798e1b-fd92-4054-a58d-0a8e14ec0cb1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-29 16:57:22</date>
      <author>https://www.fiverr.com/cldisplay_seo/do-500-seo-backlinks-non-profit-websites</author>
      <email>felisha_bartley@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>177.82.118.3</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Anyone can tell you that backlinks aren&amp;#39;t doubt the disputed heavy weight champion from the SEO world.  Ken Evoy of  and Jimmy Brown a known Internet marketer shared 2 strategies, which are &amp;quot;pre-selling&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;useful, but incomplete. Significance of Website Back-links and SEOYou could possibly be wondering how effective websites or webpages can be without back-links and SEO.  My page :: backlink for shopify [ https://www.fiverr.com/cldisplay_seo/do-500-seo-backlinks-non-profit-websites - https://www.fiverr.com/cldisplay_seo/do-500-seo-backlinks-non-profit-websites ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="38bce4e4-a1f5-4a94-a2c0-a433ffa37545" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-11-06 04:47:52</date>
      <author>backlink for online shop</author>
      <email>romandonnithorne@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>177.142.68.149</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In this process, you ought to add the url of an different website and in exactly the same way; your website owner may also help you to add the url of the website on the sites. Backlinking and selecting the proper keywords go quite a distance to enhancing search results rankings.  Quality backlinks require time and just must be company promises one thing in the ad, does not necessarily mean that maybe what the service will provide.  Feel free to visit my blog -  backlink for online shop - https://www.fiverr.com/cldisplay_seo/create-high-quality-backlinks-for-your-website </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>