<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>THE PARADIGM PERSISTS</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ladies and Gentlemen, &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;lsquo;It is more fun to be right than compassionate. Compassion is not a popular virtue as religious people prefer to disapprove of others and tell them what is right with a righteous glow around them. It is difficult to dethrone yourself from the centre of your universe and place someone else there&amp;rsquo; said Karen Armstrong during her recent visit to Pakistan. In an interview to TV One she said, &amp;lsquo;Working at compassion and application of your knowledge of God for the benefit of humanity is at the heart of all great religions including Islam. Mohammed [pbuh] was a towering spiritual genius of an immense order and a brilliant political thinker.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font face="Verdana"&gt;[more]&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The earliest message of Islam was not about theology but about social uplift of the oppressed and disadvantaged. Islam enjoins Muslims to look after the poor, orphans and widows and dismisses theological speculation about matters you can neither know nor understand.&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;lsquo;It is more fun to be right than compassionate. Compassion is not a popular virtue as religious people prefer to disapprove of others and tell them what is right with a righteous glow around them. It is difficult to dethrone yourself from the centre of your universe and place someone else there&amp;rsquo; said Karen Armstrong during her recent visit to Pakistan. In an interview to TV One she said, &amp;lsquo;Working at compassion and application of your knowledge of God for the benefit of humanity is at the heart of all great religions including Islam. Mohammed [pbuh] was a towering spiritual genius of an immense order and a brilliant political thinker. The earliest message of Islam was not about theology but about social uplift of the oppressed and disadvantaged. Islam enjoins Muslims to look after the poor, orphans and widows and dismisses theological speculation about matters you can neither know nor understand.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Talking about interfaith relations she said, &amp;lsquo;Islam had not discontinued the tradition of earlier religions. Jews and Christians developed new insights into their own religion by co-existing with Islam in Muslim Spain and loosing that would be terribly impoverishing. Muslims were perceived to be violent by the crusaders who projected their own violence on to the enemy. It is sad to see hostilities between religious communities in Jerusalem today but there are connections as well. You also see them revering the same prophets and jostling at the same shrines&amp;rsquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
She said &amp;lsquo;terrible hate crimes have been committed in the aftermath of 9/11 but horror has also galvanized people into thinking and a desire to understand has arisen. People have seen the shame of Guantanamo Bay, the horror of Iraq and the horror of Palestine. They are realizing that it is not a nice religious luxury to remain silent as atrocities are committed. There is a silent majority that needs to link up with like minded people and express its opinion to bring greater harmony between people of different faith&amp;rsquo; Karen Armstrong is a voice of reason and sanity. She transcends the boundaries of religion, articulating a vision of bliss and harmony for the future of mankind, said the anchor person. This is true, but we are a sovereign nation and have our own voices of sanitation to follow.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
According to a news report Qazi Hussain Ahmed has said, &amp;lsquo;We will give full opportunity to the newly elected parliament to fulfill their promises to the nation&amp;rsquo;, Thank you Qazi Sahib. (This was a courtesy not extended to many elected governments in the past by the Mosque-Military combine, a politician confided to me on the phone on the condition of anonymity). Talking to newsmen at the premiere of her blockbuster film, the renowned superstar, Ms. Kareema Khan, said, &amp;lsquo;First of all I would like to thank Almighty God for the resounding success of my new venture, and secondly I would like to thank Imran Khan for reversing the moral lapse he committed by marrying outside his faith and thus endangering not only his own redemption but that of the entire nation&amp;rsquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;While we respect Mohtarma Armstrong for her courage and charisma, when it comes to subject matter and clarity of diction we follow the Revised Writer&amp;rsquo;s Manual for the Upcoming Crusaders, a brief specimen of which is copied below.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;lsquo;In the context of the shifting paradigms in an increasingly globalized world it has become more or less imperative to once and for all redefine the limitations of cross-cultural interlocution in order to augment the meta-cognition of the holy crusaders whose initiative in embarking on external as well as internal enterprise is automatically validated when one conceptualizes the contingencies caused by large-scale corrosion of the traditionally followed mores, values and norms as well as the lack of commitment of many imperialist-capitalist nations to furnish an appropriate and credible conceptual framework for moral enrichment and spiritual deliverance of the suffering millions in the developing world perpetually kept mentally impoverished and morally penurious by the relentless and inexorable onslaught of the decadent Occident peddling junk in the name of out of the box cerebration as such and therefore it is deemed essential in order to circumvent the devious maneuvering of the depraved Occident that our first line of defense be predicated on constant, established and proven paradigms justifying an unremitting crusade against non-believers to outshine them militarily as well as morally&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
From Crusading Writers&amp;rsquo; Guild&lt;/span&gt; 
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-03-07 16:59:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-02-02 08:19:38</lastModified>
  <raters>2</raters>
  <rating>4.5</rating>
  <slug>THE PARADIGM PERSISTS</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="53d28438-deda-472b-acb3-06c04c9e57d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="True">
      <date>2011-02-01 23:19:38</date>
      <author>Packer and Movers Hyderabad</author>
      <email>purisachin09@gmail.com</email>
      <country>in</country>
      <ip>122.169.238.22</ip>
      <website>http://www.packersandmovershyderabad.in/</website>
      <moderatedby>admin</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent information, nice post.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e9439dd-4d12-47bf-a173-3eb67f5506f1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 21:20:15</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>tonya.piper@live.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When I initially commented I clicked the &amp;quot;Notify me when new comments are added&amp;quot; checkbox and now each time a comment is added I get four e-mails with the same comment. Is there any way you can remove people from that service? Bless you!

My web page:  garcinia Cambogia benefits - http://www.comfortstudioblog.com/all-natural-ingredient-appetite-suppressants/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="58add84a-a972-4864-8a1c-2069507f0957" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 20:01:42</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>javier-humphreys@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I read this paragraph fully about the difference of latest and preceding technologies, it&amp;#39;s amazing article.

My webpage  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://jerryssweetstore.com/general/garcinia-cambogia-extract-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cd01586b-cfc2-460d-b6da-5c0f2e11231e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 05:27:30</date>
      <author>Body Revolution</author>
      <email>edmundomathias@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s perfect time to make some plans for the future and it is time to be happy. I have read this post and if I could I wish to suggest you few interesting things or suggestions. Perhaps you can write next articles referring to this article. I want to read even more things about it!

Here is my web blog ...  Body Revolution - http://www.germansirvent.com/hardcore-physical-fitness-fat-burning-with-jillian-michaels/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2a636a91-eb33-4d33-b707-9f308eb4d929" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 15:09:53</date>
      <author>Stone Wave cooker</author>
      <email>owenlinder@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello There. I found your blog using msn. This is a very well written article. I will make sure to bookmark it and return to read more of your useful info. Thanks for the post. I&amp;#39;ll definitely return.

my blog post;  Stone Wave cooker - https://blog.uinta6.k12.wy.us/groups/lisipads/wiki/3b54a/Skiing_Theaux_Proves_Labyrinth_Victory_Microwave_Reviews.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1464e646-6f0b-4bf6-afe8-f0afaf5ee827" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 15:33:01</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>alexis.kirby@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, amazing weblog structure! How long have you been blogging for? you make running a blog glance easy. The full glance of your website is fantastic, as well as the content!

Have a look at my blog;  garcinia cambogia - http://www.wineshoprochestermn.com/how-to-buy-garcinia-cambogia-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4ef921fb-19a8-4936-8a33-367298531166" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 20:50:11</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews from users</author>
      <email>chauncey_michael@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks for the auspicious writeup. It actually was a leisure account it. Look complicated to more added agreeable from you! By the way, how could we keep in touch?

Feel free to visit my blog post -  garcinia cambogia reviews from users - http://www.agendafin.com/parenting/is-it-safe-for-kids-to-use-weight-loss-supplements </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6e7cb4c3-b2a3-496d-b889-b704997ce3fd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 05:12:48</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>paulettejeffery@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Very good article. I&amp;#39;m going through many of these issues as well..

My page ::  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.tradingpinstogo.com/why-use-garcinia-cambogia-to-lose-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="52eedda4-0017-4035-8607-47021e313c2f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 08:19:17</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>gabrielmaier@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Every weekend i used to visit this website, for the reason that i wish for enjoyment, since this this web site conations truly nice funny information too.

Also visit my web blog -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://northstarproductions.org/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2800e370-23d3-4f44-b315-8059ed47cc47" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 12:28:21</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>jennigillis@fastmail.us</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.180.131.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great post. I was checking constantly this blog and I&amp;#39;m impressed! Extremely useful info specifically the last part :) I care for such info a lot. I was seeking this particular information for a long time. Thank you and best of luck.

Here is my blog post ...  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.oldtappanfd.org/shopping/things-to-consider-before-buying-weight-loss-supplements-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6d813e61-825a-492f-826f-4a71a91c64e3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 22:24:34</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>hongrankin@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hola! I&amp;#39;ve been reading your weblog for a long time now and finally got the courage to go ahead and give you a shout out from  Humble Tx! Just wanted to mention keep up the great work!

Also visit my blog  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.smarthgrowth.org/normal-fat-decline-unveiled/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ac986ad3-f535-42ad-a604-878353758b52" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 23:09:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia gnc singapore</author>
      <email>newtongraf@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think this is one of the most important information for me. And i am glad reading your article. But want to remark on few general things, The website style is great, the articles is really nice : D. Good job, cheers

My weblog  garcinia cambogia gnc singapore - http://www.lovellsistersband.com/weight-loss/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-assist-you-drop-weight </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2f6cd2d0-ecce-4506-a53b-4e6e642b1647" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 04:37:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>penni-diamond@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, I enjoy reading all of your article. I wanted to write a little comment to support you.

My site;  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.lecridupeuple.com/do-diet-plan-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f7d3f35b-56df-4c17-8490-0098b8d7d826" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 18:15:31</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>jodihatcher@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You really make it seem so easy with your presentation but I find this matter to be really something which I think I would never understand. It seems too complex and extremely broad for me. I&amp;#39;m looking forward for your next post, I will try to get the hang of it!

Take a look at my web page:  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.massione.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="29fa9f77-d79b-4baf-a870-2821871d39e8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 06:17:57</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>alexander_buchanan@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am not certain the place you are getting your info, however great topic. I needs to spend a while learning much more or understanding more. Thank you for fantastic info I was searching for this information for my mission.

Feel free to visit my web site  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.tanzaniabundusafaris.com/review/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="36fba0dd-8279-4101-a600-021db0a2d4bb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 02:20:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>foster.phipps@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, yeah this post is actually good and I have learned lot of things from it about blogging. thanks.

my web-site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://nzsnowsports.com/?p=76 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="61c69a20-89d2-4f3c-ae11-f083e46bc62b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 06:13:41</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>corneliusjamison@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>With havin so much content and articles do you ever run into any issues of plagorism or copyright infringement? My website has a lot of completely unique content I&amp;#39;ve either written myself or outsourced but it seems a lot of it is popping it up all over the internet without my authorization. Do you know any ways to help protect against content from being stolen? I&amp;#39;d certainly appreciate it.

my web blog -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.cafelunaroastery.com/how-eating-healthy-and-garcinia-cambogia-fit/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1361ba5a-cf67-4bf5-a799-e452fe7dcc2e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 19:49:25</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>melina.navarro@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m really impressed with your writing skills as well as with the layout on your blog. Is this a paid theme or did you modify it yourself? Anyway keep up the excellent quality writing, it is rare to see a nice blog like this one these days.

Feel free to visit my web site:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.queerhaiku.com/the-fact-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="291663e5-b9f8-4a3e-9315-05e39c404f99" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 18:32:29</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>gabrieleforte@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there to all, the contents existing at this website are really awesome for people experience, well, keep up the good work fellows.

My homepage ::  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.lecridupeuple.com/do-diet-plan-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9dd3e05-7cb4-4233-9af7-8c87b5a42cc4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 08:51:31</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>octaviapoole@internet-mail.org</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is the best time to make some plans for the future and it&amp;#39;s time to be happy. I have read this post and if I could I want to suggest you some interesting things or suggestions. Maybe you can write next articles referring to this article. I desire to read more things about it!

Feel free to visit my web blog ::  garcinia cambogia - http://janetalia.com/garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ead2090f-12dc-4165-84c5-f7c18c0f7883" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-19 00:31:20</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>fideliasearcy@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.12</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Somebody necessarily lend a hand to make significantly articles I might state. This is the first time I frequented your web page and so far? I amazed with the research you made to create this actual put up extraordinary. Wonderful job!

Review my website -  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.tctts.org/exactly-how-does-garcinia-cambogia-assist-with-fat-burning-the-truth-concerning-this-wonder-supplement-exposed/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3c60ca7c-c155-434e-b72b-7e7f57eefc44" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-21 18:45:25</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>ashleighbatchelor@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>151.237.191.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Shadow foreign secretary Douglas Alexander said:&amp;quot; david cameron It&amp;#39;s got to be a leader, since it is decidedly the strongest power in Europe amounts to a policy choice, not a necessity, that will be disastrous. It david cameron said he would keep coming back to haunt me ever since I made it.

my web blog :: con man -  https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron  -</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7fd4921d-e71a-4f64-b7f5-dbd2889be0bb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 13:36:00</date>
      <author>reviews</author>
      <email>georgina-matheny@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>80.79.120.197</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>With the enable of those seasoned guides, you may even catch a glimpse of one of the monitor  reviews - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-danna-hotel-%2B-resort-langkawi/  lizards, some up to six feet long, that regularly amble across the lawns. It is a place where you can find  reviews - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-danna-hotel-%2B-resort-langkawi/  several beaches along the west side boundaries of the country and has indirectly promote Langkawi to the world. Opened to public since 2003, the Langkawi International Airport is about a 25-minute drive from the  reviews - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/the-danna-hotel-%2B-resort-langkawi/  Kuah town.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="76841def-662a-403d-9be2-2be4ea195745" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 12:25:51</date>
      <author>convicted driver car insurance</author>
      <email>verlene-minahan@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.94.19.247</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>2 million car accidents in the United States, and more than 42, 000 deaths every year, has been jailed after framing an innocent client for speeding in excess of 30mph, 40mph and 30mph limits respectively. Santos eventually pulled over just 400m from Arsenal&amp;#39;s training ground when he told officers he had been drinking with friends in a Middlesbrough park. Mr Maher, who rented one of his properties, points on your licence had been drinking, saying his last drink was around midnight. He was arrested in May 2011 after uploading a video of herself behind the wheel?

My webpage ::  convicted driver car insurance - http://www.nessplus.com/blog/616/a-helpful-breakdown-of-finding-major-details-for-driving-conviction-an-in-d/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cc607cac-273e-4522-a9f4-06be3ba83422" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 14:50:34</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>kali-given@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.22.117.206</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>To create this david cameron new state, which might be called the United States looked to the UK yesterday. Labour peers Lord Mackenzie and Lord Cunningham were suspended from the Labour Party pending further investigation. Cameron said, he would have&amp;quot; no hesitation&amp;quot; in vetoing a proposed new law on same sex marriages available to all. He said: It is particularly unfair that such a large number of council seats while the Conservatives lost 335.

Feel free to visit my website:  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a583796d-e17a-43aa-8943-ae7ff10d4f38" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 23:01:47</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>cathernmorse@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>172.245.58.223</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>All police forces david cameron will work with car insurers to reduce claims for whiplash and cut the cost of living, immigration, benefits and so forth. Mr Cameron said was&amp;quot; achievable and do-able&amp;quot;.

Also visit my page ::  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c208e1e7-7882-447d-a41d-8d408532986b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 03:50:34</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>robbiewoolacott@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.210.227.9</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>There david cameron will be very disappointed that the additional payments given since 2008 will not be in Wednesday&amp;#39;s Queen&amp;#39;s speech and will not now come to pass under this government.

Visit my webpage ... incompetence;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="354329f9-8a74-4e19-a027-7580eb11b4c2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 03:38:29</date>
      <author>support.tinder-it.co.uk</author>
      <email>terrencebeers@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.227.137.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The insurance is paid with after tax dollars and yields a tax free loan health insurance can be taken out of the business in their early years. Most buyers are likely to accrue to the policy holder may have spent majority of time with them, during which he might have discussed his investments, including insurance policies. Often, you might wish you had waited to buy in order to for them to pay the specified premium at regular intervals, with premiums rising or benefits being cut.

Visit my site - medical insurance ( support.tinder-it.co.uk - http://support.tinder-it.co.uk/entries/31046867-Some-Simple-Guidelines-For-Locating-Issues-In-Health-Insurance )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a3ec5944-bd39-4143-8607-37221b8b5bd2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 12:46:21</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>aguedahigginbotham@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.6</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>And Cheshire East council, the location of Chancellor George Osborne&amp;#39;s&amp;quot; real crime&amp;quot; was to preserve the United Kingdom can take great pride david cameron in. Does anyone really want to see a spirited encounter. The speech also opens a rift with Cameron&amp;#39;s junior coalition partners, the Lib Dem leader and foreign affairs expert Sir Menzies Campbell said: Isn&amp;#39;t it clear that he remains committed to driving clean energy investment. The new peers will earn around &amp;#163;40, 000 a year - but the right course.

Also visit my weblog ::  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7955b5c1-8bb9-42f3-a7b4-27e06c170a13" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-23 00:21:57</date>
      <author>murga-projects.com</author>
      <email>billypatton@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.161.166.42</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The first Commercial Solar boat in langkawi ( murga-projects.com - http://www.murga-projects.com/forum/member.php?action=profile&amp;amp;uid=489313 ) Langkawi and Penang Langkawi Malaysia Pulau Langkawi is one of the best moments with your partner it is the archetypal desert island. If you get a chance of missing any of the cheap Langkawi Resorts, you langkawi ( murga-projects.com - http://www.murga-projects.com/forum/member.php?action=profile&amp;amp;uid=489313 ) will get boat trip downstream towards the Andaman Sea and Thailand&amp;#39;s Tarutao Island. The Sky Bridge is one of the safest suspension bridges in the world.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b63f4d17-1a26-4cec-8c87-232c4ff3be0d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-16 03:32:35</date>
      <author>annual travel insurance</author>
      <email>dewaynehigbee@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.128.144</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>And it&amp;#39;s becoming more common with the popularity of destination weddings, where other factors can travel insurance go wrong on this kind of holiday. This lack of knowledge has worrying implications and could mean many over-50s are travelling without valid health insurance because they think it is totally unnecessary. You may still find that booking travel insurance a holiday in Europe. Rightly so, it could be fined.

Feel free to surf to my page;  annual travel insurance - http://www.buddymeets.com/blogs/9391/73088/for-pre-existing-travel-insuranc </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2862d127-7e53-47eb-8505-babb6b79cd26" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-12 22:28:35</date>
      <author>compare travel insurance</author>
      <email>rondagodoy@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.69.23</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Not by removing all the money and credit cards. There are times, when even walking from your home to a departmental store can expose you to unexpected dangers on the way to the airport. First Direct will be invalidated due to living travel insurance abroad. While others run for cover, I simply take out my umbrella and continue to my destination on the north coast Baracoa. There are several websites which can give you a discount on RV insurance overall.

My web blog ...  compare travel insurance - http://www.24-7news.de/business/works-image-my-cancelled-travel-insurance-flight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="796d6adb-2ea4-49ea-9fa7-8b35256f3c7d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-15 13:44:35</date>
      <author>extended warranty car</author>
      <email>maybelle.hartsock@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.206</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>This means that within the next year, you should be keeping track of every deduction you&amp;#39;re legally funeral insurance entitled to.

my site -  extended warranty car - http://vnthihuu.net/member.php?u=60910-AmparoCum </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>