<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>The National Tragedy </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2012%2f9%2ftragedy.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By:&lt;/strong&gt; Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;It was a historic day that ended in tragedy; a tragedy that has not failed to touch all of us, regardless of class and status. The President has cancelled his tour to his French chateau via Burj Dubai and the Mian Sahib, acting swiftly, has postponed the project of buying free iPhones for foreign correspondents. The Field Marshal is has given the batman the evening off and is stretched on his camp bed, fully clothed, staring at the ceiling and thinking how things came to such a pass that he has to rehire his retired generals to protect them from the grubby paws of the bloody civilians. &amp;nbsp;[more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Tragedy indeed, but Pakistanis are by nature a resilient nation. We will bounce back within the period it the time it takes to lower a flag to half mast and raise it again. We must identify the foreign hand that will be behind this and expose it to the visiting UN team. We should not let go of our courage and determination and must speedily restore the calm and normalcy that is so characteristic of us as a nation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;We need to restore the collection of protection money on which the currently fragile economic recovery so heavily depends. We need to re-establish the target killings of labourers from Kurram and arrange transport back to FATA on the Chipa ambulances. We must be ready to burn the western consulates, lest the Libyans steal a march on us to achieve international glory. There are martyrdom bombers to be trained and minority ulema to be executed. We will be unflinching in our undertakings and unruffled by temporary setbacks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;It is such an unedifying sight to see these decadent western nations practically revel in self pity. You hear, day after day, year after year, about Hillsborough, Londonderry, Columbine and Vietnam. It amazing to see the merchandising of tragedy. The Pentagon looses a war and Hollywood makes a tidy some out of it. Have you ever heard of Lal Masjid, the action in Balochistan, the fall of Dhaka? We quietly achieved a genocide of world class proportions with limited resources and it went unnoticed by Zionist western media. Does it not completely expose the western double standards?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;We have been sucked into fighting a war that is not ours. We are killing and being killed by our own people. We were also sucked into the the war against the Soviet Union. However that war was our war. The difference was that it was Afghans who were killing and being killed by their own people whereas we were defending Islam and the free world with the help of weapons from Israel and petrodollars from our Saudi brothers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Ever since the First Aryans came down the Khyber Pass, we have been a martial race. Our sons have won admiration from friend and foe alike. Time Square, London Underground and Taj Hotel are witness to our ingenuity and valour.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;This gives us hope that the present crisis will be solved in a timely and expeditious manner and the three accused will be acquitted with honour. Justice will be done and will be shown to be done. We have full confidence in the General Court Marshall.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2012-09-15 03:38:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2012-09-15 03:40:04</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>The-National-Tragedy-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="3882820d-c4a3-4ff8-9fb8-e1dc11095406" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-03-03 18:48:37</date>
      <author>click aqui</author>
      <email>romulohaji@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>138.128.226.238</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>﻿Wow! Ciertamente me siento cautivado con el topico del blog. Es elemental y aun asi  mismo de utilidad. En muchas veces es muy trabajoso conseguir un contrapeso entre sentido de la utilidad y aspecto  visual. No puedo dejar de comentar que has construido un desempe&amp;#241;o perfecto con esto. Por Otro Lado, la pagina web  se carga muy  veloz en mi Internet explorer. un weblog estupendo!  Chekea y ademas visita mi weblog:  click aqui - http://host.madison.com/app/advertising/YAPT/yapt-redirect.php?utm_source=yapt&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsor&amp;amp;utm_term=http://www.trucoteca.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="533ab526-f0db-4a5d-8126-cc10c8eb28df" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-08-11 05:38:11</date>
      <author>smartphone cheap</author>
      <email>simonwarfield@animail.net</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>62.122.203.82</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Many systems are becoming much easier to navigate and readily available contacts and all their associated information like e-mail social media details easily.  This is a huge supply of vulnerability as well as an increasingly inviting platform for malicious criminal activity that could have devastating effects on your own business.  This device is well sized and properly designed with stylish becoming an appropriate word, the minimalistic features and curved edges give the phone a fashionable, reliable frame.  Feel free to surf to my weblog ...  smartphone cheap - https://www.decent-price.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d25ceb74-286c-4646-b67c-5053249b7f03" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-03 16:36:45</date>
      <author>langzhuajielu.com</author>
      <email>prestonpoidevin@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>176.115.100.135</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In the fight against QR codes, you&amp;#39;ll find three significant reasons being shown to secure the theory that these two-dimensional barcodes just aren&amp;#39;t clicking with Americans:.  This type of technology utilizes specialized equipment, teaching materials and services which will enable him or her perform and function inside their surroundings.  Allowing consumers to find the charity, or perhaps creating a revolving list of charities, comes across like a marketing incentive.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="fd32281a-ff28-4e01-86c0-0a10eaa1032f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-09-12 03:54:09</date>
      <author>dịch thuật gi&amp;#225; rẻ</author>
      <email>jaytoomey@hotmail.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.175.77.148</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I simply couldn\&amp;#39;t go away your website before suggesting that I really enjoyed the usual info a person supply for your visitors? Is going to be again often in order to inspect new posts</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5cea1a70-0681-48e5-bc87-e19b7867ef97" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-07 06:13:40</date>
      <author>Аренда квартир в Аликанте</author>
      <email>gastonmcmullan@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.130.206.204</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there! This is my 1st comment here so I just wanted to give a quick shout out and say I really enjoy reading through your blog posts. Can you suggest any other blogs/websites/forums that cover the same topics? Thanks a lot!  Also visit my web-site ...  Аренда квартир в Аликанте - http://forum.mac-emu.net/index.php?p=/profile/violette10 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6ff92e9b-9685-4ffc-a16b-c390effd0b73" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-10-16 12:06:58</date>
      <author>Путеводитель Аликанте</author>
      <email>phillismenkens@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>50.3.197.234</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Highly energetic blog, I enjoyed that a lot. Will there be a part 2?  Here is my homepage:  Путеводитель Аликанте - http://nlc.bayanniecho.net/index.php/author/rayfordswin/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a11c868d-e51b-4fa2-9d65-2dc5bece7fc6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-11-05 01:56:16</date>
      <author>Аренда квартир в Аликанте</author>
      <email>nevadoris@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.122.170.24</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Touche. Solid arguments. Keep up the great spirit.  my site ::  Аренда квартир в Аликанте - http://businessethics.wiki/%D0%9D%D0%B0%D0%B4%D1%91%D0%B6%D0%BD%D0%B0%D1%8F_%D0%90%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B4%D0%B0_%D0%9D%D0%B5%D0%B4%D0%B2%D0%B8%D0%B6%D0%B8%D0%BC%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%82%D0%B8_%D0%9D%D0%B0_%D0%9F%D0%BE%D0%B1%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B6%D1%8C%D0%B5_%D0%92_%D0%90%D0%BB%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B0%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B5. </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>