<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Budhu</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;img style="color: #000000; font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 10px;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2014%2f1%2fbuddhu.jpg" alt="" width="400" height="500" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Mudassar Bashir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;Translated and Edited: &lt;em&gt;Muttahir Ahmed Khan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;Whenever the rich history, culture and architecture of Lahore is discussed, one cannot ignore Budhu&amp;rsquo;s tomb which possesses a grand status amongst the city&amp;rsquo;s monuments. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;Biography:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;Budhu is widely known for not only his tomb but also his famous &amp;lsquo;Aava&amp;rsquo;. Aava is a term used in Hindi, Punjabi and Persian to refer to a kiln where the potters bake earthen pottery and bricks. The historical writings suggest that Budhu was buried at the place where he died. It is well established through historical records that he died at his Aava.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;During the rule of Emperor Akbar, Lahore possessed a special status, due to being the hub of the state affairs, and remained the capital of the Mughal Empire in the last phase of Akbar&amp;rsquo;s rule. This factor made many nobles and the rich establish their houses in the city to remain closer to the court, and ultimately, several new areas and colonies were founded in the town. With the construction of new, luxurious and rich mansions, the brick makers made a large fortune.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;A potter named Sidhu was very famous for making baked bricks during Jahangir&amp;rsquo;s reign. After Sidhu&amp;rsquo;s death, the whole business got into the hands of his son Budhu. Therefore, Budhu grabbed the contracts of bulk supply of bricks for the construction of the Shalamar Garden and Nister Khan&amp;rsquo;s tomb. The reason for this huge demand of bricks was the grand ramparts that were built around these premises. Nowadays, these walls can be occasionally seen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;With these orders pouring in, Budhu&amp;rsquo;s contacts in the court grew and eventually, he came to be a part of the nobility. Then suddenly, an event took place which totally changed his life.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;One day, during a heavy rain, a old dervish Abdul Haq came to his kiln and asked for fire to warm himself in the cold weather. But, Budhu and his workers humiliated him and threw him out of the kiln. Due to this humiliation of the saint, the kiln did not light up in the succeeding days and the bricks remained raw and unfinished. After this setback, Budhu became unwell. Then, one night, he received an indication in his dream that the whole infliction upon him was the result of the humiliation and mistreatment of the dervish. The very next day, Budhu went to see the dervish, begged his forgiveness and became his devotee for good. After the demise of dervish Abdul Haq, Budhu himself laid the foundations of his tomb. Some historians opine that Budhu, after death, was buried beside the saint while some are of the view that he was laid to rest at the place where his Aava existed. Presently, the official gravestone at the tomb reads that Budhu is buried there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Tomb Premises&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;As we have already discussed, Budhu&amp;rsquo;s tomb was constructed at the site of his Aava. Maulvi Noor Ahmed Chishti writes in his book titled &amp;lsquo;Tahqiqat e Chishti&amp;rsquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;This Aava (kiln) is located at the distance of three miles to the eastern side of the city and is famous because of&amp;nbsp; a potter called Budhu who lived during Shah Jahan&amp;rsquo;s period and his father named Sidhu was known in the era of Jahangir.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;During the British period, many beautiful and historical buildings were sacrificed to meet the needs of the railways and the associated departments. This destructive spree was started by the state and, later on, worsened by the citizens&amp;rsquo; insensitive attitude. All included, Budhu&amp;rsquo;s Aawa, his tomb, the surrounding garden and all the beautiful buildings and boundary walls, was plundered and ruined. In the South, a graveyard was laid out and some houses were constructed to the North and East. To the West, some old houses still exist and are now being demolished to construct new shops. The mosaic work in blue shade is seen on top of the single dome, the same work is also present at Dai Anga&amp;rsquo;s Tomb.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;A small ground, filled with piles of garbage, also exists around the tomb&amp;rsquo;s platform that has bolted doors on all four sides. There are two graves, enclosed by doors and grills, under the dome, the walls of which have been affected by termites. Due to the smoke, produced by the drug-addicts who often sit there, one can find many black patches and spots in different places.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;The Budhu&amp;rsquo;s tomb is on one side of the road while University of Engineering and Technology Lahore exists to the eastern side of the other end. Nothing has been done by the past governments to preserve this four-century old building. But, more responsibility lies on the shoulders of the post-partition governments. If the status-quo persists, there would be no trace left of the tomb and its dome, the only surviving monument of Budhu&amp;rsquo;s Aava. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Damascus; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 12.8px; text-align: justify; font-size: 18px; font-family: Verdana; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-01-19 05:21:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-01-27 12:26:53</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Budhu</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="c44d0a2d-9540-4678-b26a-5074e0df9622" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-10 21:28:07</date>
      <author>Lashunda</author>
      <email>lashunda.maccullagh@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.182.120.207</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>These delicious fish are available fresh in the Pacific Northwest during the harvest season, July through September. A paper towel and a little bit of soap will remove most of the red stains on your lips. Bissell has several scented product if you prefer different scents on your cleaned carpeting.

Feel free to visit my website; wine stains ( Lashunda - http://winestains.org/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="41cbc9d1-fcdc-4e3b-a455-a663914ebcc7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-08 09:19:43</date>
      <author>backyard landscaping ideas</author>
      <email>wilburncheeke@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>89.47.29.71</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>When you decide on an area to plant a plant, make sure it can thrive there. Had you always been thinking to upgrade the pavers of the patio. With its thick, glossy needles and dense, upward-reaching branches, the yew is useful as both a shrub and tree.

My web page;  backyard landscaping ideas - http://toboganium.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c2ce7a25-8755-477e-a28e-f8652cea391d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-14 15:53:07</date>
      <author>http://www.alotspace.com/</author>
      <email>demetracousens@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.94.63.112</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>How is the web reputation of the intended web host provider. If you are planning to manage several websites, it should be able to lend various options so that you could manage your accounts as per your comfortability. Choosing how you will present your business or your personal blog to the world requires careful planning, precise goals, and informed methods of implementation.

Feel free to visit my blog ... web hosting ( http://www.alotspace.com/ - http://www.alotspace.com/best-social-networking-books-for-writers-ten-best-social-networking-books-for-writers/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f6019ee4-f258-4a8a-9ce5-b02fec2bc2fa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-11-07 07:16:56</date>
      <author>minecraft hosts</author>
      <email>alvarohirth@arcor.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>178.19.108.222</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I always spent my half an hour to read this webpage&amp;#39;s articles every day along with a cup of coffee.

my blog post;  minecraft hosts - http://briaanneny.skyrock.com/3236139843-Affordable-minecraft-hosting-worldwide-Spartanhost.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f3f79a6e-c6f8-4d38-a902-8b42deb21218" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-02-27 13:17:36</date>
      <author>Death</author>
      <email>anne.galbraith@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.171.238.177</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>An impressive share! I have just forwarded this onto a colleague who was doing a little homework on this. And he in fact ordered me breakfast because I stumbled upon it for him... lol. So let me reword this.... Thank YOU for the meal!! But yeah, thanx for spending some time to discuss this topic here on your internet site.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="30af9f60-9f13-4cde-bdd8-2affd5e3feee" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-23 01:57:21</date>
      <author>slimming capsules from china</author>
      <email>philipdorris@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>79.110.18.106</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If overweight men and women are physically energetic all through the day, they can be really helpful weak to reasonable train.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6d2b8681-b4af-440f-9713-c081cdbe0c81" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-26 01:49:16</date>
      <author>natural cures for yeast infection</author>
      <email>charmainedmunds@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>167.160.105.97</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I don&amp;#39;t even know how I ended up here, but I thought this post was great. I do not know who you are but definitely you&amp;#39;re going to a famous blogger if you aren&amp;#39;t already ;) Cheers!

Feel free to surf to my website -  natural cures for yeast infection - http://yeastinfectionstreatment.Altervista.org/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="62ad9be8-f19f-488e-a5f9-21fb5e23f54f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-08 20:29:36</date>
      <author>Slimming world dieta</author>
      <email>darciedman@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>146.185.204.238</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi Bilaras... I just needed to ask if I could make a banana smoothie on day four and to say thanks for the eating regimen plan.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e90b308b-68fa-4807-abdd-f01b03944240" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-10 12:53:41</date>
      <author>Hildred</author>
      <email>garretthornung@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>185.62.188.148</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, after reading this awesome paragraph i am too delighted to share my experience here with colleagues.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="da8ef7f7-a506-4f31-880b-73c194b456af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-06-29 17:32:15</date>
      <author>e cigs pro vapor</author>
      <email>dwightputilin@gmx.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>204.44.90.208</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I every time used to read article in news papers but now as I am a user of net therefore from now I am using net for articles, thanks to web.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4db47429-65ac-49e2-ae85-3e45ce6e5d47" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-07-02 18:08:47</date>
      <author>free hummingbird artwork</author>
      <email>mabelcarrigan@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>167.160.105.9</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The nectar solution can be achieved in your house, using a ratio of four years old parts water to at least one part white cane sugar. I want to thank Landstrom&amp;#39;s because of their assistance in providing background information. It normally takes a long time, a good few hours, to find a hot fishing spot.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68118218-772b-4f21-a6b0-d0a86a1ce345" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-10-16 06:50:03</date>
      <author>v&amp;#233; m&amp;#225;y bay gi&amp;#225; rẻ đi h&amp;#224; nội</author>
      <email>marciagreenhalgh@hotmail.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>27.221.31.66</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s more, is the amazing snaps that are uploaded on these sites offering a visual flavor of the nightspot. You can also customize the color, font, and size of the font. They pick you up from your doorstep at the desired time and drop you at your destination at the right time so that you are never late.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bd09240e-ddb5-4c5c-ae7b-0aa9853d103f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-11-14 00:36:28</date>
      <author>cheap laptop repair nyc</author>
      <email>maisienew@bigstring.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.95.195.29</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Don&amp;#39;t attempt to do it on your own or have someone without sufficient experiences work on it. Once we repair it, we&amp;#39;ll reinforce it. (word: a few of the energy jacks are difficult to seek out however we at all times can get them!).  my page -  cheap laptop repair nyc - http://hollerfest.com/index.php/component/k2/itemlist/user/127645 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d91f539b-b20e-4aaf-8c36-c72395c76c28" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-01-17 23:19:59</date>
      <author>resa till europa</author>
      <email>nam.bolton@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.22.214.60</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I thought will besome boring old post like on almost every sites , but it sincerely compensated my time with your very good.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>