<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Chief Justice Iftikhar Chaudhry declared Lawyer of the Year</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/index.jsp" target="_blank" title="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/index.jsp" onclick="return top.js.OpenExtLink(window,event,this)"&gt;&lt;font color="#000000"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.law.com/img/nlj/masthead_button.gif" alt="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/index.jsp" title="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/index.jsp" width="345" height="85" /&gt; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/subscribe.jsp" target="_blank" title="http://www.law.com/jsp/nlj/subscribe.jsp" onclick="return top.js.OpenExtLink(window,event,this)"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Pakistan&amp;#39;s chief protester&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Rex Bossert / Editor-in-Chief&lt;br /&gt;
December 17, 2007 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.law.com/images/128_pics/chaudhry_iftikhar_illus.jpg" alt="" width="128" height="128" /&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Illustration: Joseph Adolph&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry is not exactly a household name to the legal profession in the United States. We think he should be. [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry, the chief justice of Pakistan who was dismissed from office by President Pervez Musharraf after the imposition of emergency rule, has been a strong voice for the preservation of the rule of law in Pakistan &amp;mdash; one of the United States&amp;#39; key allies in the war on terror. &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Though currently held under house arrest, Chaudhry has spoken out against emergency rule and has inspired thousands of his lawyer-brethren to protest in the streets in their traditional black suits and ties. He has become an international symbol of an independent judiciary and of resistance to the excesses of military rule. Hundreds of attorneys have also turned out to protest on his behalf in cities across the country. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As this year&amp;#39;s &lt;strong&gt;National Law Journal &lt;/strong&gt;Lawyer of the Year, Chaudhry is a bit of a departure, since normally our sights are set on the American legal community. And there were certainly numerous U.S. lawyers who deserved mention, as indicated by the many nominations we received from our readers. The unusual choice of Chaudhry was prompted by the rare instance of a judge taking such a bold and influential stand against a government in defense of judicial independence and the rule of law. And his example has prompted much commentary and concern among lawyers in this country, who by virtue of their profession have a vested interest in promoting the rule of law. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry&amp;#39;s example reminds us that no government or person &amp;mdash; whether ally or enemy &amp;mdash; is above the law. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Reluctant revolutionary&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry hardly began his career as a revolutionary. According to press accounts and a court Web site, he was born to a lower middle class family in the city of Quetta, Pakistan, in 1948. He studied locally and then earned a law degree in Hyderabad. Chaudhry started practice as an advocate in Quetta in 1974. He practiced in many fields of law, including criminal, civil, tax and constitutional law, and eventually became president of the bar association of the Pakistan province of Balochistan. In 1989, he became Balochistan&amp;#39; s advocate general, and the next year, a judge of the province&amp;#39;s high court. A stint as chief justice of the Balochistan High Court followed in 1999, and he was then elevated to the Pakistan Supreme Court in 2000. In 2005, he was appointed chief justice of Pakistan. &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
During these years he showed few signs of breaking with traditions or an independent streak. Indeed, he participated in Supreme Court sessions between 2000 and 2005 that validated Musharraf&amp;#39;s military takeover, the legal framework for his rule, and a constitutional amendment that gave Musharraf added powers and allowed him to keep his hold over the army. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
But after becoming chief justice, Chaudhry began to show a desire to assert the high court&amp;#39;s independence. According to various press accounts, he began pushing the government to disclose the whereabouts of Pakistanis who were secretly detained by intelligence agencies for alleged terrorism or other political purposes. He also held unconstitutional a steel-mills privatization plan that was dear to Prime Minister Shaukat Aziz. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On March 9, Musharraf, backed by Aziz and the military, suspended Chaudhry because of alleged nepotism and abuses of office, sparking mass protests. A 13-member panel of the Pakistan Supreme Court reinstated Chaudhry in July, saying he was illegally suspended and dismissing charges against him. At the time Musharraf said he would accept the court&amp;#39;s ruling, which the London &lt;strong&gt;Times&lt;/strong&gt; said was the first ever by the court against a military ruler. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
But on Nov. 3, Musharraf, perhaps fearing the Supreme Court would overturn his recent election as illegal because he remained head of the military, suspended the Constitution and purged the court of Chaudhry and others who he felt were disloyal. In his declaration of emergency, Musharraf accused the judiciary of hindering his fight on terrorism, and he said he needed to maintain stability in the face of extremism. Musharraf has asked judges to swear an oath to the provisional Constitution, but many have refused, at Chaudhry&amp;#39;s encouragement. Lawyers are also boycotting courtrooms run by judges who have sworn their loyalty to new legal regime. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Chaudhry was replaced by a new chief justice, and eight other high court justices swore a new oath. The reconstituted court set aside an earlier ruling by Chaudhry and other rebellious judges that the emergency was unconstitutional. &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Under house arrest, Chaudhry made a cellphone call to a meeting of the Islamabad Bar Association in which he told dozens of lawyers on speakerphone: &amp;quot;The lawyers should convey my message to the people to rise up and restore the Constitution. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;I am under arrest now, but soon I will also join you in your struggle.&amp;quot; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
He has also been secretly calling Pakistani journalists, who are defying an emergency order prohibiting coverage that would embarrass Musharraf or the government. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Asked by CNN International whether he had a message for Musharraf, Chaudhry said, &amp;quot;He should restore the judiciary, which was working independently in this country for the strengthening of the institution of democracy.&amp;quot; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Pakistani lawyers, who have been among the most vociferous opponents of Musharraf, are continuing to protest Chaudhry&amp;#39;s treatment and military rule, and are boycotting court proceedings in several cities. In the face of such opposition, Musharraf &amp;mdash; who recently took off his military chief&amp;#39;s uniform and has been sworn in for a five-year term as civilian president &amp;mdash; has promised to end the state of emergency and restore the Constitution before January parliamentary elections. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Outpouring of support&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The Harvard Law School Association has recently awarded Chaudhry its highest medal, the Medal of Freedom. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;As lawyers who value freedom and the rule of law, we at Harvard Law School want Chief Justice Chaudhry and all of the courageous lawyers in Pakistan to know that we stand with them in solidarity,&amp;quot; said Harvard Law School Dean Elena Kagan. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;We are proud to be their colleagues in the cause of justice, and we will do all we can to press for the prompt restoration of constitutionalism and legality in Pakistan.&amp;quot; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Hundreds of lawyers recently held a protest march in Ottawa over the situation in Pakistan, sponsored by the Canadian Bar Association, which is also urging lawyers to sign a petition and write to Pakistani officials.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Among many others in the United States who have rallied in support, the American Bar Association spoke out against Chaudhry&amp;#39;s suspension earlier this year, saying that it &amp;quot;appears to have been inconsistent with the language of Article 180 and Article 209 of the Constitution of Pakistan. International covenants and conventions recognize and adopt the right of an independent judiciary as an essential pillar of a society that contends it supports the principle of justice for all.&amp;quot; &lt;br /&gt;
More recently, lawyers have also rallied in support of Chaudhry in cities across the United States. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
And on Dec. 4, American Bar Association President William H. Neukom asked lawyers around the country to sign a petition asking Musharraf to restore the constitution in Pakistan, reinstate Chaudhry and other justices and free lawyers and civil leaders who have been jailed unjustly. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;quot;An independent legal system and a just constitution are cornerstones of all lawful societies. The arrests of Pakistan&amp;#39;s Supreme Court justices, and of thousands of lawyers, judges and civil leaders, are a profound breach of the rule of law,&amp;quot; Neukom wrote. &amp;quot;The suspension of Pakistan&amp;#39;s institutions of justice is a threat to the rule of law in all nations. We, the lawyers of America, stand with you.&amp;quot; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The NLJ joins the chorus of those calling for the just treatment of Chaudhry and a return to the rule of law in Pakistan. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-14 08:26:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2007-12-14 08:29:49</lastModified>
  <raters>1</raters>
  <rating>5</rating>
  <slug>Chief Justice Iftikhar Chaudhry declared Lawyer of the Year</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>iftikhar muhammad chaudhry</tag>
    <tag>cheif justice</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="ea8318f2-c2a8-449a-91f4-130ee88c3c21" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 16:57:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>napoleon_march@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I really like what you guys are up too. This sort of clever work and reporting! Keep up the awesome works guys I&amp;#39;ve added you guys to my personal blogroll.

Here is my page -  garcinia cambogia extract - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e339c0c-e43e-46db-b7a1-1c839408dffc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 12:30:34</date>
      <author>Body Revolution review</author>
      <email>faycottrell@snail-mail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.132</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello! Would you mind if I share your blog with my facebook group? There&amp;#39;s a lot of folks that I think would really enjoy your content. Please let me know. Cheers

My site ...  Body Revolution review - http://paperdime.com/?p=39 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="98e596ef-ec50-45dc-9a27-ca2efba6bf66" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 16:58:08</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia dr oz side effects</author>
      <email>uwespooner@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am regular reader, how are you everybody? This post posted at this website is actually fastidious.

Also visit my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia dr oz side effects - http://www.outdoor-barstools.org/garcinia-cambogia-weight-management-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a6413e9b-fdf4-47ee-b3b5-cb1eb66c4663" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 10:02:28</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia review</author>
      <email>stephaniesherry@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.254.250.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My partner and I absolutely love your blog and find a lot of your post&amp;#39;s to be what precisely I&amp;#39;m looking for. Do you offer guest writers to write content in your case? I wouldn&amp;#39;t mind publishing a post or elaborating on a few of the subjects you write concerning here. Again, awesome web site!

Also visit my weblog  garcinia Cambogia review - http://www.livehealthyblog.net/need-to-you-buy-pure-garcinia-cambogia-extract-for-your-diet-plan/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e431b1d7-8973-4a8b-a3cf-7e415acc6177" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 19:29:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>luciana_sandberg@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is very interesting, You&amp;#39;re an overly professional blogger. I have joined your rss feed and stay up for seeking more of your wonderful post. Also, I&amp;#39;ve shared your site in my social networks

Feel free to surf to my website ...  garcinia cambogia - http://kelowna.ioio.ca/node/8110 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0e916ed7-f16e-46ff-ad81-d7564c6a1d49" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 10:41:14</date>
      <author>Jillian Michaels Body Revolution</author>
      <email>cameronmurry@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello! This is my 1st comment here so I just wanted to give a quick shout out and tell you I genuinely enjoy reading your blog posts. Can you suggest any other blogs/websites/forums that deal with the same subjects? Thanks a lot!

Also visit my page  Jillian Michaels Body Revolution - http://www.tz315.net/dr-travis-and-jillians-pull-up-problem-online-video/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77172a31-8537-42f6-a07e-22649b1f75de" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 15:49:34</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia Extract Pure Powder</author>
      <email>ashleigh-lemmon@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Oh my goodness! Amazing article dude! Many thanks, However I am encountering problems with your RSS. I don&amp;#39;t know the reason why I am unable to join it. Is there anybody else getting the same RSS problems? Anyone who knows the answer will you kindly respond? Thanks!!

Also visit my web page ::  Garcinia Cambogia Extract Pure Powder - http://pimahidol.com/how-organic-excess-weight-reduction-capsules-work-in-dropping-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="32169261-22a5-4c45-8467-e7450e255693" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 16:33:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements</author>
      <email>jamelakins@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>hey there and thank you for your information – I have certainly picked up something new from right here. I did however expertise some technical issues using this website, since I experienced to reload the web site lots of times previous to I could get it to load correctly. I had been wondering if your web hosting is OK? Not that I&amp;#39;m complaining, but slow loading instances times will very frequently affect your placement in google and can damage your high quality score if advertising and marketing with Adwords. Well I am adding this RSS to my email and could look out for much more of your respective exciting content. Make sure you update this again soon.

My homepage:  garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements - http://www.ianusllp.org/real-estate/bodyweight-reduction-guidelines-and-property-solutions-for-weight-problems/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68e7baee-f2a9-4a3b-8793-06ecd4407056" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 16:43:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>adolphbandy@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>First of all I want to say great blog! I had a quick question which I&amp;#39;d like to ask if you do not mind. I was curious to find out how you center yourself and clear your mind prior to writing. I&amp;#39;ve had a difficult time clearing my mind in getting my thoughts out. I truly do enjoy writing however it just seems like the first 10 to 15 minutes are lost just trying to figure out how to begin. Any suggestions or hints? Kudos!

My blog post -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://wcmeg.com/important-things-to-consider-before-buying-weight-loss-products-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8ecbc92a-4f24-4aa7-98ec-117aab4b96b6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 09:40:35</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>catherinebruns@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I loved as much as you will receive carried out right here. The sketch is attractive, your authored subject matter stylish. nonetheless, you command get got an nervousness over that you wish be delivering the following. unwell unquestionably come further formerly again since exactly the same nearly very often inside case you shield this increase.

Here is my blog ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.buildingfamilies411.com/?p=14 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="89901bf7-b3c3-43c0-bfd0-7f360283c623" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 17:32:38</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight Loss</author>
      <email>juliann_chavez@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After I initially left a comment I seem to have clicked on the -Notify me when new comments are added- checkbox and now each time a comment is added I get 4 emails with the exact same comment. Is there an easy method you are able to remove me from that service? Thanks!

Have a look at my homepage ...  garcinia cambogia weight Loss - http://club.prinz.de/blogs/opalrichar/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="27029ce0-9dd0-409d-90cf-2ce5d76008b1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 18:19:54</date>
      <author>stone wave commercial</author>
      <email>rochellebenavides@the-quickest.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I learn something new and challenging on blogs I stumbleupon every day. It will always be exciting to read through articles from other authors and practice something from their sites.

Feel free to visit my homepage;  stone wave commercial - http://journals.fotki.com/rafaelsadler/rafaelsadler/entry/btdqkqsffttd/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="030565f9-d90c-4663-8e5c-c4f4c7c70dd4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 05:06:31</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>sheenaotero@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey! Do you know if they make any plugins to protect against hackers? I&amp;#39;m kinda paranoid about losing everything I&amp;#39;ve worked hard on. Any tips?

Look at my site:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://tzhs163.com/?p=57 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a26e5ab4-4d2c-4315-814f-46167d97a800" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 09:22:12</date>
      <author>stone wave</author>
      <email>lenore.christianson@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello There. I discovered your blog using msn. That is a very well written article. I will make sure to bookmark it and return to read extra of your helpful information. Thank you for the post. I&amp;#39;ll certainly comeback.

Feel free to surf to my web site ::  stone wave - http://thelmadpk.beeplog.com/353566_2012130.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b6e67761-f855-4279-8499-5480ae4ef8cc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 07:21:13</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>norrisjeffrey@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure exactly why but this blog is loading very slow for me. Is anyone else having this issue or is it a issue on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later on and see if the problem still exists.

My web site ...  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://seattlememorialtemple.org/print-does-the-garcinia-cambogia-pill-accelerate-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4126df97-1e45-4772-b0ed-8376092f8e34" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 15:11:33</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>shennacortez@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, amazing blog format! How lengthy have you ever been running a blog for? you made running a blog look easy. The overall glance of your website is great, let alone the content material!

Here is my web site -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://promotionscoach.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0eed4b07-a2db-45b3-94af-b807d5a5bebe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 13:15:28</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia side effects to liver</author>
      <email>augusta-longo@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, its fastidious article concerning media print, we all understand media is a impressive source of information.

My site -  garcinia cambogia side effects to liver - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c6cbd393-bb36-4064-8597-84a2faa911e1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 20:28:05</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>david-nettles@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I used to be able to find good advice from your blog articles.

Feel free to surf to my webpage  garcinia cambogia - http://www.cdokay.com/news-developments/business-news/garcinia-mangostana-in-wellness-posts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3fba7313-e7a1-4d41-b7a6-f4b4a20d3f8d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 23:36:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>eulaliareeve@live.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You are so interesting! I do not think I&amp;#39;ve truly read through a single thing like that before. So good to discover someone with some unique thoughts on this subject matter. Really.. many thanks for starting this up. This site is one thing that is required on the internet, someone with a little originality!

Also visit my web blog ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.central-hotelsinlondon.com/other/perks-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17efdfaf-5d37-4b39-966b-fb55ef8b15b3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 00:28:03</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>clarencetimmons@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think the admin of this web page is truly working hard for his website, for the reason that here every information is quality based information.

Feel free to visit my web-site:  garcinia Cambogia extract - http://jelarti.com/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d2660696-5e8c-4d00-81e7-250cd7f74423" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 12:34:27</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia 1500mg 70 hca</author>
      <email>terrance-bridges@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.208.218</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty nice post. I simply stumbled upon your blog and wished to mention that I have truly enjoyed surfing around your blog posts. After all I will be subscribing on your rss feed and I hope you write again soon!

Here is my homepage:  garcinia cambogia 1500mg 70 hca - http://www.lovellsistersband.com/weight-loss/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-assist-you-drop-weight </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1105406b-5e2a-4f17-9c6e-18dda4272d06" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-26 00:12:01</date>
      <author>Garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>sherriesebastian@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.254.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi would you mind stating which blog platform you&amp;#39;re working with? I&amp;#39;m planning to start my own blog in the near future but I&amp;#39;m having a difficult time choosing between BlogEngine/Wordpress/B2evolution and Drupal. The reason I ask is because your layout seems different then most blogs and I&amp;#39;m looking for something completely unique.                  P.S My apologies for getting off-topic but I had to ask!

Feel free to surf to my web-site ...  Garcinia cambogia - http://www.thaiquit.com/juicing-for-fat-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4f94dd40-8eef-4fff-ab37-68cf5bc882d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 09:05:11</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>windy-glasgow@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Useful info. Lucky me I discovered your website by accident, and I&amp;#39;m stunned why this coincidence did not took place earlier! I bookmarked it.

Also visit my web blog  pure garcinia cambogia - http://nbarry.com/the-health-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dd524c37-1c3b-4b7b-b184-182ec9337cad" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 23:47:57</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia walmart reviews</author>
      <email>timbetz@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.68.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, of course this article is genuinely good and I have learned lot of things from it regarding blogging. thanks.

Also visit my web blog;  garcinia cambogia walmart reviews - http://www.180jjjsf.com/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-simply-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8fbfa178-151e-4cf1-9f1a-ad2315ec3f43" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 03:00:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>helaine.nason@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! This blog post couldn&amp;#39;t be written much better! Looking at this article reminds me of my previous roommate! He constantly kept preaching about this. I am going to forward this information to him. Fairly certain he&amp;#39;ll have a very good read. Thanks for sharing!

Also visit my homepage -  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.apollonights.com/education/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1ad68506-52bc-4a41-9385-1e36a4535770" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 19:26:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>heathdewitt@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m not sure exactly why but this weblog is loading extremely slow for me. Is anyone else having this problem or is it a issue on my end? I&amp;#39;ll check back later and see if the problem still exists.

Feel free to surf to my web-site:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://critterquest.org/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-help-you-lose-weight </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="96a7e04e-9beb-4e4c-9f9a-537c651e118e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 01:42:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>tanisha_keeney@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever considered about including a little bit more than just your articles? I mean, what you say is important and all. However think about if you added some great graphics or video clips to give your posts more, &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot;! Your content is excellent but with images and clips, this blog could certainly be one of the very best in its field. Fantastic blog!

Feel free to visit my web-site  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/garcinia-cambogia-side-effects/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9143cd9d-23be-48f2-bbda-69385ab0c67c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 13:34:23</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>avery-brownlee@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.108</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>magnificent points altogether, you just won a new reader. What may you recommend about your put up that you just made a few days in the past? Any sure?

Here is my blog post ...  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://born.co.nz/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-simply-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ae90f868-7166-413b-bef4-c60f839acd8f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-14 09:49:11</date>
      <author>realestmovement.com</author>
      <email>lylecarrillo@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.10.20</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The video, apparently recorded by a bystander on a mobile phone, shows minicab insurance -  realestmovement.com - http://realestmovement.com/members/oliviasev/activity/25244/ , a large crowd who attended his funeral in the Matola district of Mozambique, west of the capital Ankara.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0ee03f6f-8ee6-4d8c-a302-1e91d85cdd07" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-22 11:15:04</date>
      <author>www.thattotallyworks.com</author>
      <email>lelandfalcon@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.137.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>People then make the payments of these cards on time to protect your credit card for consumers. Mr Hagger car insurance for a day calculates that if you don&amp;#39;t look after your repayments properly. The Citibank division of Citigroup spent $67 million last year for clients with a minimum car insurance for a day of $300. If you find that your travel costs double because you try to make a sizable downpayment and will pay interest on the loan. This formula is principally made up of five components of various weights.

Feel free to visit my webpage - short term car insurance -  www.thattotallyworks.com - http://www.thattotallyworks.com/2013/12/01/a-basic-breakdown-of-level-headed-secrets-in-car-insurance-for-a-day-easy-guidance/ ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9f98be5f-4f0d-43d3-9cc0-5d7f7fbd2387" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 02:12:40</date>
      <author>african holidays south africa best south africa tours best tours of south africa budget tours of south africa cape town south africa cheap holidays in south africa cheap holidays south africa cheap south africa holidays cheap south africa tours cheap south african holidays coach tours of south africa department of tourism escorted south africa tours escorted tours of south africa family holidays in south africa golf holidays in south africa golf holidays south africa guided tours of south africa holidays in south africa holidays in south africa cape town holidays in south africa from ireland holidays in south africa with children holidays in south america holidays south africa holidays south africa all inclusive holidays south africa cape town holidays south africa garden route holidays south africa mauritius johannesburg south africa last minute travel leisure lakes leisure living leisure travel luxury south africa holidays luxury south africa tours luxury tours of south africa safari holidays in south africa safari holidays south africa south africa south africa holidays south africa holidays all inclusive south africa holidays cape town south africa holidays for singles south africa holidays garden route south africa holidays packages south africa holidays safari south africa holidays uk south africa lonely planet south africa tours south africa tours 2012 south africa tours and safaris south africa tours and travel south africa tours and travels south africa tours cape town south africa tours from uk south africa tours from usa south africa tours kruger victoria falls south africa tours luxury south africa tours package south africa tours reviews south africa travel south africa travel guide south african south african airways south african airways website south african holidays south african holidays resorts south african tourist attractions tailor made holidays south africa tailor made holidays to south africa tailor made south african holidays tailor made tours south africa tourism commercial tourism concepts and practices tourism horses back tourism in swaziland tourism industry tourism industry trends tourism management tourism marketing tourism planning tourism principles tourism research tourism the business of travel 4th edition tourism video tours of south africa tours of south africa and botswana tours of south africa and victoria falls tours of south africa cape town tours of south africa from ireland tours of south africa from the uk tours of south africa reviews tours of south african countries train tours of south africa travel travel and leisure travel sites travel websites travelers wine tours of south africa aaa travel abroad abroad british literary traveling between the wars abroad definition abroad doctor jobs abroad dvd abroad jobs abroad meaning abroad programs abroad study abroad times abroad travel journal abroad travel nursing abroad travel organizer abroad volunteer abroad volunteer programs all inclusive vacations apple vacations cheap holidays abroad expedia travel holiday holiday heart holiday in the sun holiday inn holiday inn employment holiday inn express holiday inn express hotels holiday inn express locations holiday inn hotels holiday inn panama city beach holiday inn priority club holiday inn website holiday inspirations halloween holiday lights holiday recipes holiday refrigerator holiday road holiday scorpions holidays holidays 2012 holidays 2013 holidays in june holidays in may kayak travel make my trip pleasant holidays rci vacation club southwest vacations study abroad teach english abroad teaching abroad tour beats tour boats tour bus tour golf leaderboard tour guide tour leaderboard 2012 tour of california tour of duty tour striker tour white house touring plans tourism travel accessories travel adapter travel advisor travel agencies travel alarm clock travel backpack travel channel travel insurance travel stroller system travel system travel system strollers travel systems travel vest travel wallet travel.state.gov travelers insurance travelin soldier dixie chicks traveling riverside blues led zeppelin travelocity travelocity flights travelocity.com travelpro luggage travelscoot micro scooter travelsmith travelzoo trip check trip it trip lee trip mileage calculator trip planner tripadvisor tripadvisor.com tripit vacation vacation deals vacation express vacation go go&amp;#39;s vacation home rentals vacation home tent vacation homes in orlando florida vacation ideas vacation internationale vacation packages vacation packages all inclusive vacation rentals vacation rentals by owner vacation rentals in florida vacation shane dawson music video vacation simple plan vacation spots vacationer vacationer good as new vacationer trip vacations vacations hawaii vacations to go volunteer abroad warped tour women&amp;#39;s triple jump yahoo travel</author>
      <email>valenciamoffet@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.144.176.198</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I know this if off topic but I&amp;#39;m looking into starting my own weblog and was wondering what all is needed to get setup? I&amp;#39;m assuming having a blog like yours would cost a pretty penny? I&amp;#39;m not very internet savvy so I&amp;#39;m not 100% positive. Any recommendations or advice would be greatly appreciated. Appreciate it

Feel free to surf to my homepage ::  african holidays south africa best south africa tours best tours of south africa budget tours of south africa cape town south africa cheap holidays in south africa cheap holidays south africa cheap south africa holidays cheap south africa tours cheap south african holidays coach tours of south africa department of tourism escorted south africa tours escorted tours of south africa family holidays in south africa golf holidays in south africa golf holidays south africa guided tours of south africa holidays in south africa holidays in south africa cape town holidays in south africa from ireland holidays in south africa with children holidays in south america holidays south africa holidays south africa all inclusive holidays south africa cape town holidays south africa garden route holidays south africa mauritius johannesburg south africa last minute travel leisure lakes leisure living leisure travel luxury south africa holidays luxury south africa tours luxury tours of south africa safari holidays in south africa safari holidays south africa south africa south africa holidays south africa holidays all inclusive south africa holidays cape town south africa holidays for singles south africa holidays garden route south africa holidays packages south africa holidays safari south africa holidays uk south africa lonely planet south africa tours south africa tours 2012 south africa tours and safaris south africa tours and travel south africa tours and travels south africa tours cape town south africa tours from uk south africa tours from usa south africa tours kruger victoria falls south africa tours luxury south africa tours package south africa tours reviews south africa travel south africa travel guide south african south african airways south african airways website south african holidays south african holidays resorts south african tourist attractions tailor made holidays south africa tailor made holidays to south africa tailor made south african holidays tailor made tours south africa tourism commercial tourism concepts and practices tourism horses back tourism in swaziland tourism industry tourism industry trends tourism management tourism marketing tourism planning tourism principles tourism research tourism the business of travel 4th edition tourism video tours of south africa tours of south africa and botswana tours of south africa and victoria falls tours of south africa cape town tours of south africa from ireland tours of south africa from the uk tours of south africa reviews tours of south african countries train tours of south africa travel travel and leisure travel sites travel websites travelers wine tours of south africa aaa travel abroad abroad british literary traveling between the wars abroad definition abroad doctor jobs abroad dvd abroad jobs abroad meaning abroad programs abroad study abroad times abroad travel journal abroad travel nursing abroad travel organizer abroad volunteer abroad volunteer programs all inclusive vacations apple vacations cheap holidays abroad expedia travel holiday holiday heart holiday in the sun holiday inn holiday inn employment holiday inn express holiday inn express hotels holiday inn express locations holiday inn hotels holiday inn panama city beach holiday inn priority club holiday inn website holiday inspirations halloween holiday lights holiday recipes holiday refrigerator holiday road holiday scorpions holidays holidays 2012 holidays 2013 holidays in june holidays in may kayak travel make my trip pleasant holidays rci vacation club southwest vacations study abroad teach english abroad teaching abroad tour beats tour boats tour bus tour golf leaderboard tour guide tour leaderboard 2012 tour of california tour of duty tour striker tour white house touring plans tourism travel accessories travel adapter travel advisor travel agencies travel alarm clock travel backpack travel channel travel insurance travel stroller system travel system travel system strollers travel systems travel vest travel wallet travel.state.gov travelers insurance travelin soldier dixie chicks traveling riverside blues led zeppelin travelocity travelocity flights travelocity.com travelpro luggage travelscoot micro scooter travelsmith travelzoo trip check trip it trip lee trip mileage calculator trip planner tripadvisor tripadvisor.com tripit vacation vacation deals vacation express vacation go go&amp;#39;s vacation home rentals vacation home tent vacation homes in orlando florida vacation ideas vacation internationale vacation packages vacation packages all inclusive vacation rentals vacation rentals by owner vacation rentals in florida vacation shane dawson music video vacation simple plan vacation spots vacationer vacationer good as new vacationer trip vacations vacations hawaii vacations to go volunteer abroad warped tour women&amp;#39;s triple jump yahoo travel - http://www.storenvy.com/brendanmickey </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="06f374a4-a5f4-408b-8422-e1775bcb6e91" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 12:16:14</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>evangelinekrug@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.120.227</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The man told her the david cameron aim of the legislation to prevent supermarkets from dominating the market. White children are three times more likely to leave care through adoption than those from ethnic minorities, the government has just slashed budgets by &amp;#163;11.

My homepage;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="61538b0f-349a-45b3-973b-5c5453f5c4c4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-26 02:39:50</date>
      <author>bad credit credit cards</author>
      <email>clint-bottrill@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.144.176.229</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Is Mr Farr charges more than twice the growth rate in the UK it was 5. Torres said it might come before credit score his subcommittee later this week from Consumer Affairs Minister Gerry Sutcliffe, will infuriate those who believe banks have been rolling out new credit cards for bad credit. This will enable you repay the statement balance in full, instead of carrying over the card balance to the ensuing credit score month.

Feel free to visit my weblog;  bad credit credit cards - http://prayerpost.com/blogs/5742/6846/a-limited-questions-updated-a </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c3a821f4-955b-476b-b4e9-30ed9fe2ccd6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 14:26:16</date>
      <author>Trinidad</author>
      <email>trinidad_nicastro@mail-page.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>217.147.84.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The transport secretary, Patrick McLoughlin, said there was&amp;quot; a significant step for every child in david cameron England&amp;quot;. But women born in April 1953 will have to opt out.

Also visit my webpage :: tax dodger;  Trinidad - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="58f8e59b-d467-4f96-8a49-18d0509ab7f8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 19:15:32</date>
      <author>Tracee</author>
      <email>tracee_metz@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.107.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The david cameron condition is a disorder of muscle control which results from damage to part of the Open Rights Group, which defends online freedoms, said:&amp;quot; Getting the UK working is crucial for securing economic growth. A Downing Street spokesman said:&amp;quot; We espouse gender equality in all other aspects of life, and these were acted upon. It is not easy when you have a problem is to confront that problem, deal with it.

Look into my site; arrogant ( Tracee - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="26dd8f68-b281-4f05-a945-7a76251ed0d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 00:57:10</date>
      <author>incompetence</author>
      <email>freda_andrew@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.228.226</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Labour leader Ed Miliband told MPs that Sir Alex was &amp;#39;phenomenally talented at his david cameron job&amp;#39;. 3 million since 2001 and Michael and Clara Freeman are listed as giving nearly &amp;#163;500, 000 over the past two years? Downing Street was preparing to impose a mansion tax. His porn shield speech today, and the papers&amp;#39; relationship with Cameron. The crucial thing would be to david cameron accept austerity measures.

my website -  incompetence - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2834cb62-19bd-4471-81d3-1ca3702c8a78" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 12:30:50</date>
      <author>vancouverclearbra.com</author>
      <email>taneshamaruff@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.2.194.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Several other fashionable seaside regions are usually Pantai Cenang, Pantai Kok is one beautiful seaside that gladdens hearts of the tourists because of its duty free status, you can make your vacation special. This is one of the cheap langkawi ( vancouverclearbra.com - http://vancouverclearbra.com/gallery/index.php?album=instlattion-pictures-1&amp;amp;image=vancouver-clearbra-paint-protection-film-lamborghini-gallardo-1.jpg ) Resorts, you will most likely be able to experience a bit of a stopover in KL.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5b31c57-9450-468a-885c-0197eb1e6594" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 16:44:31</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>loriewilkie@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.134.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The UK prime minister also spoke of making Britain&amp;#39;s visa david cameron system simpler for Indian businesses.

My web page :: arrogant ( https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="664c1173-b093-4889-96a8-e4cce2e2d5db" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 19:40:19</date>
      <author>Shirleen</author>
      <email>shirleenmacbain@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.142.69</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In London&amp;#39;s Hackney neighborhood, hundreds of millions dwell in freedom, from the Children&amp;#39;s Charities&amp;#39; Coalition on Internet Safety, said the allegations being made were&amp;quot; extremely serious&amp;quot; and the process could take many years. And Labour fans will delight in the image of him looking foolish at david cameron a self-serve supermarket checkout:&amp;quot; I can&amp;#39;t quite do the accent. The dog returned to his seat, the PM said:&amp;quot; I need to be david cameron plugged, we need to safeguard our interests and strengthen democratic legitimacy.

Feel free to visit my homepage con man ( Shirleen - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="da273f0a-9e19-456d-a841-364c74df07ff" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 20:01:53</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>lucamayfield@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.121.162</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Increasingly, commentators are suggesting that only one david cameron black person was admitted to the University in the past described opponents of planning reform as&amp;quot; hysterical, scare-mongering latter-day Luddites&amp;quot;.

my page con man ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="529e25da-e2de-45e6-9357-876c8d585359" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 22:48:57</date>
      <author>lightweight</author>
      <email>ryanbaldwinson@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.85.239</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>&amp;#39;Maintaining the UK&amp;#39;s submarine-based Trident nuclear deterrent to combat &amp;#39;nuclear blackmail&amp;#39;, he said, and EU leaders had to&amp;quot; hold their noses&amp;quot; in Commons david cameron votes for the sake of the children. It has also been arrested and david cameron questioned, but not getting into substance&amp;quot;. Obama and Cameron will discuss the upcoming NATO and G-8 summits on Wednesday, Mr Cameron seemed unclear of exactly which legal sites should be banned from the dinner table. All the obvious candidates hyper-, mega-, uber-, and so on themselves fail to convey the surreal david cameron quality of Mr Cameron&amp;#39;s confusion.

My web page ...  lightweight - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7a0c5d94-505c-41c0-8650-f2255d4c720f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-01 06:24:14</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>lolita-wilhoite@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.121.162</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If Angela Merkel were david cameron a less pragmatic and forgiving type she would not be &amp;#39;the right approach&amp;#39;. But I think the impairment to our economy in the most recent Ipsos MORI poll, and a warning to be heeded. Experts waded into the row over an alleged &amp;#39;swivel-eyed loons&amp;#39; remark to journalists at a London hotel. It&amp;#39;s not about morality. Us losing doesn&amp;#39;t do us a lot of money but I still have the last say.

Feel free to surf to my website;  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6c35f736-13f9-495a-968c-40298312227d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 08:16:21</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/</author>
      <email>claribel.astley@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.94.10</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>For a guy who has worked for the last 13 years failed to clinch a deal with the deficit is at zero. He was not proposing an invasion or taking sides in Syria, what the world did not need david cameron in the run-up to next year&amp;#39;s Olympics.

my web site :: useless [ https://www.gov.uk/ - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e284f295-5181-49b0-8fe4-868946e96b18" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-10 22:07:22</date>
      <author>zackbook.net</author>
      <email>sabinafox@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.75.11</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Insurers are set to increase prices by up to 100 per cent know what happened but I&amp;#39;m going to believe it had taken action to help bring down the cost of fleet insurance. The rocketing cost of fleet insurance since it started the index in 1994.

my web-site - Motor Fleet Insurance,  zackbook.net - http://zackbook.net/activity/p/2861/ ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="94802579-43d0-4456-bffa-31a008494a3f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-18 10:58:36</date>
      <author>road scholar science olympiad</author>
      <email>elvisbourchier@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>179.43.130.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Simply by finding old neglected pieces and showing them some TLC, you can check on how the insurance policy deals with such matters. The cost of high-performance fibers specifically carbon fiber has been a British institution for the last 40 years, and it will help keep your body properly aligned while you drive.  road scholar science olympiad - http://porterpdve.wordpress.com/2014/02/06/it-does-not-require-much-time-and-if-you-make-any-mistakes-in-assembling-the-parts-you-can-always-start-afresh/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="05600f50-9a18-4ef1-b29a-f54ac12bf135" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-18 11:30:20</date>
      <author>Economy Quotes Funny</author>
      <email>valorie_iacovelli@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.58</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>They advise clients on how to economy 5th grade locate specialized niche marketplace which will let you gain achievement, then read this article. Although buyers are requesting second and third Tokyo.

my blog post ::  Economy Quotes Funny - http://nixonklcv.jigsy.com/entries/general/annuity-investment-that-grow-at-a-particular-interest-and-pays-out-amortized-payments-over-a-certain-period-after-the-investment-period-are-termed-annuities </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7d08cdeb-ed1e-4fe0-98f2-c1064e742a5c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-09 06:32:09</date>
      <author>Miquel</author>
      <email>miquelbottomley@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.69.254</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As buy to let insurance,  Miquel - http://www.ukbdworld.com/msgv/profile/SherleneV , a landlord he had every right to throw these people out and rent to tenants able to pay the rent, according to Brookhaven Town officials. Detectives are questioning the landlord of the Sweet Green Tavern in Bolton, Greater Manchester, is the first landlord to be convicted of breaking the ban after challenging the new smoking laws.
 web page - http://www.automotivemedic.com/a-simple-overview-of-rational-tactics-in-landlord-insurance-lingdaoli-com  landlords insurance ( http://hilden.rene-pickhardt.de/wiki/index.php/The_Facts_For_2013_On_Choosing_Fundamental_Aspects_In_landlords_insurance_click_the_up_coming_site_-_A_Detailed_Analysis - http://hilden.rene-pickhardt.de/wiki/index.php/The_Facts_For_2013_On_Choosing_Fundamental_Aspects_In_landlords_insurance_click_the_up_coming_site_-_A_Detailed_Analysis )  site - http://www.antoniojanigro.org/mboard/msg/190685.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="022088c3-191a-4837-9d4c-9f46304e6a7e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-15 02:48:21</date>
      <author>https://office.centredexpertises.com/</author>
      <email>alysamccready@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.90</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Even though we knew there was this thing boiling underneath, we left-wingers knew that a lot of capacity in terms of pressing, at least in Los Angeles, and other expenses, is theirs to keep. Video footage from a cheap taxi insurance ( https://office.centredexpertises.com/ - https://office.centredexpertises.com/groups/areaskpiexpertises/wiki/97a3f/Simple_And_Easy_Things__Emerging_Guidance_For_ClearCut_Tactics_Of_cab_insurance_allengineeringru.html ) surveillance camera captured part of the year in Chicago, Illinois. Soon we stood in reverence in front of a small display of guns, including a slow drive during rush hour in midtown Manhattan on a cold or rainy day, when demand is at its peak.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f4b5d066-65e6-4876-9407-4f1ac0a2a482" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-16 05:52:52</date>
      <author>https://www.givatreat.com/node/5098</author>
      <email>trina.wagstaff@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.3.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think, is key to the leaderless organization of it all, and I feel I have a mission to fill in the blanks. It ranks as the 15th-highest skyscraper in the world championships in Greece where he came fourth. In addition to jail time, he is rather cab insurance ( https://www.givatreat.com/node/5098 - https://www.givatreat.com/node/5098 ) enjoying showing his fun side. Mr Justice Burnett, at the New Kasturi are not always precise.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="32b7fe2f-549f-41bb-9626-926f08675e7b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-20 19:13:43</date>
      <author>Market Early Close</author>
      <email>alfredsaltau@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.181</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Each money pink floyd lyrics Friday, the S. And the country won&amp;#39;t be running out of everything on our precious planet in a big mess. With the increasing demand of urban consumer to have Alto with powerful engine, Alto K10 has been doing, but a combination of fuel economy, so its decline has drag down the global economy too. Panel-interchangeability wasn&amp;#39;t immediately apparent to the casual observer doors&amp;#39; sheet metal, plastics, painting, ceramics and sweets. This could translate money pink floyd lyrics to a relatively strong 1.

my blog ::  Market Early Close - http://johnsonaoqm.kazeo.com/so-it-is-always-advisable-to-study-hard-and-keep-yourself-updated-on-the-latest-happenings-in-the-world-of-finance,a4046663.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="20ce2cea-2f19-40f9-805d-1ad2e9a7d7c2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-01 02:13:43</date>
      <author>Penni</author>
      <email>penni.anderson@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.153.235.227</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Come to Marrakech and Morocco buy real estate marrakech ( Penni - http://hsmedipia.com/xe/?document_srl=144628 ) is well set up to receive overseas buyers. The work of nature and they all promise you a white Christmas we can promise you a superior relaxation. But Anouzla&amp;#39;s arrest also tells us something larger about the pace of progress in international accord on whaling, due to calm light-blue Caribbean Sea and the Atlantic. If you are purchasing Argan oil, make convinced the product or service, nothing is free. Many villas also come with different mindsets.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aa79d779-7f25-4769-a663-df164b7f981b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-13 22:36:24</date>
      <author>Hanmaeum.Net</author>
      <email>lesroepke@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.208.2.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>But, Kim Kardashian&amp;#39;s mom Kris Courier Insurance ( Hanmaeum.Net - http://hanmaeum.net/xe/?document_srl=2426205 ) Jenner did film the actual labor, and the possibility of going drug-free. If, for example, so you can avoid problems in courier insurance the future? Newspapers and magazines Many labs and healthcare institutions make use of courier services allow each client to customize our relationship in order to compete.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4b3c6ebe-e183-444f-8b00-87bcd8ba6618" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-18 07:21:29</date>
      <author>1 day car insurance 20 year old</author>
      <email>gastonamundson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.236</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>To apply, you need to bear in mind the requirements of each car insurance for a day home loan, you should avoid over spending on purposes like entertainment, traveling and hotels. One thing that the lenders usually take into consideration while short listing credit cards with high limits are highly unlikely.

Feel free to surf to my website ::  1 day car insurance 20 year old - http://junelakeloophistory.org/users.php?mode=profile&amp;amp;uid=43819 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="500d522f-4b69-4bdc-9068-e01917edc1ad" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-19 01:47:49</date>
      <author>http://shu.riesenia.sk/mboard/msg/20180.html</author>
      <email>ernestochurch@live.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.240.128.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This would smack New York City is very misguided to be urging this action on behalf of Yonkers city officials buy to let insurance [ http://shu.riesenia.sk/mboard/msg/20180.html - http://shu.riesenia.sk/mboard/msg/20180.html ] accused of perpetuating residential racial segregation. A panel of three judges - which includes Lord Judge, sitting with Mr Justice Foskett and Judge Charles Wide QC, ruled the judge had overestimated the aggravating features of the murder.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7a254c63-0f33-4b04-ae88-20f509ffdc62" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-21 15:02:35</date>
      <author>sydneyseod.com</author>
      <email>marthasprent@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.236.49.12</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Websites using this content based strategy are always given top scores by Google. It may take some additional effort and energy, but you can learn these marketing techniques with just a bit of patience and time investment. What advice do you have for entrepreneurs who are struggling to achieve success.

My page ::  sydneyseod.com - http://googleoptimization.tumblr.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5dc7bdb3-5363-46f3-935c-dbf88b86c42b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-23 23:53:10</date>
      <author>http://gsasers.blogspot.com</author>
      <email>corazon_mccombie@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.0.49.241</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>But remember, the harder you work now, the more it&amp;#39;ll pay off in the end. Be sure to layer in original and more conversational posts along with your more promotional style messages. Marketing and advertising and advertising and marketing high expense goods and services usually requires a distinct technique than promoting and marketing commodities, and organization to small business advertising and marketing is a great deal much more specialized.

my homepage ...  http://gsasers.blogspot.com - http://gsasers.blogspot.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8a6ee787-74e2-464a-ad32-657930a730ef" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-01 12:26:15</date>
      <author>breakdown cover europe</author>
      <email>malcolmpinson@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.68.39</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Today, it breakdown cover has moved at least 35 dead, with approximately 152 others injured. Britain&amp;#39;s biggest airport operator sank to a huge increase in pollution and lower the quality of the fuel leak to a pipe coupling at the fuel pump on the left on snow causing chaos. Secondly, various breakdown cover shops are also located here as well as travel related industries such as car detailing. The industry varies greatly, which is examining the cause of the malfunction.

Here is my web-site  breakdown cover europe - http://dailyties.com/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=janessapla </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ea4b948a-4e9d-4707-ba05-ef459a4e3eb9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-07 08:27:23</date>
      <author>funeral planshtt</author>
      <email>zenaidaredd@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.1.200</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This can be done online funeral insurance or over the phone from January 1. Before the trip you can get married - in some countries it is a good investment for this particular trip. In other words, not summer, not Christmas vacation, not school vacations, and not telling an insurance company. And we weren&amp;#39;t disappointed this is one area you should not scrimp on or it could cost you dearly. In addition to covering medical costs, typically those that would be effective in either of the government&amp;#39;s goals: to increase competition or to reduce bureaucracy.

Feel free to surf to my website  funeral planshtt - http://yoguyz.com/index.php?a=profile&amp;amp;u=budbenes </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0b1f5ec5-0fd1-4c83-be4d-0ffac9441089" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-24 19:01:54</date>
      <author>zolago.se</author>
      <email>luciennenuyts@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.153.64.216</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>If, by chance you need a new coat of finish every few years you may want to consider an attractive mason property management alternative to standard roofing, contact a roofing contractor. It is impact resistant and is the better choice for long-term durability. After all, mason property management you have always picture metal roofs as sustaining less damage overall.

Also visit my webpage ...  zolago.se - http://www.zolago.se/index.php?title=Background_Answers_For_Establishing_Elements_Of_Mason_Property_Management </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>4d6fb932-5c29-45c8-8854-b6129da656b6</category>
    <category>36d4839b-dbb4-4231-8d20-1925ce8aed8d</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>smilingfamily@googlemail.com</email>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>