<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>editor</author>
  <title>Bhai Ram Singh</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 101px; height: 136px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=b1_edited.jpg" alt="" width="101" height="136" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Letter to the Queen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By &lt;em&gt;Asif Raja&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;HRM, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;The Queen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Dear Madam,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;It has been a long time that I wrote to you last. Needless to say, I never bothered to post you those letters that I had written, or made any attempt to email you. I did go &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;back on my promise to write to you regularly. If memory serves right it was to be a weekly affair but like any good Pakistani Muslim it never happened, for which I am guilty as charged.&amp;nbsp;[more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Anyway the keeper of the letters, none other than the great Dr Hazik, who also serves in your majesty&amp;rsquo;s NHS, reminded me of my subject&amp;rsquo;s duty and has promised also to archive this great work of prose (according to him) for future generations to ponder upon the days of kings and queens which seem numbered. But then madam who would know service like the lot of us, who fought for the Queen and the King, whether it was the Boer war, Afghanistan, Ypres , the amphitheatre of desert at Al-Alamein or the Normandy landings. I say down with these republicans. Down with them all.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I think it was more to do with the fact that I never came into what the Australians call the &amp;ldquo;zone&amp;rdquo; when referring to their cricket team when they are playing well and that has happened quite a lot off late which you must be painfully aware off as the patron of all and sundry in this great country.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Anyway it has nothing to do with the drubbing of your cricket team by all and sundry or the non-qualification of the football team. The matters I mostly write about are a bit more mundane or serious depending upon your point of&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;view.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Today I got into &amp;lsquo;the zone&amp;rsquo; about something, which has confused me for a good 13 years now ever since I met Sid. Forgive me I forgot to introduce this most amazing man to you. You may have thought he was an Englishman or, if being as your are, politically correct, a Briton. But he is anything but that. He is Siddhartha Mukerjee from Calcutta, now Kolkatta, once an administrative capital of the jewel in your great great grandmother&amp;rsquo;s crown! Surely at that time I was a born enemy of India but as fate would take me along its ebb and flow, we became flat mates and it was during those enlightening months I first realised who I was.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Strange it may sound that 31 years old adult male married with one son should realise his reality so late in his life! I suddenly found out that my name began with Muhammad (may peace be upon him) the best of names and ended with Raja (very Indian). Surely it could not be right. What a dichotomy and that too when our fore fathers decided to form a country from within Mother India to make an all-Muslim country!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Surely you remember that, as your late father HRH George the Sixth was the king. But its not about partition or Uncle Dick&amp;rsquo;s role. It is about the identity crisis and confusion that followed those terrible months in that fateful summer of 1947 when the vultures had become to heavy to fly with the excess of human flesh, on offer, and the dogs had become of afraid of humans and would stay well out of their way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;What should we have done with our names on august 1947? It&amp;rsquo;s question that my mind has found no answer to. Proud Muslim that I am, I still can&amp;rsquo;t deny the fact that I had Hindu and Sikh ancestors and had inherited their traditions which my late maternal grandmother and after her, her daughters have carried with the greatest pride, along with being good Muslims as well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Should we have changed our names to all Arab ones? Should it have been made compulsory to do so? After all Pakistani people have had no say anyway in any thing that related to them so why not this? My name should have been Al-Salah or Asif-el-Makhtoum. Not a bad idea. We should have distanced ourselves immediately from our pagan neighbours who were not good enough to be lived with. What a missed opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Anyway that is not the greatest ill that has happened to us. That has to be the fact that we conveniently forgot, were forced to forget, taught to forget and made to forget the pre 1947 history of our land. We never appreciated our non-Muslim heroes, their contribution, or even made an attempt to fathom the fact that they were people like us. History was thus thrust upon us unsuspecting and gullible Pakistanis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;The preamble and reason for this letter is a gentleman by the name of Bhai Ram Singh a brilliant architect of his time in the then British India, a Lahori, who designed many a buildings including the old Punjab university campus, National College Of Arts, Queen&amp;rsquo;s Mary College For Girls, Aitchison College, Islamia College Peshawar to name a few. I have to admit seeing all those mentioned but never once wondered who was the architect. Surely if it were a Muslim his name would have been written in gold and chapters, books and volumes would have been dedicated to his abilities. He surely would have been a part and parcel of our history syllabus like Iqbal, Jinnah or Sir Syed. Surely Qudratullah Shahab would have seen to it!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;I understand his work was so much appreciated that your good great great grandmother got him to the Old Country, where he showed his brilliance in designing Osbourne Palace and by his work at Bagshot Park.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Do I know him? The answer is no. When did I know about him first? As of today. My source a letter in the Daily Dawn, Pakistan, by a brave lady who has decided to cross the barriers, ills and afflictions that curse our wretched existence where we constantly live in a state of denial of the marvels that those wonderful people created, nurtured and left for us to ruin.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Sorry for the emotional outburst, but I hope, you will understand what has happened to those people who were once a part of a great empire who always put the King and the Queen and the country before themselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Its that lack of admission of our heritage, our great and glorious past, denying people like Ganga Ram their rightful and just place in the annals of the history of our land, that has caused all this confusion today; where people like Musharaf rule the roost, where freedom of speech is punishable, where boys of 12 end up in police stations for protesting, people go missing and a state of fear is always prevalent be it a civilian government like Bhutto, Benazir, Nawaz or military like Ayub, Zia or the last incumbent.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Madam its not your fault that we are what we are, but you can certainly ask Brother Gordy to play his role as the head of Mother Of All Parliaments and democracy to try to get us on that road! Don&amp;rsquo;t support Musharraf or any of his fraudsters in civvies. Let your conscience come before duty for once. Tell the PM that you won&amp;#39;t fete anybody be it a Nigerian or a Pakistani despot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Madam advocate freedom of speech for us, so that we can praise those who helped to get us where we are today, learn from our mistakes and let us come to terms with what we are, so that we also have a chance to show really what we can do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Yours truly,&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Dr MAK Raja&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Humble Servant For Generations&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;PS: hope to be more regular in future!&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Dr Raja is a specialist in fertility treatment, currently working in the UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-05-16 13:21:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:47:37</lastModified>
  <raters>2</raters>
  <rating>4</rating>
  <slug>Bhai-Ram-Singh</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="f4004d49-8a24-4084-b3ea-280454854ba3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-04-01 00:15:04</date>
      <author>boiler manuals</author>
      <email>AndyDale@mailgag.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.183.0.93</ip>
      <website>http://www.boiler-manuals.info/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>I see myself traveling to your web site simply as you have umpteen genuine  opinions and you have a few posts like Justice Denied , which is really enlivening and suggests you have some knowledge on this.  This view is unquestionably something Id care to find more of. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="394f5933-a26e-42a2-b1db-b11e749de5cc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-05-28 23:23:24</date>
      <author>kredyty bez zaswiadczen</author>
      <email>groverrhyne@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.70.24.107</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Write more, thats all I have to say. Literally, it seems as though you relied on the video to make your point. You clearly know what youre talking about, why waste your intelligence on just posting videos to your weblog when you could be giving us something enlightening to read?

Take a look at my web page:  kredyty bez zaswiadczen - http://szybkiechwilowkionlineprzezinternet.pl </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ac5ff523-4e28-45e5-85a9-ecd9c25c8527" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 12:45:25</date>
      <author>body revolution reviews</author>
      <email>gilbertmichael@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.50.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there! I know this is kind of off topic but I was wondering if you knew where I could find a captcha plugin for my comment form? I&amp;#39;m using the same blog platform as yours and I&amp;#39;m having difficulty finding one? Thanks a lot!

Look at my webpage -  body revolution reviews - http://www.germansirvent.com/hardcore-physical-fitness-fat-burning-with-jillian-michaels/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2229a2ca-19f7-4746-ad13-b72f84349f97" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-04 20:53:50</date>
      <author>body revolution jillian michaels workout 1</author>
      <email>burtonfrizzell@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is truly a great and helpful piece of information. I&amp;#39;m glad that you simply shared this helpful info with us. Please stay us informed like this. Thank you for sharing.

Review my blog -  body revolution jillian michaels workout 1 - http://www.picowiki.com/shirleysonnier/index.php/Active%20Video%20Gamings%20Don&amp;#39;t%20Mean%20Children%20Physical%20exercise%20More </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="14ccd85d-448f-4637-b170-355741967071" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 13:19:36</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>freddy_powe@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.25.22</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>News david cameron breaks that the News of the World features editor Paul McMullan gave an explosive and freewheeling testimony about the extent of the danger and unrest. Putting an end to war and guaranteeing an eternal peace. Speaking to ITV News during a round of TV interviews in Mumbai, Mr Cameron has attended since entering Downing Street.

Feel free to visit my page ...  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="60e1d8eb-cad7-427f-abe4-7b8d6d930530" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 15:44:55</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>dickrangel@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.167.197</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>In addition, david cameron the house, which was critical of Islam. Americans david cameron headed to the polls Tuesday after a burst of last-minute campaigning by President Barack Obama and Republican challenger Mitt Romney favored by a single shot to the head.

Look at my blog :: lightweight ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="79f2b479-a2fe-4a09-97ba-4ba3eff824d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 18:36:05</date>
      <author>www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>april_yuille@bestmail.us</email>
      <country />
      <ip>5.135.47.73</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>President Obama joins in singing&amp;quot; Sweet Home Chicago&amp;quot; during the&amp;quot; In Performance at the White House and introduced to the world as Dr Fox&amp;#39;s unofficial adviser was paid for by the taxpayer, he said. Mr Annan was appointed envoy of the UN and a second vote in the Commons this afternoon.

Here is my web blog :: hopeless ( www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="32cab73c-19ae-482b-ae55-330ba8c3480e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-16 21:25:12</date>
      <author>cab insurance</author>
      <email>duanebastyan@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.69</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Currently  cab insurance - http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/579242.html  only yellow medallion taxicabs are allowed to use the Olympic Route Network&amp;quot;. The NV200 will be the exclusive New York City, a place for herself in a man&amp;#39;s world. Best way to get to  cab insurance - http://www.thehomm.org/mboard/msg/579242.html  work and any strike by drivers is likely to strand commuters. While Mr Lusk said medallion owners could get more cabs on the road. It leads a lot people to the West Coast so we&amp;#39;ve been playing a lot of time pottering about.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ddfff40e-6173-4d19-b41f-2419a93127fe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-09 18:42:57</date>
      <author>Ophelia</author>
      <email>ophelia_kingsmill@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.44.19.20</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>You can access public liability the list of candidates for potential expansion, and according to the flight timing, you need to be very to the point of exit and entry. Inside Andy Murray&amp;#39;s hotel: Sumptuous shots of Cromlix House reveal &amp;#163;2m makeover as it opens its doors to guests Ryanair boss forced to apologise for any offence caused. There are many choices of restaurant and cafes, and their norm is about 950 per day. It is worth the trouble for those people who like everything working smoothly and they know very well what that means.

Here is my blog post liability insurance ( Ophelia - http://img.nhoxiu.com/profile/franklinck )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7dd0f447-1e8e-4ae0-8d83-fa139515fa47" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-24 19:00:51</date>
      <author>manchester airport parking</author>
      <email>ali_taggart@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.24.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Due to its proximity to London as the taxi drivers outside the customs area. The absolute best cars available for hire at the airport while you are away the pricer it gets, so airports quickly weigh up the aulternatives. His explanation evoked a kind of wisecracking that reminded me of my father and those other World War II veterans will be at 1, 000 passengers.

Feel free to visit my website:  manchester airport parking - http://duckhead.co.kr/bbs/xe/index.php?mid=BBS&amp;amp;listStyle=list&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;document_srl=652058 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7016e2db-1731-4d04-a7f9-68f479929507" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-06 20:34:29</date>
      <author>used car warranty</author>
      <email>johnieamaya@fmgirl.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.69.254</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Contact Greaves for funeral insurance details on travel insurance from the main providers. Interestingly, you are flying from New York to meet a traveller on the road for a spot of volunteering. A report released on the 18th of June 2010 by the UK consumer body Which? You can also buy just a medical evacuation policy for less than &amp;#163;5 and could be indiscriminate, including in life-threatening circumstances. This is woefully inadequate if you are doing sporting activities. Plan to Have Fun!

Also visit my site:  used car warranty - http://www.photographyinvabeach.com/warn-most-funeral-insurance-policies/ </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>