<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>TUNED OUT</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 200px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=mail.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;font face="Times New Roman" size="3"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;lsquo;The government is not fulfilling its responsibility to fight terrorism and protect the lives of the people&amp;rsquo;, said an eminent politician as reported by a newspaper. The argument sounds familiar as it has been made before. We want the government to realize its responsibility to fight the battle against extremism and terrorism alone. The media is entrusted with the job of creating awareness in the masses. But the media can propagate awareness only to the extent that it is aware itself. Even the journalists who yearn for freedom of expression want it hedged when the freedom goes against their favorite school of ideology. For example, Shahid Masood of Geo TV was all for revealing the signs of Kiamat but did not want Maulana Abdul Aziz to be shown on TV fleeing the Lal Mosque clad in a burqa, since he thought it would bring a bad name to Islam.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;[more]&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Khaled Ahmed wrote, &amp;lsquo;Fighting the party accused of terrorism is putting your life on the line without anyone openly recognizing that you have done anything honorable.&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;TV channels have unwittingly taken the side of the terrorists in the war that is unfolding in Waziristan. The avoidance of such a tilt is almost impossible unless there is an inculcation against this drift in the training process of the of the TV channels&amp;rsquo; and&amp;nbsp; &amp;lsquo;People who use vigilante action in the name of Islam are pretty close in their thinking to the terrorists. So far the TV channels have not thought of how they will tackle this&amp;hellip;.&amp;rsquo; The regime has served the cause of &amp;lsquo;freedom of expression&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;awareness&amp;rsquo; by inundating us with relatively innocuous Indian serials &amp;lsquo;Kahani Ghar Ghar Ki&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Kiamat Se Kiamat Tak&amp;rsquo; while keeping out some excellent Irani cinema on Iranian revolution. It would be interesting to see the facial expressions of JI leaders if some of these Irani movies are aired on the TV, notwithstanding their tireless campaign to &amp;lsquo;open up&amp;rsquo; the media. An isolationist rhetoric is constantly fed to the masses by the media while there is no informed debate as to &amp;lsquo;what kind of states behave in what kind of pattern in foreign policy&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;The intellectual elite usually sit back and are happy to leave the cause of awareness to God and evolution. They cannot be blamed entirely since the intellectual elite are by definition quiet and introspective and are ready to take a back seat when confronted by loud and half baked doctrinaires. The journalism on the electronic media is currently dominated by those who are loud and &amp;lsquo;hard-hitting&amp;rsquo; often overshadowing the more subtle and nuanced and never even mentioned among the top ten (e.g. Dr. Huma Baqai, Dr. Khalida Ghaus, Ijaz Haider, S. Wajahat Hussain). Some of the excellent journalistic minds in Pakistan are found in English language newspapers and TV channels leaving a huge segment of the Pakistani youth tuned out of the advances made in thought and journalism by these journalists.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;As a section of the civil society we in Pakistan have the honor of mingling with other sections of the civil society and see little evidence of revolutionary awareness burgeoning among the masses, often claimed by some analysts. The media has created awareness in Pakistan as to the role of the military in the defense of the country&amp;rsquo;s borders and the need for democracy to flourish. But the masses are pretty vague as to how a democracy really functions beyond the holding of free and fair elections. Following are some of the quotes of the Pakistani masses recorded to show the extent to which they have become aware. &amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;lsquo;Taliban had brought peace to Afghanistan and killing of Muslims by Muslims never took place before the invasion by America&amp;rsquo;. &amp;lsquo;Kala Bagh dam should have been forcibly made by the military regime irrespective of the possible bloodshed since a few casualties for a good cause do not matter much in the final analysis&amp;rsquo;. &amp;lsquo;Wavering from Pakistan ideology and two-nation theory has led to confusion as Hindus and Muslims&amp;nbsp; are separate nations and can never live together because Jinnah said so&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp; &amp;lsquo;The right place for women to be is within the home unless forced to do otherwise by circumstances as scientific studies on working women have proven that they are perpetually unhappy.&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Forced closure of CD shops, barber shops and girls&amp;rsquo; schools should not be a matter of concern for us as this is tribal culture and this what the tribals want&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;.Pakistan should have cut off diplomatic relations with Denmark after the publication of the profane cartoons&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Anti India and pro war pronouncements are issued by the likes of Professor Ghafoor Ahmed and General Hameed Gul regularly denouncing the pragmatism of the mainstream politicians and the litany is taken up by the civil society. After all we memorized our history books correctly and are well versed with Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s ideology. The ideologues may be low on liberal content of their pronouncements but are high on nuisance value and the amount of noise generated. Thus professor Ghafoor and General Hameed Gul get the centre stage in the nation&amp;rsquo;s psyche in spite of their poor showing in the elections and the verdict of the masses against extremism. &amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;There is no doubt that the conditions are ripe for change as the advent of the electronic media and cyberspace brings an unprecedented possibility of free exchange of ideas. But to inform and mould ideas to suit the needs of a modern and progressive state far better schooling in ideas is required than is being offered at present. Right now the scale is balanced evenly between forces of progress and obscurantism but to tip it on the side of progress the initiative will have to be captured by those who understand the prerequisites of a liberal and enlightened tomorrow but choose to remain silent. The elite need to throw off the cloak of their elitism and speak louder and more often to counter the revolutionary ideologues (e.g. Maulana Fazlullah and his soul mates) that may be all set to reverse the gains made painstakingly by the liberal segments of the society since the creation of Pakistan.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;With the resources of the age of information and ubiquitous presence of the Internet the people, even in the remote areas of Pakistan, should have better options to tune in to than the infamous Mullah Radio.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;From ATTO (Association of the Tuned Out)&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;p align="justify"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-03-18 07:37:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:55:04</lastModified>
  <raters>6</raters>
  <rating>4</rating>
  <slug>TUNED-OUT</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="a1a46811-c855-4532-b946-d1746d94b605" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 07:44:38</date>
      <author>body revolution 2013</author>
      <email>aileeneastman@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.220</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An outstanding share! I have just forwarded this onto a friend who had been doing a little homework on this. And he in fact bought me dinner because I found it for him... lol. So allow me to reword this.... Thanks for the meal!! But yeah, thanx for spending time to talk about this issue here on your website.

Have a look at my blog:  body revolution 2013 - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="17859702-a24c-4062-8e23-4755f79dac95" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-02 17:53:46</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>antonio-unger@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This info is worth everyone&amp;#39;s attention. Where can I find out more?

My web site;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.mdconvention2012.com/garcinia-cambogia-review-what-you-had-to-know/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b2acf42a-45e0-4e3c-a5a4-157315ee08c6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 04:33:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>lenore.burris@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Oh my goodness! Impressive article dude! Thank you so much, However I am encountering issues with your RSS. I don&amp;#39;t understand the reason why I am unable to join it. Is there anybody getting the same RSS problems? Anyone that knows the answer can you kindly respond? Thanks!!

Also visit my blog post -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.quickestsubmitter.com/a-lot-of-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9751e753-ebf9-477a-9289-5a2cffad7593" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 14:49:33</date>
      <author>stone wave cookware</author>
      <email>adabratton@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I love your blog.. very nice colors &amp;amp; theme. Did you make this website yourself or did you hire someone to do it for you? Plz reply as I&amp;#39;m looking to create my own blog and would like to find out where u got this from. appreciate it

Feel free to surf to my web blog:  stone wave cookware - http://thelmadpk.beeplog.com/353566_1992996.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="de95ab36-3ba2-4719-8a6d-58097c79c88d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 22:32:27</date>
      <author>body revolution</author>
      <email>fletcher-schmitt@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.92.53</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey! This is kind of off topic but I need some help from an established blog. Is it hard to set up your own blog? I&amp;#39;m not very techincal but I can figure things out pretty fast. I&amp;#39;m thinking about setting up my own but I&amp;#39;m not sure where to start. Do you have any points or suggestions?  Thanks

My web page ::  body revolution - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0d9c4650-29e1-4676-b9d2-96eb8cf774b5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 03:59:27</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>veronicaholguin@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s actually a great and helpful piece of information. I&amp;#39;m satisfied that you shared this helpful info with us. Please keep us up to date like this. Thank you for sharing.

Here is my homepage;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://lifeplanatpf.com/garcinia-cambogia-is-it-just-for-fat-burning/193 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ff836126-35a8-40be-ae87-119b7a385d8e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 05:05:07</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>philbreeden@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Magnificent site. Plenty of helpful information here. I am sending it to some friends ans also sharing in delicious. And naturally, thanks to your sweat!

Feel free to surf to my web blog;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://bleurestaurantandwinebar.com/why-you-shouldnt-use-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="51111eb0-74f2-4f55-9c86-8c22f247260e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 10:31:00</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia reviews from users</author>
      <email>suzanne.epstein@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Heya i&amp;#39;m for the primary time here. I found this board and I to find It truly helpful &amp;amp; it helped me out much. I am hoping to present one thing again and aid others such as you aided me.

Take a look at my site ::  garcinia cambogia reviews from users - http://thatssodumb.com/best-weight-loss-supplements-for-mothers-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a3f5aebc-8acd-4523-be83-9d8f6cb51c48" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 03:06:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>ariellejordan@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Everyone loves what you guys are up too. Such clever work and exposure! Keep up the wonderful works guys I&amp;#39;ve added you guys to  blogroll.

Also visit my weblog -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.betterbuildingchallenge.net/all-natural-excess-weight-management-vs-conventional-excess-weight-loss-support/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2039ff6a-5c96-44fb-b311-10b8120465ef" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 18:42:12</date>
      <author>Stone Wave</author>
      <email>jeanne.seay@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.220.246</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I was recommended this website by my cousin. I&amp;#39;m not sure whether this post is written by him as no one else know such detailed about my problem. You are wonderful! Thanks!

My web page:  Stone Wave - http://thelmadpk.beeplog.com/353566_1987569.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="93a80570-6855-4bdb-aa01-d644d39fa90a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-10 01:35:53</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia 1500 mg nutrabio</author>
      <email>jayme_koontz@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.193.255.83</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello There. I found your blog using msn. This is an extremely well written article. I&amp;#39;ll be sure to bookmark it and return to read more of your useful info. Thanks for the post. I will definitely comeback.

Stop by my web blog:  garcinia cambogia 1500 mg nutrabio - http://hostandcare.com/DennyBold </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="738a5ff4-b7be-4a3b-b638-bff0d4a9280d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 13:19:33</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>wilson.medlin@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Article writing is also a excitement, if you be familiar with then you can write or else it is complex to write.

Also visit my web site -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.medtripinfo.com/diet-plan-patch-for-women/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="53f42792-7b2a-4bab-87d2-b76eba658001" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 19:17:10</date>
      <author>Pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>matthias_anderson@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.61.142.102</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Write more, thats all I have to say. Literally, it seems as though you relied on the video to make your point. You definitely know what youre talking about, why throw away your intelligence on just posting videos to your site when you could be giving us something informative to read?

My web page ...  Pure garcinia cambogia - http://africancommunityhealthinitiatives.net/?p=8 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0254e0f7-0581-44df-8b0a-7c9ff71c4076" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 08:40:40</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>paulina.crabtree@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I constantly emailed this webpage post page to all my friends, since if like to read it next my links will too.

Here is my web page -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://www.indianapolis-bk.com/uncategorized/home-physical-exercise-packages-for-fat-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5da4988d-42e9-4014-b6d6-c1e713bac3e8" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 11:22:36</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>leslifarrell@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.38.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, I check your blog on a regular basis. Your story-telling style is witty, keep it up!

Also visit my blog post;  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.schac.org/?p=76 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e41e3a9-6799-492c-be56-236586d2af08" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 21:08:02</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>sheila-roberts@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.130</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Your style is so unique compared to other people I&amp;#39;ve read stuff from. I appreciate you for posting when you&amp;#39;ve got the opportunity, Guess I will just bookmark this blog.

My homepage:  garcinia cambogia - http://www.my-des.com/garcinia-mangostana-xanthones-in-health-short-articles/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="31e02061-0244-4e24-9713-9141875b1c51" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 13:29:10</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>christinhalstead@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My family always say that I am wasting my time here at web, except I know I am getting familiarity daily by reading such fastidious content.

Take a look at my web site  pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.alecmaclaren.org.uk/about-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b58f06e3-3af8-47b4-a97f-28f24ef4f224" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 02:09:12</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max review</author>
      <email>aubreygibbs@whale-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Keep on working, great job!

Feel free to surf to my site ...  garcinia cambogia max review - http://www.apollonights.com/education/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-management/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1c759b94-fb1c-4417-9d42-179fd4241a7c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 08:01:04</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>reynaldoberrios@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.130</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>hello!,I love your writing so so much! proportion we communicate extra approximately your post on AOL? I require an expert on this space to unravel my problem. Maybe that&amp;#39;s you! Taking a look forward to peer you.

Feel free to visit my blog ...  garcinia Cambogia extract - http://www.queerhaiku.com/the-fact-bared-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3772efce-5230-46b9-ad33-6e5e70eddfc6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 09:04:32</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>nathanielwestbrook@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I do believe all the ideas you&amp;#39;ve offered in your post. They are very convincing and will definitely work. Nonetheless, the posts are too quick for novices. May you please extend them a little from next time? Thanks for the post.

Look into my website  garcinia cambogia extract - http://matildas.net/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f69e4931-2884-4523-94dc-0dceb0c3a5a5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 10:01:06</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia For weight loss</author>
      <email>buddyharrison@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.88.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! I could have sworn I&amp;#39;ve been to this site before but after going through a few of the articles I realized it&amp;#39;s new to me. Anyways, I&amp;#39;m definitely pleased I stumbled upon it and I&amp;#39;ll be bookmarking it and checking back frequently!

Here is my web-site ...  garcinia Cambogia For weight loss - http://www.charlottecitizen.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="13fe4d57-b626-4748-ab5e-c53e3b0e2542" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 13:58:23</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>abigailbeardsley@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.191.50</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I visit day-to-day a few websites and sites to read articles or reviews, but this webpage provides quality based content.

Stop by my webpage -  garcinia Cambogia extract - http://proxydrop.org/?p=31 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f9152029-e8d2-4e36-bbb6-ebce8f63ea5a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-05 13:04:45</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia review</author>
      <email>edwardmcintosh@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.141</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Fantastic site. Lots of helpful info here. I am sending it to some buddies ans also sharing in delicious. And obviously, thank you for your effort!

Also visit my weblog:  garcinia cambogia review - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="94bbdc3d-9bcc-490f-a9dc-c2982f32c43e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 19:13:32</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>breanna_goll@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.107.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Addressing david cameron the Business in the Community conference, Mr Cameron pledged to hold a prompt In/Out referendum on Britain&amp;#39;s membership of the EU and back towards the USA. They have since had two sons, Fraser, who david cameron has given &amp;#163;1. Before the 2010 election partly in response to a question she asked about the exchanges between Adam Smith, Mr Hunt&amp;#39;s special adviser, and News Corporation lobbyist Fred Michel.

Feel free to visit my web blog:  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="77cec7e1-8a9f-42af-b42b-7a44fea79938" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-27 02:31:03</date>
      <author>http://www.altmu.com</author>
      <email>rosellawhitehouse@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.195</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>With direct links to everything users might need to share the road and public liability insurance turn left on the M4 westbound. The hotel public liability insurance also has extras for guests to stay connected and aware about their business below. Going through central London using combinations of rail, Underground, and/or taxi is not an isolated example. The observers of airlines and destinations and if you have used the services before.

Feel free to surf to my site: what is public liability insurance ( http://www.altmu.com - http://www.altmu.com/angeliabri/ )</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>