<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Lord's Prayer</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 149px; height: 177px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=NABugti.bmp" alt="" width="149" height="177" /&gt; &lt;img style="width: 152px; height: 177px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=redmosqueguy%5b1%5d.jpg" alt="" width="152" height="177" /&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;img style="width: 149px; height: 180px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=Benazir%2520Bhutto_edited.jpg" alt="" width="149" height="180" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/font&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;by &lt;em&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;O Lord, O Master, O Creator of the Universe and of Tribal Areas, I seek your forgiveness for the transgressions that I have committed. I have sinned. I don&amp;rsquo;t have Sind any more; neither do I have the Punjab, or any other province. I have also lost FATA, FANA and Azad Kashmir. I have lost the uniform, the elections, the assembly, Mushahid Oilcan, Sheikh Ding-Dong and Chaudhry Lickspittle.&amp;nbsp;I can&amp;rsquo;t even find my glasses. The only companion I have got left is 58-2b. It is my pride and joy. When I stroke it, it purrs with pleasure. When it growls with hunger, it sends a shudder through the country. It is growling more and more, as it has not been fed since 1996.&lt;/font&gt; [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Forgive me O master, as I lied when I said that we were hot on the tracks of Bin Laden and Zawahiri. I had them sleeping in the Camp Office all the time. When I said that I would bring the head of Mullah Umar on a spike, I was not telling the truth either. I was sending him his snuff regularly in Quetta. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;I am seeing strange things O Lord. Yesterday I saw Bugti on the telly. He was playing cricket. He sent me a special coded message. He asked me to come and visit him in Dera Bugti. I told him that I prefer golf, but he said he would get me over, one way or the other. Maulana Abdul Rashid came knocking on the door this morning. He said he was Maulana Fazlur Rehman and wanted to be the prime minister, but he can&amp;rsquo;t fool me. He invited me to come and stay with him a while. I flatly refused. I will never fall into the trap of this crazy mullah. The women in black from Jamia Hafsa are on the march again, on the streets of Islamabad, with their &lt;em&gt;dandas. &lt;/em&gt;They are disguised as lawyers, but I have seen through their conspiracy. I am not stupid. I am talking regularly to Benazir. I have asked her to keep her part of the deal, if she wants to be the prime minister. She said &amp;lsquo;be nice to Makhdoom Sahib&amp;rsquo;. I said I am already nice to Makhdoom Sahib. It is not my fault that Zardari wants 100% from now on. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;Kayani has been a bit stand-offish. I asked him what happened to the angels. He said they could not vote because the Langley did not clear them. I told him it is Nadeem Taj who is in-charge here, not Robert Gates. He said he knows very well who is in-charge. Strange man. &lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font face="Arial" size="2"&gt;The Armageddon is nigh. Kurd and Aitazaz are on the loose. They are Gog and Magog. Dajjal is hiding in the Judges Colony. Where is Shahid Masood? He has unleashed all these horrors. He must get a visit from Nadeem Taj. Maybe he will be a good lad like Kamran Khan. &lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img style="width: 169px; height: 200px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=hello1_edited.jpg" alt="" width="169" height="200" /&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
please also see:&lt;a href="/JDP/post/2008/03/The-Trial-of-Pervez-Musharraf.aspx" class="taggedlink"&gt;The Trial of Pervez Musharraf&lt;/a&gt; , &lt;a href="/JDP/post/2008/02/Lota-Nama.aspx" class="taggedlink"&gt;Lota Nama&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-03-15 07:31:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:52:45</lastModified>
  <raters>6</raters>
  <rating>4.5</rating>
  <slug>Lords-Prayer</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="737d4660-c905-4289-8fc7-1c24626c29ea" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-05-28 22:20:47</date>
      <author>kredyty na dowod</author>
      <email>laurelrangel@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.70.24.107</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An impressive share! I have just forwarded this onto a friend who was doing a little research on this. And he actually bought me dinner due to the fact that I discovered it for him... lol. So allow me to reword this.... Thanks for the meal!! But yeah, thanx for spending the time to talk about this matter here on your internet site.

My homepage  kredyty na dowod - http://szybkiechwilowkionlineprzezinternet.pl </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2f58c6ca-4525-444a-ad01-a24780018787" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-01 15:16:31</date>
      <author>jillian&amp;#39;s body revolution</author>
      <email>antwandurr@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there! Someone in my Myspace group shared this website with us so I came to give it a look. I&amp;#39;m definitely enjoying the information. I&amp;#39;m bookmarking and will be tweeting this to my followers! Fantastic blog and excellent style and design.

Here is my page -  jillian&amp;#39;s body revolution - http://vdesignstudio.ca/get-price-cut-jillian-michaels-largest-loser-training-dvds/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="665fab0c-5946-4daf-aeae-0dbd37e63427" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 17:32:40</date>
      <author>stone wave cookware</author>
      <email>son-sonnier@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great post.

Feel free to surf to my website;  stone wave cookware - http://diegomayberry.beeplog.com/353568_2004781.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="973c958d-7d90-4ec8-816e-b90c4e94e97c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 05:32:27</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>dedra.lapointe@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>96.127.161.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! This is kind of off topic but I need some guidance from an established blog. Is it tough to set up your own blog? I&amp;#39;m not very techincal but I can figure things out pretty quick. I&amp;#39;m thinking about setting up my own but I&amp;#39;m not sure where to start. Do you have any tips or suggestions?  Cheers

My web page:  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.quickestsubmitter.com/a-lot-of-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8b3e3a5f-b76d-4215-822a-96fe13e9ca00" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-08 06:07:32</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>davidnathan@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.34.103</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello mates, nice piece of writing and pleasant arguments commented here, I am really enjoying by these.

Here is my weblog ...  garcinia cambogia extract - http://aierbang.org/question/5680 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8132c330-47de-4c72-93bd-e981a6399e29" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-12 11:49:30</date>
      <author>Pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>nicholas.bonilla@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi! I know this is somewhat off-topic but I had to ask. Does operating a well-established website such as yours require a massive amount work? I am completely new to writing a blog but I do write in my diary everyday. I&amp;#39;d like to start a blog so I can easily share my personal experience and thoughts online. Please let me know if you have any kind of suggestions or tips for brand new aspiring bloggers. Appreciate it!

Feel free to surf to my web blog ::  Pure garcinia cambogia - http://www.lecridupeuple.com/do-diet-plan-patches-work/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9416fb89-1487-424f-8c67-1382395115ae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 02:17:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>natishalindquist@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.149</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I do not even know how I ended up here, but I thought this post was good. I don&amp;#39;t know who you are but certainly you are going to a famous blogger if you aren&amp;#39;t already ;) Cheers!

Take a look at my web page  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.mdconvention2012.com/garcinia-cambogia-review-what-you-had-to-know/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="58928d13-850e-4a18-9a07-0a2ff990852f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 03:22:41</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>barbarameehan@animail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.236.10.222</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This article will help the internet visitors for setting up new blog or even a blog from start to end.

Look into my web page:  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.greekommend.com/diet-patch-that-functions/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e1a8daf-83a0-4dbe-b5df-898690a8cd29" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-17 11:17:56</date>
      <author>pure garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>angelapape@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.158.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Your style is very unique in comparison to other people I have read stuff from. Thank you for posting when you have the opportunity, Guess I will just book mark this blog.

Also visit my web site ::  pure garcinia Cambogia extract - http://libyanreliefcommittee.org/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="efc39431-2576-475a-be4f-e02d33aefe38" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 14:23:57</date>
      <author>doctor oz garcinia cambogia for weight loss tv episode</author>
      <email>juana-pruett@peacemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My brother suggested I might like this web site. He was totally right. This post truly made my day. You cann&amp;#39;t imagine simply how much time I had spent for this info! Thanks!

Here is my website:  doctor oz garcinia cambogia for weight loss tv episode - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ff179285-663b-4a26-991d-fc110393ecfa" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 17:45:00</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>ruby-weston@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.174</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great blog here! Also your website a lot up very fast! What host are you the usage of? Can I am getting your associate hyperlink on your host? I desire my site loaded up as fast as yours lol

Look at my web blog -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.solusikeamanan.com/pure-garcinia-cambogia-lose-10-pounds-in-1-month/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="edf1e111-c948-4c45-a363-6dfd1df28c54" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 07:00:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements</author>
      <email>briansimon@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After looking into a number of the articles on your web page, I really appreciate your way of writing a blog. I saved it to my bookmark website list and will be checking back in the near future. Please check out my website too and tell me how you feel.

Feel free to surf to my web page ::  garcinia cambogia weight loss supplements - http://thegreetingcardbox.com/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="662209ba-1f8e-493f-8c4c-fec83d574e76" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 16:12:32</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia gnc stores</author>
      <email>glory-mckenzie@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.192</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there I am so grateful I found your website, I really found you by accident, while I was looking on Yahoo for something else, Anyways I am here now and would just like to say thanks for a fantastic post and a all round interesting blog (I also love the theme/design), I don&amp;#39;t have time to go through it all at the minute but I have book-marked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read a great deal more, Please do keep up the excellent work.

Also visit my blog post ::  garcinia cambogia gnc stores - http://www.seattleteens.org/just-where-can-i-purchase-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7f6cfc12-2d54-4abb-b0ec-2c18c14db84a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-06 22:52:12</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>mallorymurry@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.88.109</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>My brother suggested I might like this web site. He was entirely right. This post truly made my day. You cann&amp;#39;t imagine simply how much time I had spent for this information! Thanks!

Here is my web blog -  pure garcinia cambogia - http://piercell.com/get-the-realities-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2753cf82-12a9-45a3-872a-b291026919b9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 15:43:58</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk</author>
      <email>regenamcdougal@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.30.48.154</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Adam, from Mitcham, London, in the david cameron conclusions, it was misplaced. But the prime minister gave his clearest indication to date that Britain will not be supplying arms to the Syrian conflict to Scottish independence. It did not name the firms, and emphasised that the raids did not mean the creation of the single market, the City of London with tent cities. Practically speaking, at the White House:&amp;quot; Meet Australia&amp;#39;s david cameron Karl Rove.

Feel free to surf to my website ... arrogant [ https://www.gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ]</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d2e6a4aa-b6a4-4aa0-be31-bfea40c4b4c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-08 16:20:56</date>
      <author>www.wikiagro.com</author>
      <email>andraburke@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.227.133</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When calculating towing weights it&amp;#39;s the kerb pounds on the tow car that&amp;#39;s the essential determinator, the caravan should competently fit in a 85 percents ratio, even though you may pull a 100 and still achieve it. Whichever option you ultimately choose, make sure the company providing you with you with caravan insurance or motorhome insurance plans are aware of its location. For holiday makers, driving around in damaged caravans is not any way to start a vacation.

Feel free to surf to my homepage cheap caravan insurance -  www.wikiagro.com - http://www.wikiagro.com/pt/Comparing_Fundamental_Criteria_For_caravans ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6b9a4b6e-0c89-4694-9bf7-099526b3d240" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-17 15:30:18</date>
      <author>http://www.newmanlakerc.com/community/mboard/msg/11277.html</author>
      <email>claire_sterne@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.39</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>SpaceX has a contract taxi insurance ( http://www.newmanlakerc.com/community/mboard/msg/11277.html - http://www.newmanlakerc.com/community/mboard/msg/11277.html ) with NASA to take cargo to the station in 2015 for less than what Russia charges for rides in its Soyuz capsules. Ed Helms&amp;#39;s character Stu, actually played by Scott, hangs out of the black cab trade. Unfortunately, the driver could not be more specific. Taxi and Limousine Commissioner David Yassky says apps are the latest expats to fall foul of the United Arab Emirates for use of its space habitats.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>readinglord@yahoo.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>