<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Abbaji’s Dream </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f7%2fabbajis+dream.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Letter to Brother Abdullah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Dear Brother Abdullah,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Virtue is consolidating its hold in the Republic and vice is on retreat. Brother Tinpot is also in retreat. He has defied the Islamic court in Islamabad and has made good his escape with the help of his vassals in a Nissan off-roader. He has escaped to Chak Shahzad, where he has dug himself in and raised the banner of rebellion. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Dear Brother,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Whoever rebels against God must face the full force of the Ummah and of the soldiers of the Ummah, the French commandos. Be it Tinpot or be it Juhayman al Otaybi, should not make any difference. Accompanied by the soldiers of the Ummah, the returning officers, across the length and breadth of the country and the wukala of the bar association will surround Chak Shahzad and will bring Tinpot to the court in an orange jump suit. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;O Pillar of the Ummah,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Yours Truly is worried about the dangers to Islam that are lurking in every corner in that seat of infamy, Islamabad. There are many people who want to undermine the rule of the righteous and do no want to see Your Brother becoming the fifth rightly guided caliph of Islam, (pending elections and a&amp;nbsp; constitutional amendment). These mischief makers are creating these diversions, so that the metro bus of the sharia careens of its prescribed path and the Ummah is left in doldrums. No such plan of these munafiqeen and mushrikeen will be allowed to succeed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Instead, Shahbaz Sahib, the hawk eyed servitor of the Punjab emirate, will foil any attempts by the Otaybi of Ontario or of Chak Shahzad to stand in the way of sharia. We will march forward in unison, with inspiring leaders of the Ummah such as Maulana Ludhianvi and Malik Mumtaz Qadri to achieve the ideal that our forefathers had laid down their lives for and that Abbaji had dreamed of.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;O the shadow of the Almighty on earth, and the guardian of the house of the Almighty,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Brother Imran is causing problems. He does not have the maturity and understanding that comes with experience of exile and imprisonment by the infidels. Brother Raymond Davis was released under the injunctions of Islam, after paying diyat to families. It was Brother Pasha who was ensured that justice is done and that the will of Allah prevails, by sticking his pious and righteous handgun in the ribs of the session judge. As Your Majesty will recall, the riyals came from the treasury of the Holy Kingdom. I think Brother Imran should keep his mouth shut and submit to the will of Allah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Once your brother sits on the throne of the caliphate and wears the crown of sharia on his head, he will talk to Brother Obama, as he has talked to Brother Clinton in the past. We have drones of our own which cause greater damage than the drones fired by Brother Panetta. Your brother will be quite happy to exchange technology where Brother Panetta can have Rana Sana Ullah, if we can have the Predators.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Your bhabi gives profound salam,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;MMN Sharif&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;PML(N)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-07-27 01:10:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-07-27 01:13:22</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Abbaji’s-Dream-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="5e8249a5-685a-4a60-b5eb-3b2c77dc5aac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-25 20:12:50</date>
      <author>what game is similar to candy crush saga</author>
      <email>gabriella.pinkerton@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.3.147.146</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>In addition, the wonderful  also comes with the fashion and practical GPS function. It helps you stick with healthier eating habits &amp;#39; which start from the food items that you pile up on your grocery cart. Productivity features include an organiser, document editor (MS Office compatible) and the standard Android Google features.

Feel free to visit my homepage;  what game is similar to candy crush saga - http://candycrushcheatzz.blogspot.com/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a409f5fa-b5f6-471b-b44c-e18a562817de" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-21 23:29:07</date>
      <author>game Of war fire age free chips</author>
      <email>stacie-coyne@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.90.4.226</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>To heal from the pain you need to process the four healing emotions discussed in the book Mars and Venus Starting Over. The Great War between the Northern and Southern states of the &amp;quot;United States&amp;quot; possess a peculiar interest for civil war chess set enthusiasts, not only because it was a struggle between two sections of people akin to us, but because of the epic courage with which the weaker party with ill-fed, ill-clad and ill-equipped troops, for four year sustained the contest with an opponent not only possessed of immense numerical superiority, but having the command of the sea, and being able to draw its arms and munitions of war from all manufactures of Europe. 0 have been shown to be ahead of the curve in this regard.

my weblog:  game Of war fire age free chips - http://Www.youtube.com/watch?v=NQhu_tOlFuw </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c84374c5-0279-4fc1-baca-342e9a2442af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-24 17:00:55</date>
      <author>game of war cheats chips</author>
      <email>melissa_troupe@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.10.142</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Claudia Black (the voice of Chloe Frazer through Uncharted 2 and Morrigan through Dragon Age Origins, she also played Aeryn Sunrays in Farscape and Vala Mal Doran in Stargate SG-1) would be voicing Sam Byrne and it&amp;#39;s not only new faces, there are some fresh tricks up your sleeve like having the capability to swap weapons with your teammates and you could now knock over enemies while talking about cover, add a couple of new executions and you will be able to take the fight into the Horde. Author Karen Traviss picks up the story from there as the COG and remaining humans attempt to rebuild. Remember, I don&amp;#39;t associate health with &amp;#39;health&amp;#39; insurance or visiting the doctor.

Take a look at my web site:  game of war cheats chips - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NQhu_tOlFuw </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>