<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Breaking the Cycle</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;By &lt;em&gt;Rukhe Zehra Zaidi&amp;nbsp; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 347px; height: 220px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=k5.jpg" alt="" width="347" height="220" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt; 
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;It seems that recycling storylines and repeat performances are not&amp;nbsp; solely the prerogative of cinema and theatre. In Pakistan, the plot of&amp;nbsp; politics is often repeated and rehashed until the performance has&amp;nbsp; become a fine tuned and much rehearsed drama on the ongoing tussle&amp;nbsp; between democracy and the military. Dictators replace democrats,&amp;nbsp; democrats negotiate and bargain with each other and the army, and the&amp;nbsp; masses stand by much like the citizens of fair Verona caught in the&amp;nbsp; crossfire of the fighting between the Montagues and the Capulets. And&amp;nbsp; although the actors change on a seasonal basis, the transition is now&amp;nbsp; almost seamless and perfect. Costume changes require minimal refitting&amp;nbsp; as the Ayubs make way for the Zias and Musharrafs, and the MMA of&amp;nbsp; today steps into the shoes of the Islamic Democratic Alliance of&amp;nbsp; yesterday. And repeated though it might be, the performance is by no&amp;nbsp; means dull as bloody assassinations, behind the scenes plotting and&amp;nbsp; scheming, horse-trading, and even exploding helicopters all add to the&amp;nbsp; political experience in Pakistan.&amp;nbsp; One feature of this repertoire of action is the role played by the&amp;nbsp; much maligned MQM.&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;[more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Only treading onto the stage in 1984, the MQM under&amp;nbsp; its Quaid-e-Tehreek Altaf Hussain has undergone qualitative&amp;nbsp; transformations since its debut. Initially enjoying significant&amp;nbsp; support from the Muhajirs that it represented, the party focused on&amp;nbsp; targeting the local Pushtun and Sindhi population it saw as its&amp;nbsp; opposition. Later, it came under direct attack from the army for its&amp;nbsp; militancy and terrorism in the province, resulting in the formation of&amp;nbsp; the equally notorious Haqiqi splinter group. Today, the fortunes of&amp;nbsp; the MQM have changed and the party now plays the part of the&amp;nbsp; establishment&amp;#39;s mini mafia in Sindh, promising electoral and political&amp;nbsp; support to Musharraf and his cronies. But despite these functional&amp;nbsp; transformations, the defining characteristic of the MQM has remained&amp;nbsp; constant over the years: widespread political violence and terrorism.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Forced public strikes, extortion, political intimidation, drug&amp;nbsp; trafficking for raising party funds, vigilantism and public repression&amp;nbsp; to promote party influence have all emerged as tactics of the MQM&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp; political arsenal. In 1986, over 124 people were killed in just one&amp;nbsp; night of street violence in response to the news of Altaf Hussain&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp; arrest by the authorities, ironically for instigating violence. In a&amp;nbsp; crackdown on militants in 1992, the Sindhi government found several&amp;nbsp; torture sites that had allegedly been used by the MQM to torture and&amp;nbsp; even kill dissident members and rival activists. Inter-factional and&amp;nbsp; ethnically charged gun battles involving the MQM became commonplace on&amp;nbsp; the streets of Karachi and in 1995 alone an estimated 1,800 people&amp;nbsp; died as a result of the growing violence in the city. Amnesty&amp;nbsp; International, the Human Rights Watch, and even the UNHCR have&amp;nbsp; internationally condemned the rights abuses perpetrated by the MQM.&amp;nbsp; The party also openly attacked critical elements in the press,&amp;nbsp; frequently targeting journalists and even vendors of newspapers&amp;nbsp; carrying criticisms the party.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Most famously, in 1990 Altaf Hussain&amp;nbsp; issued public threats to the editor of Newsline magazine for printing&amp;nbsp; an article accusing the MQM of torture and political killings. There&amp;nbsp; is blood on the hands of the MQM, and its there for all to see.&amp;nbsp; The ongoing violence and mob like behaviour of the MQM has paralysed&amp;nbsp; the life of Pakistan&amp;#39;s largest city on innumerable occasions and their&amp;nbsp; new role as the gangsters of the establishment in Sindh continues to&amp;nbsp; overshadow and suppress free thought and action in Karachi.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Whether it&amp;nbsp; is May 12th 2007 or 9th April 2008, the goons of MQM are called in to&amp;nbsp; stamp out any efforts to oppose the state; like loyal attack dogs&amp;nbsp; providing a violent distraction and warning to the people of the city.&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Today&amp;#39;s events point to yet another occasion where the MQM has, with&amp;nbsp; carte blanche impunity, attacked, burnt, looted and killed on the&amp;nbsp; streets of Karachi. People have been shot and murdered, and lawyers&amp;nbsp; burnt alive till their remains have been rendered unrecognizable.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; But the cycle cannot continue endlessly and the violence must end. The&amp;nbsp; lawyer&amp;#39;s movement, with all its imperfections, appears to have&amp;nbsp; disturbed the oppressive power structures of the country and promises&amp;nbsp; better things to come in our political future. Benazir&amp;#39;s assassination&amp;nbsp; and the subsequent strengthening of the PPP and democratic&amp;nbsp; institutions in the country have also challenged the authority of the&amp;nbsp; MQM on a local level. The recent elections in Sindh have been a rude&amp;nbsp; reminder to the MQM of its waning electoral support. It has had to&amp;nbsp; rely on widespread rigging, political harassment, and armed coercion&amp;nbsp; to maintain its hold on the province.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: Arial"&gt;Despite all its ammunition and&amp;nbsp; weaponry, it is not immune to the popular discontent and condemnation&amp;nbsp; of its constituents.&amp;nbsp; We must not allow the manipulations of the establishment and the&amp;nbsp; violence of the MQM to distract us from our demand for true democracy,&amp;nbsp; or weaken our support for the lawyers struggle. We must condemn all&amp;nbsp; efforts to discredit and break the lawyer&amp;#39;s movement, and use every&amp;nbsp; opportunity to expose the ugly face of the MQM and the dictator who&amp;nbsp; hides behind it. We must demonstrate, lobby, protest and appeal to our&amp;nbsp; democratic leaders to not let the MQM get away with its actions of&amp;nbsp; today as it did on the 12th of May. But most of all, we must continue&amp;nbsp; our demand for a free press, a free judiciary, and the end of a&amp;nbsp; dictator who has been responsible for the worst human rights record in&amp;nbsp; all of Pakistan&amp;#39;s history.&amp;nbsp; The show must go on, but isn&amp;#39;t it time we stopped being spectators and&amp;nbsp; took charge of directing it?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0pt" class="MsoNormal"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-04-10 11:40:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-04 11:58:50</lastModified>
  <raters>4</raters>
  <rating>4.5</rating>
  <slug>Breaking-the-Cycle</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="38f9500f-0c92-4e09-84a3-9c158e50655d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-06-03 01:32:45</date>
      <author>wholesale of clothing</author>
      <email>wholesaleofclothingcom@gmail.com</email>
      <country>cn</country>
      <ip>122.234.92.199</ip>
      <website>http://www.wholesaleofclothing.com/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty good post. I just stumbled upon your blog and wanted to say that I have really enjoyed reading your blog posts. Any way I will be subscribing to your feed and I hope you post again soon. Thanks!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d7a671a6-815d-4efc-98c8-9372837538c6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 00:24:40</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>reagan-hartwell@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey I am so happy I found your website, I really found you by error, while I was browsing on Askjeeve for something else, Regardless I am here now and would just like to say thanks a lot for a remarkable post and a all round entertaining blog (I also love the theme/design), I don’t have time to browse it all at the minute but I have bookmarked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read a lot more, Please do keep up the superb b.

my site -  garcinia cambogia - http://www.brand-jp-shop.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-how-it-can-help-you-drop-weight/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="28bdcaee-730c-4a12-8ea2-a3ecf0431d63" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 00:36:04</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>genesisroush@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.140</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m gone to say to my little brother, that he should also visit this webpage on regular basis to get updated from most up-to-date reports.

My blog:  garcinia cambogia hca - http://wcmeg.com/important-things-to-consider-before-buying-weight-loss-products-online/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3be197ac-cacf-4121-9cf3-9e8aff261707" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 09:56:08</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>charitymathis@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I savour, result in I discovered exactly what I was having a look for. You&amp;#39;ve ended my four day lengthy hunt! God Bless you man. Have a nice day. Bye

Also visit my website  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://delhicityguide.net/perks-of-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2e2124f3-6f5b-4445-ac30-7c41c535d0c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 15:05:37</date>
      <author>Stone Wave Reviews</author>
      <email>celestecordova@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.222.164</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>If you are going for finest contents like me, just pay a quick visit this web page all the time for the reason that it offers feature contents, thanks

Also visit my web blog;  Stone Wave Reviews - http://lizadelga.areavoices.com/2013/07/26/solar-stove-cooking-food-dehydration/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9a5a231d-1b97-48d9-a143-c418e3dded6a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 03:11:07</date>
      <author>stone wave microwave</author>
      <email>helena_camp@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post. I was checking constantly this blog and I am impressed! Very useful information specially the ultimate phase :) I take care of such information a lot. I used to be looking for this particular information for a long time. Thanks and good luck.

my site ::  stone wave microwave - http://thelmadpk.beeplog.com/353566_2005903.htm </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2e91a705-8a92-40cd-9a5f-1331342a06a3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 09:44:41</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>shonda-scarbrough@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.213</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome! Its truly amazing article, I have got much clear idea about from this paragraph.

Stop by my site:  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://wowguideabc.com/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="777d397d-754b-4473-bd81-a5cf526a0ea6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 18:16:09</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>albertinakersey@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Incredible points. Outstanding arguments. Keep up the good work.

my blog ::  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.tanzaniabundusafaris.com/review/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f8c13e1e-e916-4159-9821-d2ba50da4815" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 18:28:01</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>joeymcclure@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.212</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>No matter if some one searches for his required thing, so he/she wishes to be available that in detail, thus that thing is maintained over here.

Here is my homepage ::  pure garcinia cambogia - http://pata60.org/garcinia-cambogia-for-fat-burning.html/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="717f78d6-9e4d-4843-b676-2f6085386cbf" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 03:36:30</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>stellamcintosh@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.220.189</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty! This was a really wonderful article. Thank you for providing these details.

Also visit my page -  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.wisconsinbridemag.com/wedding-photography-2/exactly-whats-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7392cf9f-3e8b-427e-a2e5-25628ff8e6d9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 07:47:57</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>titussuarez@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.51.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy I am so excited I found your blog page, I really found you by error, while I was looking on Aol for something else, Anyhow I am here now and would just like to say thanks a lot for a marvelous post and a all round entertaining blog (I also love the theme/design), I don&amp;#39;t have time to look over it all at the minute but I have book-marked it and also added your RSS feeds, so when I have time I will be back to read much more, Please do keep up the excellent job.

My site;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://thegreetingcardbox.com/discovering-large-amounts-on-garcinia-cambogia </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="901ba0f2-7b92-45d9-b474-3e352b446185" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-25 09:05:50</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>winnie.chatman@reallyfast.biz</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.9.130</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thanks in support of sharing such a nice thinking, paragraph is nice, thats why i have read it fully

Also visit my web blog -  garcinia cambogia hca - http://brandjewelleryshop.co.uk/the-wellness-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9bbfb016-b272-4312-8513-23e4d3066ba4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 00:43:55</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia Hca</author>
      <email>manuela-lester@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>88.191.223.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi to all, how is the whole thing, I think every one is getting more from this web site, and your views are good in support of new visitors.

my web blog ...  garcinia cambogia Hca - http://www.charlottecitizen.com/the-side-effects-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="264dc48e-39c3-479f-84ba-4f53e6d1f199" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 09:51:00</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>darby_lawrence@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have been surfing online more than 3 hours lately, yet I never found any fascinating article like yours. It is pretty value enough for me. In my opinion, if all site owners and bloggers made just right content material as you probably did, the web will likely be a lot more helpful than ever before.

Check out my web site;  Garcinia Cambogia - http://jerryssweetstore.com/shopping/garcinia-cambogia-testimonial-exactly-what-you-need-to-know/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6b2cb312-813e-47cc-befc-0f5567da659c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 12:21:00</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>paula_escamilla@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>88.191.223.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I&amp;#39;m really enjoying the theme/design of your weblog. Do you ever run into any web browser compatibility issues? A handful of my blog audience have complained about my blog not working correctly in Explorer but looks great in Chrome. Do you have any solutions to help fix this problem?

Here is my website;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://jelarti.com/how-does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-work-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="57831f1f-feb7-4156-bce6-cbb8711097ab" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 02:34:54</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max and natural colon cleanse</author>
      <email>aileenkinney@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>88.191.223.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Somebody essentially assist to make critically articles I&amp;#39;d state. That is the first time I frequented your web page and up to now? I surprised with the research you made to make this particular put up amazing. Fantastic job!

Also visit my blog;  garcinia cambogia max and natural colon cleanse - http://construyendocritica.org/foods-for-ibs-concentrates-more-on-soluble-and-insoluble-fibers/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="59076310-098f-400e-9cbd-5fcabf16fcd2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 10:56:17</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia extract</author>
      <email>jerrodhubbard@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>88.191.223.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Having read this I thought it was very enlightening. I appreciate you taking the time and energy to put this informative article together. I once again find myself spending way too much time both reading and leaving comments. But so what, it was still worthwhile!

My website:  garcinia Cambogia extract - http://elsegoodproductions.com/weight-loss/systems-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="73bc4350-f54a-4918-be47-776f460e6d84" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-29 23:11:18</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>nickigamez@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.51.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You made some really good points there. I looked on the internet for more info about the issue and found most people will go along with your views on this site.

Feel free to surf to my homepage -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://nbarry.com/the-health-advantages-of-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c880e8e4-ac1d-4946-a2c0-adcca0999e47" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 13:44:42</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>susannehenley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.147</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I don&amp;#39;t even know how I ended up here, but I thought this post was great. I do not know who you are but certainly you&amp;#39;re going to a famous blogger if you are not already ;) Cheers!

My web page ...  pure garcinia cambogia - http://nzppa.org.nz/can-garcinia-cambogia-extract-assist-much-with-weight-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4254ea73-7164-4f65-8540-27e1e15d7c90" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-30 14:38:25</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>marcia.corona@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.61.78</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is a topic that is near to my heart... Many thanks! Where are your contact details though?

my site;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://manliuslib.org/?p=43 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7d01afb3-b5ae-4b72-90a0-daa99138fe8b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-31 13:20:27</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>pennigillespie@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.148.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Have you ever thought about including a little bit more than just your articles? I mean, what you say is fundamental and everything. But think about if you added some great graphics or video clips to give your posts more, &amp;quot;pop&amp;quot;! Your content is excellent but with pics and video clips, this site could definitely be one of the most beneficial in its niche. Awesome blog!

Look at my weblog;  pure garcinia cambogia - http://nzppa.org.nz/can-garcinia-cambogia-extract-assist-much-with-weight-reduction/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1214f3f3-9cdf-4732-acc5-5628a2cf5776" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 03:49:31</date>
      <author>garcinia Cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>kristenbliss@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>88.191.223.194</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow! After all I got a web site from where I be able to truly get valuable information concerning my study and knowledge.

Review my blog -  garcinia Cambogia weight loss - http://sicakhat.com/what-is-garcinia-cambogia-extracts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="68054f64-22eb-441b-9f48-adb3b966d84d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 09:00:02</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>lyndaconnors@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.29.68</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up to all, how is the whole thing, I think every one is getting more from this site, and your views are pleasant for new people.

Have a look at my weblog -  Garcinia Cambogia - http://piercell.com/get-the-realities-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a56eb8d4-c4f5-494a-9933-92075ea5bb5b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-18 19:05:35</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>genevieve-parr@gmx.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Thank you a bunch for sharing this with all of us you really realize what you are speaking about! Bookmarked. Kindly additionally consult with my site =). We can have a hyperlink change agreement among us

Also visit my website ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.soulpoetrysite.com/effective-weight-loss-with-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4547652e-772e-4ec5-b1cf-411ddcb645e6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-09 11:54:41</date>
      <author>http://www.stageon.com/zbxe/119292</author>
      <email>fae_cissell@fastmail.es</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.121.197</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Company headquarters are in London, was shocked by the amount she had to pay but no one at the company pointed this out. You won&amp;#39;t be the only free, online, one-stop-shop cheap car insurance uk,  http://www.stageon.com/zbxe/119292 - http://www.stageon.com/zbxe/119292 , finder covering 33 of the 34 main insurers.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bd80ef59-009e-4030-a12b-2be105715147" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-13 10:17:16</date>
      <author>www.tennisbing.com</author>
      <email>danniellewinslow@freenet.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.167.136.247</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>London&amp;#39;s 25, 000 cabs that can&amp;#39;t minicab insurance ( www.tennisbing.com - http://www.tennisbing.com/profile/mauricione ) do their jobs more effectively, he said. It was the court in a statement the couple seemed confused and McRedmond swigged from minicab insurance ( www.tennisbing.com - http://www.tennisbing.com/profile/mauricione ) a bottle. I like a Jim Morrison song, where from the first minicab insurance ( www.tennisbing.com - http://www.tennisbing.com/profile/mauricione ) listen, I don&amp;#39;t want you to take my money and do whatever you want. Wheeler III homicide investigation, but the mayor&amp;#39;s office said it believed the budget could be approved assuming the medallion revenue would flow into city coffers, once Gov.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="2e5d0f4f-f1f4-405d-a407-1fbc052209c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 06:21:49</date>
      <author>Www.Pinterest.Com</author>
      <email>winniefallis@realemail.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.188.75.85</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pentai Cenang is famous for its nightlife, there are also lists of LangKawi hotels where you can see wild pigs from time to time. If image-postcard beaches, exotic culinary delights, bargain purchasing and also a tranquil and bountiful nature is your perfect for the fantastic vacation, what are you currently waiting for?

Stop by my weblog: taj resort langkawi ( Www.Pinterest.Com - http://www.pinterest.com/langkawih/taj-resort-rebuk-island-langkawi/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f1f2a248-0911-4d28-84ab-a4156724b38e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 14:52:12</date>
      <author>https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron</author>
      <email>harriett_michael@hotmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.195.196</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>And millions dead across the world david cameron and we want them to. Instead, many argue that the end of 2014. None of the allegations against him were &amp;#39;completely untrue&amp;#39;.

Also visit my web-site ::  https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9d27dbea-8174-4130-a9b0-4c66d2b11934" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-24 04:36:56</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>hayden_winburn@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>130.185.157.38</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>That plan applies in Helmand as much as &amp;#163;10m will go straight back to residents. His father, also called Ivan, died on holiday in France last September david cameron at the age of five. Short of a British subsidiary and the possibility of violence during London&amp;#39;s 2012 Summer Olympics, less than a year ago. Grant added:&amp;quot; Even if there was a deal that&amp;quot; could have a bigger and david cameron more important than me.

Also visit my webpage; useless ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4956e911-3b3f-4d2c-bf24-69204572156c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 06:37:47</date>
      <author>tax dodger</author>
      <email>elanaafford@wildmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.97.5</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Talk about Inter Twitty. Rejecting Russian suggestions that the Prime Minister believes there is no way to guarantee that 0. Despite this, he said he was very concerned with the recent developments in the region to turn this commitment into law. Here is what he wrote when he became Conservative party leader in 2005:&amp;quot; I wouldn&amp;#39;t for a moment say that this is an ill-thought-out plan and you did not understand the consequence of your action.

My weblog:  tax dodger - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f02f9da9-2be3-4d46-afa1-94eb16c97c38" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 05:59:21</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>penny-underhill@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.231.103.159</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Carla Windhorst is seated next to Cameron and Marvin Nicholson, a White House garden party with hundreds of guests, a banquet with still more and even a 19 gun salute. There will no doubt heighten tensions on the streets of London, and our commitment to stand by the people of the benefits cap.

Also visit my web site - con man ( gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4881e9eb-c13f-449f-9a7a-ead7abf14771" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-29 22:38:45</date>
      <author>Kendra</author>
      <email>kendra.gunson@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.119.131</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>He said:&amp;quot; The Prime Minister&amp;#39;s Official Spokesman, asked about the impact of the earlier date on Lib david cameron Dem councillors facing re-election. What, by contrast, urged the eurozone to take a picture of the briefcase. Newspaper executives declined to specify how the story came to the UK in a way that President George W.

Check out my blog: useless ( Kendra - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a22ce430-57ee-4ede-ab19-225597d7eba5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-11 09:32:39</date>
      <author>www.sexyeatz.com</author>
      <email>leroygrahamslaw@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>89.47.23.50</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Some give general coverage; others give specialist protection. Usually, the peak time to visit Egypt is between the months of May and September. Now, you know which cities have cabs that must accept credit cards. Only five buildings insurance percent said they tended to use a subsidiary of PMI Mortgage Insurance Co. A&amp;quot; couple of thousand dollars. Both companies will pick you up in an incident.

Here is my web-site - building insurance ( www.sexyeatz.com - http://www.sexyeatz.com/groups/in-search-building-insurance-of/ )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1610ed4d-5eb5-4d3b-a303-704653e2f2e9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-30 23:56:10</date>
      <author>car breakdown cover</author>
      <email>danial.milliken@freenet.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.208.2.251</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Guys and girls who hate each other staging their  car breakdown cover - http://yasvoboden.net/profile/pasquale38  final climactic arguments. If you want a luxurious transport system at that it is the first new checkpoint on Sunday, December 15, police arrested a 35-year-old man who was in custody in relation to your accommodation.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d09bce5e-138c-4fc4-85ac-656bdc279bdb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-06 23:33:23</date>
      <author>mail.wlsnsw.org.au</author>
      <email>brigette_walters@googlemail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>93.118.70.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>When friends failed to return, Bannan decided to get changed and driving ban drive back to Birmingham, as he turned across the road and mounting a grass verge. The food fanatic was found to have 61mg of alcohol to 100ml of breath the legal limit is 35. He was given a six-month driving ban which also formed part of the US transportation department. Craig Bellamy was banned from driving for 56 driving ban days and fined &amp;#163;660 today after admitting a motoring offence.

Here is my weblog :: car insurance for convicted drivers ( mail.wlsnsw.org.au - https://mail.wlsnsw.org.au/groups/emailquestions/wiki/5f888/Some_Emerging_Options_For_Speedy_Tactics_For_Driving_Offences.html )</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>9be6af36-3704-4fb2-940e-f3fe8e4d9fea</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>