<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>O the Martyrs of the True Path </title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;img src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f11%2fimran+shocked.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Extraordinary Rendition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;Hakim Hazik&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;I condemn the reckless killing of Brother Hakimullah by the arrogant imperialist Americans. They have droned the peace process. I cannot begin to describe the contributions of the late Brother to the world peace. He shot Brother Imam in the chest after the recitation of the Holy Quran and in the back for good measure and for the glory of the Ummah. A befitting end for someone who violates the orders of Allah SWT and Hakimullah RA. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;For the first time in a decade the Ummah is united on a single point agenda to come together and lie down in front of the NATO tankers. Such awe inspiring occasions are rare in the history of nations. We are united from Tarnol toll plaza to Torkham check post and from Bani Gala to Aitchison College. Under the shadow of this flag we are one.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Let me take this opportunity to salute Chaudhry Nisar Ali. He is the only leader in the country with a vision. If he is ready to lead, I am ready to follow. Together, we can bomb all the churches at the hour of worship, behead the soldiers of the infidel Pakistan army and arrange them in neat rows for Umar Media to film, plant explosives in the Qissa Khawani Bazaar and in the passenger buses to celebrate the blessed memory of the late Brother.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;The most shameful thing we have done in our history is to become a part of the war that is not our war. When we established Pakistan, it was to make sure that we were free to live according to the tenets of Islam and free to kill one another without outside interference. What is the point of sovereignty if we cannot bomb our own marketplaces and slaughter our own polio teams?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;I know the West better than anyone else, including West London where I go for charity balls. I married into the West and was accepted by them as one of their own. They can not face someone who stands up to them. If we rise like Maula Jat and say, &amp;lsquo;Are you new my lovely&amp;rsquo;, they will start shaking in their boots, stop the drone strikes and scuttle out of Afghanistan with their tails between their legs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;We can establish the rule of law in Afghanistan after the Americans leave. After we have killed the last doctor from Medicins Sans Frontieres and bombed the last school built by the USAID, women will die at home with honour, dignity and puerperal sepsis. Meanwhile, my children will go to Eton and I will have physiotherapy in the London Othtopaedics Hospital in a peaceful manner with intact sovereignty and preserved honour.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Pakistan is the seventh nuclear power of the world. We will rise like the spirit of General Mustache ul Haq from the deserts of Khairpur Tamewali and shoot down the drones which breach our sovereignty. We have squadrons of F-16 flying falcon which we have paid for, in full, with the help of the IMF extended credit facility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica; min-height: 14px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="color: #222222; margin: 0px; font-size: 12px; font-family: Helvetica;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Tie your dog under a canopy and trust in God. Don&amp;rsquo;t let him near a mobile phone, unless you want him to achieve martyrdom.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-11-12 13:18:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2013-11-12 13:30:01</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>O-the-Martyrs-of-the-True-Path-</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="5d0623ed-a566-4181-b072-0d1217c56ea2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-11-30 09:19:23</date>
      <author>behind the music</author>
      <email>irene-hatfield@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.82.177.42</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>As a result the Deutsche Wochenschau, this means The A language like german Daily Newsreel was made and extended to use till get rid of wwii. So, prior to spg one of them warm Spanish terms with your fan, process. Asian words are more complex than their european brethren, but to my opinion, the journey is worth it.

I need to eliminate 20 fat here  behind the music - http://www.djassatube.com/groups/safe-and-sound-operating-tips-for-the-sunshine/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c002d706-09f8-4108-9e41-7accfdefd260" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-12-05 20:21:59</date>
      <author>mbfx system scam review</author>
      <email>dontepaltridge@t-online.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>50.115.169.21</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Individuals Year With The Rooster. It also involves the sovereign state of Monaco. These firms page layout a special internet site per express.

one teaspoon finely chopped thyme this:  mbfx system scam review - http://www.yourshortlink.net/mbfx-system </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="692a69cc-9b12-413d-8af9-2d41b6b3d85d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-12-22 08:45:18</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia diet pill</author>
      <email>lornaruiz@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.174.69</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>We are a group of volunteers and starting a new scheme in our community. Your website offered us with valuable info to work on. You&amp;#39;ve done a formidable job and our whole community will be grateful to you.

Have a look at my web blog;  garcinia cambogia diet pill - http://www.gnbl.or.kr/85braille/?document_srl=220456 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="dfa3c58d-6ab7-472a-8461-dd50073b65c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-12-26 06:28:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>antonettamock@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>199.119.226.55</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Pretty section of content. I just stumbled upon your website and in accession capital to assert that I acquire in fact loved account your blog posts. Anyway I&amp;#39;ll be subscribing on your feeds or even I achievement you access consistently rapidly.

Here is my web-site;  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://meituitu.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c4328d5b-0337-4ec9-a425-3477d69a16f6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-30 17:09:47</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>utamouton@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.71.91.151</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Great post. I will be going through many of these issues as well..

my page ...  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://packparachute.org </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6daaa803-5252-47a5-aa73-aa768e790b50" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-02 05:11:53</date>
      <author>miracle garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>carmelogaines@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>23.90.4.29</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Wow, fantastic blog layout! How long have you been blogging for? you made blogging look easy. The overall look of your website is magnificent, as well as the content!

Here is my webpage -  miracle garcinia cambogia - http://deannadimarziophotography.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="aef9575c-43e0-450b-bd94-8a78f16b3706" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 03:59:04</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>elise_gentile@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.33.60</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Write more, thats all I have to say. Literally, it seems as though you relied on the video to make your point. You definitely know what youre talking about, why throw away your intelligence on just posting videos to your blog when you could be giving us something informative to read?

my page;  pure garcinia cambogia extract - http://meituitu.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cae0e646-e011-4b25-8682-f3577ab4041e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 06:18:35</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia reviews</author>
      <email>wayne-visconti@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>91.108.182.21</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I will right away clutch your rss feed as I can&amp;#39;t in finding your e-mail subscription link or e-newsletter service. Do you have any? Please allow me realize in order that I may subscribe. Thanks.

Feel free to surf to my page;  pure garcinia cambogia reviews - http://geneessence.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1cf1bf9d-cc61-48ae-80db-882d5221398b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 12:44:42</date>
      <author>quran learning</author>
      <email>efren_stagg@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>203.223.94.109</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Everyone loves what you guys are usually up too. Such clever work and coverage! Keep up the awesome works guys I&amp;#39;ve added you guys to my blogroll.1

Check out my blog post -  quran learning - http://www.quranteaching.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="60206887-c6ad-4db9-898d-298e86112372" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-01-03 16:01:59</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia reviews</author>
      <email>lanora-selfe@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.143.135.21</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I visited many websites but the audio quality for audio songs existing at this web page is really superb.

My webpage ...  pure garcinia cambogia reviews - http://maxnettv.net </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6c651e4d-dbc0-47a6-9dc6-ba8867d8267d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-03 00:50:28</date>
      <author>Allnet Flat</author>
      <email>vernabrobst@gmx.net</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.3.60.252</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>George Muschler, an odd select but heaps of programming, before comely head of Zaragoza and Sporting. If liberals want more people to pay taxes don&amp;#39;t you think it would be better to have more people working to increase the size of the tax base. We shouldn&amp;#39;t focus our energies on the Xbox One reveal event kicks off online football managing director on a computerfor gratuitous: You can download to your disc where challenging and complicated items are on a halting.

My weblog;  Allnet Flat - http://ow.ly/unJvS </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5d64b86a-ed0f-49dd-ad3d-37e4c96bb743" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-07 09:00:09</date>
      <author>http://www.freeamazonitems.com/</author>
      <email>harriet.lindell@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>110.86.185.35</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is appropriate time to make some plans for the future and it is time to be happy. I have read this post and if I could I wish to suggest you some interesting things or advice. Perhaps you could write next articles referring to this article. I want to read even more things about it!

my blog ...  http://www.freeamazonitems.com/ - http://www.freeamazonitems.com/true-religion-slim-fit-jeans-men-p-339/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a427fa39-cdc4-434b-819f-0f148fff2f7b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-23 02:18:59</date>
      <author>http://www.161993up.com</author>
      <email>dawn_dominquez@gawab.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.227.212.175</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Howdy! I know this is somewhat off topic but I was wondering if you knew where I could locate a captcha plugin for my comment form? I&amp;#39;m using the same blog platform as yours and I&amp;#39;m having problems finding one? Thanks a lot!

Feel free to surf to my site:  http://www.161993up.com - http://www.161993up.com </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>