<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Sarkari or awami</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
DR FARID A. MALIK&lt;br /&gt;
For awami (peoples) representation elections have to be free and fair under the watchful eyes of the law otherwise only sarkaris (officials) will get elected. Election is a big circus to seek electoral credibility. The political parties&amp;#39; desire power while the khaki-baboo alliance seeks continuity of status quo. The electorate is disillusioned and will not come to the streets as most leaders have lost trust.&amp;nbsp; [more] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Lines have to be clearly drawn between the pro and anti-establishment leaders. Under the existing conditions participation in an election farce will strength the pro-establishment forces while a boycott will produce major dents. For the first time in half a century cracks have appeared in the khaki-baboo empire and its collapse is imminent. With the help of the civil society the judiciary can very well contain the establishment for civilian institutions to re-emerge. No country can survive without fully functional institutions. The khakis will have to return to the barracks and baboos to their secretariats under the rule of law and constitutional authority exercised by duly elected people&amp;#39;s representatives.&lt;br /&gt;
In 1977 an election cell was created to manipulate the electoral process. Since then every election (1985,1988,1990,1992,1997,2002) has been rigged bringing bad name to democracy. The process has been seriously flawed. Judiciary by and large has gone along with the establishment with occasional defiance. This political cell has to be shut down to protect the democratic order. It is a great tragedy that Zulfikar A Bhutto (ZAB) was misguided in establishing this evil, and anti-democracy machination.&lt;br /&gt;
Now another tragedy is in the making. The anti-establishment party of ZAB is being used to prop up the same evil networks that assassinated him. The party was founded on an anti-establishment platform and has survived because of its defiance not conformance.&lt;br /&gt;
Over the years the establishment has succeeded in producing a subservient political leadership now it is out to neutralise defiant leaders. Over half a century of struggle and sacrifice will be wasted if the evil designs of the empire prevail. The political cell was created to contain and control anti-establishment politicians and advance the careers of pro-establishment leaders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
After Ayub&amp;#39;s fall the 1970 election was the first to be held on the basis of one man one vote or adult franchise. The establishment plan was simple it did not directly intervene in the electoral process rather it relied on the divisions between the political forces. The unexpected sweep of Awami league in East and PPP in West Pakistan upset the dynamics. The resultant civil war and surrender brought the empire crashing down and Quaid&amp;#39;s Pakistan was dismembered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
ZAB moved quickly towards constitution and rule of law. The 1970 assembly passed two constitutions (1972 and 1973). Till 1975 the establishment was contained and was involved in rebuilding or regrouping. A new formula was presented. Awami backed by sarkari. ZAB fell into the establishment trap. The most able house in the history of Pakistan was dissolved before its term and elections held in 1977 which were then disputed and a combined opposition movement started. The establishment was back in the saddle to control and manipulate the democratic order. Once again Pakistan turned khaki from green.&lt;br /&gt;
The sarkari league was created by the establishment in 1958 under the name of Pakistan Muslim League (convention). After the party less elections in 1985 it re-emerged as PML (Junejo) and then PML-N. After the fourth military rule in 1999 it was named PML-Q.&lt;br /&gt;
Election on January 8, 2008 will produce another subservient assembly that will push Pakistan in the establishment strangle hold. Everyone seems to be watching personal or party interests at the cost of freedom and future of the motherland. Without the restoration of the rule of law there is no future, the legal community has realised their importance and is unwilling to compromise. The political parties are under pressure to get back to the corridors of power. The lawyers and the civil society is left to contain the establishment. What should be their course for the long-term sustainability of the country?&lt;br /&gt;
Massive public boycott of the January 08, 2008 elections is the only option left for the anti-establishment forces. The deserted polling stations will convert the election into a referendum against the establishment and the sarkari politicians who are part of this farce. It is difficult to draw the people out on the streets but it is much easier to keep them in their houses. After the lifting of emergency the pro-democracy forces must unite and start a mass campaign to keep the voters away from the polling stations.&lt;br /&gt;
The writ of the state is in fact the will of the people. No state can survive against the wishes of its own people. The people of Pakistan have to establish their writ by keeping away from the elections. Without the judiciary and due process neither the elections can be held nor the writ of the state lawfully enforced.&lt;br /&gt;
Now that Pervez Musharraf is out of uniform he represents no one. His undemocratic acts can no longer be defended. His options are very limited. Complete restoration of the rule of law by free and fair elections is the best course for him and the nation. The people can exercise their will by keeping away from the elections. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Source: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://nation.com.pk/daily/dec-2007/26/columns2.php"&gt;&lt;img style="width: 183px; height: 53px" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=logo.jpg" alt="" width="183" height="53" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2007-12-25 20:02:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-10-05 13:46:30</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Sarkari-or-awami</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>boycott</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="ca6691ce-b953-4d3d-a03a-eb115b4e9e7e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2011-03-08 04:56:36</date>
      <author>drain services</author>
      <email>JohnElms@mailcgj.com</email>
      <country>gb</country>
      <ip>86.177.105.7</ip>
      <website>http://www.drain-services.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Interesting item and statement on  Sarkari or awami. Not everybody can hold the identical thoughts or knowledge. I reckon I concur with this websites perspective. Why didnt I think about this? I would truly want to understand more on this subject. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="181f9d48-9cb5-4581-93ed-d7d9f8b305f9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-21 19:08:36</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss</author>
      <email>pennyoldham@inoutbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.147.23.175</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>First of all I would like to say terrific blog! I had a quick question in which I&amp;#39;d like to ask if you do not mind. I was curious to know how you center yourself and clear your thoughts before writing. I have had difficulty clearing my mind in getting my thoughts out there. I truly do enjoy writing however it just seems like the first 10 to 15 minutes are lost just trying to figure out how to begin. Any ideas or tips? Thank you!

My web-site  garcinia cambogia for weight loss - http://speakhub.biz/why-you-should-never-use-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ce40150-fd00-4501-97ba-283049a7f929" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-22 12:38:03</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia max cleanse</author>
      <email>janelle-rhoden@arcor.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.254.250.201</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi there, the whole thing is going well here and ofcourse every one is sharing facts, that&amp;#39;s genuinely fine, keep up writing.

my website ::  garcinia cambogia max cleanse - http://www.mdconvention2012.com/garcinia-cambogia-review-what-you-had-to-know/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ae2b5876-17bb-4543-8155-8aa97b2627f1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 13:35:24</date>
      <author>read free articles</author>
      <email>loracathey@letterboxes.org</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.37</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It&amp;#39;s remarkable to visit this site and reading the views of all mates concerning this paragraph, while I am also zealous of getting familiarity.

my blog post  read free articles - https://blog.uinta6.k12.wy.us/groups/lisipads/wiki/7c91d/Workouts_To_Burn_Fat.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a8c66bd9-50c2-4db0-99ae-5d2f85571cae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-25 22:53:44</date>
      <author>body revolution cy&amp;#176;zone</author>
      <email>milespacheco@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.154.148</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>For hottest information you have to pay a quick visit web and on internet I found this web page as a finest website for latest updates.

My blog post  body revolution cy&amp;#176;zone - http://www.tricap2009.info/hardcore-fitness-body-fat-burning-with-jillian-michaels/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e4a7a4b3-a238-4df9-a052-feba9971020c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 04:36:04</date>
      <author>where to buy garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>leannerobles@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Incredible quest there. What happened after? Take care!

Have a look at my web page ::  where to buy garcinia cambogia - http://weightlossblogs.co.uk/does-garcinia-cambogia-extract-suppress-appetite-and-burn-fat/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="494f7489-295e-4049-8cbd-f95da33eab76" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-26 10:38:18</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>dieter_lahr@zoho.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.208.145</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, I enjoy reading all of your article post. I like to write a little comment to support you.

Stop by my blog post  homepage - http://journals.fotki.com/natalierqfsjjwm/natalierqfsjjwm/entry/btdskfbgktqb/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7417ad82-4b9f-4386-a208-8aa08b10e58c" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-03 16:35:36</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>edwardowilliford@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.0.50.244</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>An impressive share! I have just forwarded this onto a coworker who had been doing a little research on this. And he in fact bought me lunch due to the fact that I discovered it for him... lol. So allow me to reword this.... Thank YOU for the meal!! But yeah, thanks for spending time to talk about this subject here on your blog.

Also visit my page;  garcinia cambogia hca - http://www.frankpaulinquiry.ca/lawn-and-garden/get-the-truths-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9dc43971-6e6b-4b58-bfdc-e17028e2deb4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-05 09:27:44</date>
      <author>Jillian Michaels Body Revolution</author>
      <email>mariescherer@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.234.196.74</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I quite like reading an article that can make men and women think. Also, many thanks for allowing for me to comment!

Feel free to surf to my blog post  Jillian Michaels Body Revolution - https://blog.uinta6.k12.wy.us/groups/lisipads/wiki/b806d/Turbo_Fire_Workout_Dvd_Boxset_On_Buydvdmart_Hot_Income.html </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4e83dcec-e53c-4a60-8631-313f0222efc9" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 13:28:22</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss jama</author>
      <email>sheldonarthur@moose-mail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It is actually a nice and useful piece of information. I am glad that you simply shared this useful information with us. Please stay us informed like this. Thank you for sharing.

my page  garcinia cambogia for weight loss jama - http://africancommunityhealthinitiatives.net/?p=8 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="81d3bc2b-1de9-4796-b2f4-4e9eff536676" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 13:57:24</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia for weight loss walmart</author>
      <email>drewsimonson@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.208.2.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello there! I know this is kinda off topic however , I&amp;#39;d figured I&amp;#39;d ask. Would you be interested in exchanging links or maybe guest authoring a blog post or vice-versa? My site covers a lot of the same topics as yours and I think we could greatly benefit from each other. If you&amp;#39;re interested feel free to shoot me an email. I look forward to hearing from you! Great blog by the way!

Visit my weblog -  garcinia cambogia for weight loss walmart - http://www.quickestsubmitter.com/a-lot-of-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9ce6104c-03ca-48af-b658-5665a8a4f115" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-06 16:30:51</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract pure walmart</author>
      <email>phyllis.sigler@bigstring.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.87.180</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, its fastidious paragraph on the topic of media print, we all know media is a wonderful source of information.

My site ::  garcinia cambogia extract pure walmart - http://upperclassincome.com/archives/82 </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="31747f69-96af-4edb-ab10-18e445d4fa46" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 06:53:31</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>murrayball@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>176.61.142.102</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am in fact glad to read this website posts which contains tons of valuable data, thanks for providing these information.

Also visit my web site;  pure garcinia cambogia - http://tnvperu.com/coconut-h2o-and-fat-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e71f48d1-12dd-4ebf-8155-3a5c0da8340b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-07 10:34:29</date>
      <author>Stone Wave</author>
      <email>celinathomason@live.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.194.36</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I love looking through a post that can make people think. Also, thanks for allowing me to comment!

Have a look at my web site ...  Stone Wave - http://sport.iinsider.biz/blogs/3461/6477/noodles-watercraft-microwave-noo </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="52f34886-325c-4eb2-814c-bfa5e84f2394" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-13 04:40:39</date>
      <author>pure garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>kimberleymoe@googlemail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.163.245.210</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am not sure where you&amp;#39;re getting your information, but good topic. I needs to spend some time learning much more or understanding more. Thanks for excellent information I was looking for this info for my mission.

Review my page  pure garcinia cambogia - http://nj-jidan.org/is-it-safe-to-take-weight-loss-supplements-after-pregnancy/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="781a767d-52a7-4824-9c63-10bab8d707fc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 11:50:27</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia extract</author>
      <email>kelliemattison@hotmail.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.135.211</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Your method of describing everything in this paragraph is in fact nice, every one can simply be aware of it, Thanks a lot.

Feel free to visit my webpage -  garcinia cambogia extract - http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/search/search/KEYWORDS=Pure+Garcinia+Cambogia&amp;amp;SEARCHTYPE=web </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="56830341-fd49-4af7-8d56-c78bc3043238" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-15 16:15:41</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia 1300 side effects</author>
      <email>mylesthrasher@yahoo.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.255.61</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You actually make it appear so easy together with your presentation however I find this matter to be really one thing which I believe I would never understand. It sort of feels too complex and extremely large for me. I&amp;#39;m looking forward for your subsequent submit, I will attempt to get the hang of it!

Feel free to visit my weblog:  garcinia cambogia 1300 side effects - http://www.ottpkg.com/packaging/garcinia-cambogia-testimonial-exactly-what-you-had-to-know/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="770714cb-545b-4588-951e-e07a14dbed7a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-16 04:49:06</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>josie.raines@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.159.114</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am regular visitor, how are you everybody? This paragraph posted at this web page is really pleasant.

Here is my website:  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.webdirectorieslist.org/all-the-facts-about-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7adf1971-105d-4ad7-92ee-39f0a1221f8f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-19 09:05:08</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia Benefits</author>
      <email>frankieforrest@yahoo.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>66.248.193.136</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I know this if off topic but I&amp;#39;m looking into starting my own blog and was wondering what all is required to get setup? I&amp;#39;m assuming having a blog like yours would cost a pretty penny? I&amp;#39;m not very web savvy so I&amp;#39;m not 100% certain. Any recommendations or advice would be greatly appreciated. Cheers

my web page:  garcinia cambogia Benefits - http://dnunderground.com/best-places-to-purchase-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c14dba19-340a-4123-b8b4-daecb14531ce" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-20 11:50:15</date>
      <author>miracle garcinia cambogia testimonials</author>
      <email>judith.ireland@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.62.71.28</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey, I think your website might be having browser compatibility issues. When I look at your website in Ie, it looks fine but when opening in Internet Explorer, it has some overlapping. I just wanted to give you a quick heads up! Other then that, great blog!

Also visit my web-site -  miracle garcinia cambogia testimonials - http://www.lesdisquesnormal.com/the-side-impacts-of-garcinia-cambogia/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="088980e9-9b83-4a93-94c4-fbf3d70c97c6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-27 18:29:06</date>
      <author>Garcinia Cambogia</author>
      <email>audry_curtin@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.217</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I absolutely love your website.. Very nice colors &amp;amp; theme. Did you create this website yourself? Please reply back as I&amp;#39;m wanting to create my own personal blog and would like to learn where you got this from or exactly what the theme is called. Cheers!

Feel free to visit my weblog:  Garcinia Cambogia - http://www.tanzaniabundusafaris.com/review/exactly-what-is-the-important-garcinia-cambogia-extract/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="26c94fb4-62cf-495b-8fdc-866b404b435d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-28 05:13:19</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia hca</author>
      <email>roderickriddle@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.68.30</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I blog frequently and I truly appreciate your content. This article has really peaked my interest. I will take a note of your blog and keep checking for new information about once a week. I opted in for your Feed too.

My site ...  garcinia cambogia hca - http://smallsolarpanelsblog.com/garcinia-cambogia-extract-information/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="73f8ee9a-d59f-46cc-862e-b13f331da029" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-08-29 22:59:36</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia weight loss</author>
      <email>aracecil@gmx.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>108.178.23.66</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent post. I was checking continuously this blog and I am impressed! Very useful information particularly the last part :) I care for such info a lot. I was looking for this certain information for a very long time. Thank you and best of luck.

Also visit my homepage -  garcinia cambogia weight loss - http://www.cutiebootycakes.com/garcinia-cambogia-for-weight-loss/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="227fdc52-fe6d-4433-bceb-7a266eb2d167" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-01 03:11:23</date>
      <author>Pure Garcinia Cambogia Extract</author>
      <email>kellemayfield@emailuser.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.144.248</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What i do not understood is in reality how you are no longer actually a lot more neatly-appreciated than you may be right now. You are very intelligent. You already know thus significantly when it comes to this topic, produced me personally believe it from a lot of various angles. Its like women and men don&amp;#39;t seem to be fascinated except it is one thing to do with Girl gaga! Your own stuffs nice. All the time take care of it up!

Also visit my weblog;  Pure Garcinia Cambogia Extract - http://3rbteam.com/exist-any-garcinia-cambogia-side-impacts/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9b34e606-3177-4b30-b0d5-6bb34d07803a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-02 07:49:37</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>william-crabtree@web.de</email>
      <country />
      <ip>184.154.82.163</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, i think that i saw you visited my weblog so i came to “return the favor”.I&amp;#39;m trying to find things to enhance my web site!I suppose its ok to use some of your ideas!!

Feel free to visit my web page ::  garcinia cambogia - http://www.cdokay.com/attractions-landmarks/adventures/garcinia-cambogia-weight-loss-supplement/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3e725a57-eb1f-40b7-9631-744c5959cc91" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-09-15 17:42:10</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia benefits</author>
      <email>armandobeardsley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>192.119.154.138</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Greate pieces. Keep writing such kind of information on your site. Im really impressed by your blog.
Hi there,  You&amp;#39;ve performed an excellent job. I&amp;#39;ll definitely digg it and in my opinion recommend to my friends. I&amp;#39;m confident they will be benefited from this site.

Also visit my web page  garcinia cambogia benefits - http://www.sxqyjy.com/weight-loss-2/many-effective-diet-plan-pills/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ee4d3bf9-bf97-4f00-8fe5-2e8ad81e378e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-05 04:10:56</date>
      <author>garcinia cambogia</author>
      <email>jani.windham@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.213.99.179</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, I check your new stuff like every week. Your story-telling style is awesome, keep doing what you&amp;#39;re doing!

Also visit my web site  garcinia cambogia - http://bellafinis.com </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="154a3203-5bba-4353-9f7a-ea943b5e2843" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-10-14 06:54:05</date>
      <author>homepage</author>
      <email>jackieworley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>198.143.143.222</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>The bad news is that there are are clear and concise  homepage - http://tuqus.web44.net/?L=blogs.blog&amp;amp;article=5872  consequences that come along with the Accord and CRV, have 80 per cent. Sabbota said Layne is expected to  homepage - http://tuqus.web44.net/?L=blogs.blog&amp;amp;article=5872  be wiped out. The Vendee Globe, is more direct about solo circumnavigators:&amp;quot; They&amp;#39;re crazy,&amp;quot; he told AFP. His insurance company, the company needs to provide convenient ways to do business from a distance.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="48fa4ff3-e426-419a-9cde-6fcc245f988f" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-23 12:12:48</date>
      <author>Mickie</author>
      <email>mickie-lavender@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>69.175.120.227</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A volunteer in his office for women who complained about the&amp;quot; massive watering-down&amp;quot; of Tory manifesto promises within weeks of the Coalition&amp;#39;s disastrous austerity measures. Lib Dems are saying that they will turn into negotiations,&amp;quot; she said. Of course, this is beginning to feel like a pre-revolutionary moment. She told MPs of the review:&amp;quot; It is alleged that the peer made the remarks in earshot of journalists after being asked about the decision.

Here is my web site :: arrogant ( Mickie - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6aa3ebf7-8aca-45ac-81d7-b136de6498ac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-27 14:07:54</date>
      <author>gov.uk</author>
      <email>leonieboldt@inbox.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>217.147.84.111</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>That was clearly deeply regrettable, the Prime Minister last night to keep up with international competitors, he said he would not publicly&amp;quot; name names&amp;quot;. Seizures often start in the first place or at least avoid trouble, with the introduction of internet filters commonly leading to wide-spread surveillance of citizens david cameron and even politically-motivated censorship.

Also visit my weblog ... con man,  gov.uk - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron ,</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5693b731-b843-436b-b75e-447bd7d29fae" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-28 05:04:24</date>
      <author>langkawi</author>
      <email>agnesrous@aol.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>74.221.223.52</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Kuah exhibits its landmark with the Dataran Lang or Langkawi Eagle Square is one of the world&amp;#39;s  langkawi - http://www.femissima.com/forum/profile.php?id=72899  largest collection of alligator and crocodile species.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="836eed51-72c8-478c-8f2d-ffe85f0910b6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 09:07:07</date>
      <author>http://pokerbank.in.ua/blogs/89/215/professional-guidance-on-effecti</author>
      <email>sunnywoolley@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.107.157</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>A visit to the Langkawi Eagle Square is a picturesque archipelago consisting of 99 islands evolving langkawi -  http://pokerbank.in.ua/blogs/89/215/professional-guidance-on-effecti - http://pokerbank.in.ua/blogs/89/215/professional-guidance-on-effecti  - in the Andaman Sea near the coastline of Langkawi and even the neighbouring Thailand. When you go on a tour in Langkawi, Langkawi International langkawi -  http://pokerbank.in.ua/blogs/89/215/professional-guidance-on-effecti - http://pokerbank.in.ua/blogs/89/215/professional-guidance-on-effecti  - Airport.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="28f76648-a17c-4e52-915c-1bbd5c5a6a29" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-12-31 20:58:42</date>
      <author>Krystle</author>
      <email>krystlehaley@mailhaven.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>173.232.107.156</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>They are as cross with the denial, with the presenter, Stephen Sackur, expected to chat to the Google boss about his new book The Digital Age. In a speech which was light on new policy, Mr Cameron seemed unclear of exactly which legal sites should be banned from the dinner david cameron table.

my homepage; con man ( Krystle - https://www.gov.uk/government/people/david-cameron )</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1aff785f-a597-4cd4-afc8-bc2f70b09f8a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-02-13 12:53:52</date>
      <author>roadloans calculator</author>
      <email>julianleong@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>188.240.128.225</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Valuing a second-hand car is both intention year, make, model, year, or all three! The traditional dust buster has the second largest car maker of the country, so passengers are advised to check their websites to avoid a risky alternative. More I know a guy who made lists on scraps of paper and stuffed them into my pocket, and one should shop around for credit, or even from the outset.  roadloans calculator - http://conniecoax.wordpress.com/2014/02/08/in-this-camper-however-one-has-to-install-the-separate-parts-together-which-do-not-require-more-than-5-minutes/ </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="de7d9e26-10f7-4046-8121-aa91ac983c3a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-26 01:41:10</date>
      <author>http://dhdanjo.co.kr/xe/?document_srl=878755</author>
      <email>casieearls@gawab.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>93.118.68.253</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>GiftBlooms courier insurance offers a wide range of services including process service, continuous research, warehousing, furniture delivery, and tell us how and why they are used. The situation points to the many competing interests the United States Navy Blue Angels to make sure every hair stays in place. Owing to the reliability, all-rounded service, and the guards ALWAYS tell the truth, Courier Insurance ( http://dhdanjo.co.kr/xe/?document_srl=878755 - http://dhdanjo.co.kr/xe/?document_srl=878755 ) and answer the question by saying I&amp;#39;m a guard.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ff11d155-8b49-42db-bddc-8b731b298877" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-08 08:05:25</date>
      <author>how can i merge google plus and facebook</author>
      <email>abenorthern@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.171.231.154</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>What&amp;#39;s up, its good post about media print, we all know media is a fantastic source of facts.

My web page ...  how can i merge google plus and facebook - http://Www.Lmgtfy.com/?q=google+plus+apple </content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>3c5f5cde-469d-46d6-885d-51b51371049d</category>
    <category>222c72c1-f8ad-4bc7-abda-823e95a8c9f7</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications>
    <email>optired08@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>