<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Admin</author>
  <title>Ayaz</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;img style="font-size: medium; letter-spacing: 0px;" src="/JDP/image.axd?picture=2013%2f7%2fAyaz.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Mudassar Bashir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Lhor Di Var&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Where have we left our heart? Where shall we find it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;When looking for the loved one, lose yourself and search&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;(Master Altaf Hussain)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;A look at his life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: medium; letter-spacing: 0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 13px; font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial; color: #232323;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;According to one group of historians, the name of Ayaz ranks the highest among those who laid the foundations of Lahore. While this may not be wholly true, it is certainly true that Malik Abul Najam Ayaz gets the credit for bringing Lahore back to life after it had been laid waste in the war against Raja Anang Pal. It is said about Ayaz that he was born a slave. In those days, slaves were bought and sold according to their rank, their color, their ancestry, their age and their personal qualities. In 396 Hijri (1006 CE) a group of about 120 slaves was brought to Ghazni. [more]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;At that time Ayaz was excessively thin and looked pale due to some illness. Nobody bothered to bid for him and the rest of the 119 slaves were sold. Gradually, Ayaz rose to become the chief of royal slaves due to his hard work. When Mahmood died, Ayaz was in Ghazni but his love for Lahore brought him back. He laid the foundation stone to rebuild the Royal Fort and built the protective wall around the city. He was popular among the people of Lahore and the stories of his bravery and generosity can still be heard. He is mentioned in works of poetry, in addition to books of history. Some of the poets have depicted the relations of Mahmood and Ayaz in a negative way, whereas Iqbal has seen this relationship in a positive way. Due to his poetry the names of Mahmood and Ayaz enjoyed a new fame in the twentieth cectury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; min-height: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;His date of death is disputed among historians, however the majority view is that he died in 433 AH, 1041 CE.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; min-height: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Building:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;This tomb is one of the oldest in Lahore. Before partition, this place was also called Malik Ilyas&amp;rsquo;s Khanqah. Kanhayya Lal writes in Tarikh e Lahore:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; min-height: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Adjacent to this tomb was a big garden, which has disappeared with the passage of time. There are currently some shops near this tomb. During the reign of Maharaja Ranjit Singh, a mint was based here. Therefore the bazar is called Taxali. The building of the tomb is old. The platform is in the middle of the courtyard. This shrine in much respected among the citizens.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; min-height: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;Now a days, if you go to Sooha Bazar from Shah Alami Chowk, there is a mosque called Jamia Masjid Hazrat Ahmed, across the road from Mission High School. The mausoleum is in front of the mosque entrance. The building of the mausoleum is round with an oblong dome. The place is quite small, not more than two hundred square feet. Below the centre of the dome is the mound slab of the grave. There is an information plaque next to the door of the mausoleum. On this one can find Ayaz&amp;rsquo;s name, his date of death and a description of his association with Mahmood.&amp;nbsp; The mound slab is covered with a green sheet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; min-height: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0px; font-size: medium;"&gt;At the head of the grave oil lamps can be seen. The denizens of Lahore consider Ayaz a sufi and a religious figure. Nobody recognises him as a ruler or a general. People visit here say offer salutations and prayers. This mausoleum is in better state than many others in Lahore. The environs have been encroached upon after partition. Now the remaining area is so small that further encroachment is not possible.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2013-07-27 02:59:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-02-02 08:48:17</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Ayaz</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="3a104aa8-4221-4ed7-9c2d-86f5ae9cd579" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-29 13:29:38</date>
      <author>Tariq Maqbool</author>
      <email>tariqmaq2000@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>ca</country>
      <ip>96.55.204.135</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Excellent, Mudassar the standard of your research and the in depth knowledge you provided in this article is really excellent and you are pride of all Lahorites for showing your love and dedication  towards this wonderful and beautiful city.  May Allah give more power to your pen. Aameen.
</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="857cbf27-d594-4306-a612-00049ac58233" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2013-07-31 06:09:02</date>
      <author>Anwar Hossain</author>
      <email>anwar01740@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>180.149.7.59</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>I will definitely share it with others.Thanks for sharing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="86a35e9c-ad3a-472f-aa86-2b5378ac70c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="True">
      <date>2013-08-30 18:16:02</date>
      <author>menopause treatment</author>
      <email>mystyle825@gmail.com</email>
      <country>bd</country>
      <ip>117.18.231.52</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>yes. i agree with  you.thanks for this nice historic informative article. 1 question to you &amp;quot;you are a experienced historian ?&amp;quot;</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0a57dc82-81d6-49e7-9755-061fb8028037" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-28 20:47:50</date>
      <author>best weight loss apps for android</author>
      <email>lavonnemcbrien@yahoo.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>198.52.223.208</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Family and friends may be the best resource in accomplishing your goal. Including snacks or even one little bit of food, because at the end of the week whenever you review of your food diary, you may be shocked at how much food you consumed. When you lose weight quick it happens through the entire body and never in isolated locations thus you must learn that you need to shed weight all over your body to acheive more visible and defined abs.

Look at my page;  best weight loss apps for android - http://En.wikipedia.org/wiki/Weight_loss </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="eaa864c9-decf-4b73-a38b-ed15405d61cd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2016-01-10 14:40:38</date>
      <author>Suzanne</author>
      <email>tarendunlap@web.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>201.172.101.220</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>There was the occasional brilliant spot for Hodgson, especially in Ross Barkley&amp;#39;s first half game and, until the targets, a decent efficiency from Phil Jones and Chris Smalling at centre-back.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="174fabeb-63ab-438e-8432-19b6216c11fc" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-04-26 20:13:42</date>
      <author>BHW</author>
      <email>maritzaeden@t-online.de</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>114.37.247.137</ip>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey, I think your site might be having browser compatibility issues. When I look at your website in Opera, it looks fine but when opening in Internet Explorer, it has some overlapping. I just wanted to give you a quick heads up! Other then that, great blog!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9762ae2f-c469-4ad7-af4b-4807476c8cbb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2017-05-06 10:59:00</date>
      <author>florriehaataja.weebly.com</author>
      <email>kathryn.idriess@inbox.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>114.44.203.124</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hey there, You&amp;#39;ve performed a great job. I&amp;#39;ll certainly digg it and individually recommend to my friends. I am sure they&amp;#39;ll be benefited from this web site.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>tariqmaq2000@hotmail.com</email>
    <email>anwar01740@gmail.com</email>
    <email>mystyle825@gmail.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>